Chapter 1901: Formation Calms Sea Area

Five lumps of white light, flashing abruptly in the sky, brought Fang Yuan, Miao Ming Shen and the others from the Merit Obelisk to here.

All five of them were familiar with the mission and headed down to get a bird's-eye view, each of them activating their investigative killer moves.

Fang Yuan was the first to observe the area and take a closer look.

His investigative methods had always been his shortcoming, but that was only relative to his enemies. When compared to Miao Ming Shen and the others, even his weaker aspects were still far superior to them.

This was a vast sea area.

The sea was raging, creating thousands of fierce waves, they were so powerful that countless sea beasts could be seen within the reflections of these ripples.

In this sea, there were five small islands.

First was jade shaking island with countless jade pillars, chiming and tinkling due to powerful winds.

Second was white bone island, it was pale white and had the corpses of beasts scattered around.

Third was hidden space island, it seemed illusory as if it did not exist.

Fourth was sword wind island, there were three tornadoes on the island that would never stop moving.

And fifth was treasure moon island, it was crescent shaped and was shrouded by the night sky at all times, every inch of sand on this island shined with faint moonlight.

Three of these five islands had begun to drift slowly with the current. Among them, sword wind island had the fastest flow and confusing direction of movement.

For the remaining two islands, jade shaking island was in danger, the pillars underneath the island were broken, and in a little while, just like the three islands, it would start to drift away on the sea surface.

As for hidden space island, however, it was very stable and remained firmly entrenched in the distance. This was because this island was filled with phantom path dao marks.

The main cause of the islands' drifting was the impact currents that ran deep under the sea.

These currents had become so large that they endangered the sea itself. Suppressing the currents, restructuring the ecology of the sea, and restoring the former five-islands chain were the contents of this large-sized mission.

Fang Yuan started to make calculations and deductions in his mind.

There were indications that this sea area had originally formed an intrinsic ecology with the five-islands chain as its core. Impact currents did not exist before, but now they were like a shark in a calm pond, causing severe destruction to the habitat and ecology of this sea area.

While Fang Yuan made his deductions, Miao Ming Shen and the rest also explored this entire sea area with their investigative methods.

They frowned and had serious expressions.

"This is a large sized mission? The difficulty is several times higher than a mid-sized mission!" Hua Die's heart sank steeply.

Feng Jiang had an ugly expression as he thought: "I tried my best earlier to improve the ecology of beehive island but it was still imperfect. This large sized mission is not about balancing the ecology, but restructuring it. Each island is in greater danger than beehive island itself. And the five islands are only part of the mission, there's still a large sea area and the underwater impact currents to resolve."

"This is very complex, to restructure the habitat of the sea area, we would need to change everything and meticulously alter the details. Without a wisdom path Gu Immortal, we will need to make many experiments and attempt the restructuring step by step. During this process, we would make many mistakes." Gui Qi Ye sighed in his heart.

Miao Ming Shen was calculating the gains and losses: "The mid-sized mission I just completed expended a large amount of my rank seven immortal materials. To restructure the ecology of this place, the resources invested, the immortal essence consumed and the energy spent will be an extremely large sum!"

The more Miao Ming Shen and the rest observed, the faster their morale slipped away.

The difficulty of the large sized mission made them feel like giving up.

The truth was, they started to regret it, following Fang Yuan blindly to accept this mission was not a wise decision.

"Brother Chu, let's plan together." At this point, Miao Ming Shen could only smile bitterly and find Fang Yuan to discuss their actions.

He was not going to give up on it, just because they took the mission did not mean they could abandon it. In fact, in order to give up the mission, they needed to exchange for another title.

Bright light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, with both time path clone and Fang Yuan making deductions at the same time, he had already arrived at a perfect plan.

He cupped his fists at Miao Ming Shen: "Brother Miao, I have already planned something, follow my instructions and we will definitely complete the mission."

Miao Ming Shen was stunned, although he did not believe it in his heart, he nodded without rebuking: "Please give the instructions Brother Chu, we will do our best!"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Brother Miao is too polite, it will be good for both of us if we work together to complete this mission. The better we complete a large sized mission, the greater the returns compared to a mid-sized mission!"

"I'm only afraid we can't complete it well." Miao Ming Shen sighed internally but did not say anything, he had already lost confidence in himself, he could only place his hopes on Fang Yuan now.

But Fang Yuan's words were comfortable for him to hear.

Fang Yuan was not high and mighty, but rather he had an attitude of equal cooperation. This was different from Shen Cong Sheng.

"Brother Miao, I want you to occupy jade shaking island to guard against the impact currents. Please ask Gui Qi Ye to station at sword wind island and make sure that it doesn't wander off. Ask Feng Jiang and Fairy Hua Die to guard treasure moon island island and white bone island respectively. I'm going to deal with hidden space island first."

Fang Yuan made the arrangements, Miao Ming Shen's group was clueless to begin with, they followed Fang Yuan's instructions.

With the four immortals in action, the islands were quickly suppressed, no longer drifting with the current, their speed of movement fell to a level that could be controlled.

Watching Fang Yuan descend on hidden space island, the four immortals had doubts in their hearts.

"Hidden space island is a phantom path island, it is the most stable place in the entire sea area, it is also the easiest part of the mission."

"Why is Chu Ying trying to deal with this island first? He should fix the other islands before trying to fix this hidden space island. After all, this island is almost non-existent, by dealing with it first, he will cause some obstruction when handling the other islands later."

"In my opinion, he should deal with the impact currents first. It is the cause behind the collapse of the five-islands chain. To restructure the ecology here, one has to deal with the root cause at the start."

Fang Yuan landed on hidden space island, quickly flying out afterwards, his speed was shocking to Miao Ming Shen and the rest.

Fang Yuan went to white bone island.

Under Hua Die's observation, Fang Yuan took out immortal materials from his immortal aperture and threw them around at will.

"He is setting up a formation!" Hua Die was seeing Fang Yuan create a formation for the first time.

Fang Yuan was skillful and experienced, the process was very fluid, Hua Die watched with a sense of appreciation and amazement.

Soon, Fang Yuan finished setting up the formation.

Hua Die's mouth opened with deep shock, she could not close it.

"Chu Ying actually used immortal materials to set up a formation! Doesn't this mean he has grandmaster attainment in formation path?"

"So he is not a transformation path Gu Immortal but a formation path Gu Immortal."

"No, not true, when he defeated Ge Wen and saved us, he clearly used transformation path methods."

"Don't tell me, he cultivates two paths?"

It was not that rare for Gu Immortals to cultivate two paths. But for Fang Yuan to be so proficient in both paths, with such high attainment, it was very rare.

White bone island's arrangements were done, Fang Yuan activated this sub-formation and connected it to the main formation on hidden space island.

Due to the effect of the immortal formation, white bone island shook intensely, it anchored itself to the sea and showed no signs of movement anymore.

Hua Die finally understood Fang Yuan's intentions: "So he was using hidden space island as the base to stabilize the other islands around it."

"Amazing, hidden space island is the best foundation for this chain, because the impact currents are useless against it. But..."

Hua Die soon realized a flaw: "But the other islands are using hidden space island as the anchor, this is the power of a formation, these impact currents will still hit these islands over time, as the formation continues to get damaged, it would break eventually, these islands will still float away in the end."

Fang Yuan did not show any inclination to dispel her doubts, soon after, he landed on the three remaining islands and set up his formation, stabilizing them all.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest looked at Fang Yuan with complex gazes.

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment was too shocking to them.

Formation path grandmasters were very rare!

And earlier, Fang Yuan's transformation path attainment was also exemplary.

With such strength, the mysteriousness of Fang Yuan intensified in the immortals' hearts.

"However, stabilizing the five sea islands is just a good start."

"The real problem are the impact currents around the sea islands."

"Without water path methods, how can we deal with the sea currents?"

Miao Ming Shen and the rest talked among themselves. They could not transmit their voices in Dragon Whale Paradise, but they could still use information path mortal Gu like letter pigeon Gu.

The impact currents that rampaged in this sea area were too huge, Miao Ming Shen and the rest could only think of using immortal methods to attack the impact currents and destroy them bit by bit.

This method was crude and wasted a lot of time and immortal essence, the biggest flaw was that attacking these currents would cause tremendous damage to the surrounding sea area.

But other than that, Miao Ming Shen and the rest did not have any good ideas.

Boom!

Right at this time, Fang Yuan rose to the sky and activated the entire Gu formation.

Each of the five islands blossomed with rushing pillars of light of various colors, the power of the Gu formation soared upwards, breaking through its original limit.

"So this is the true power of the formation!" Miao Ming Shen and the rest had changes of expressions, they were dumbfounded.

These five islands' dao marks were so dense that they could also be seen as a single gigantic immortal material. The immortal formation that Fang Yuan had set up naturally included them within the range that could be utilized.

"I am going to draw in the impact currents now. Everyone, continue to defend your islands, if any beasts attack or if any waves approach that would endanger the islands, I need you to stop them." Fang Yuan called out as his voice resounded in the sea area.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest quickly responded, saying they would do their best.

The formation buzzed and the five pillars of light gradually dissipated, turning into white light that scattered in the sky.

The light went into the seawater, staining the water around the island with a beautiful illusion of white light.

In this illusory white light, the impact currents were like a blue whale that had been stirred up by fish and shrimps, slowly moving its body, then swimming faster and faster and crashing towards jade shaking island, which was the closest.

Miao Ming Shen, who was on jade shaking island, gritted his teeth, he felt tremendous pressure, tensing up and going on full alert.

If the immortal formation's defense was not enough, such a sea current could completely crush jade shaking island if it hit directly!

Boom!

The impact currents touched the formation and created a startling explosion.

A huge wave, up to ten feet high, pounded at jade shaking island.

Miao Ming Shen immediately flew up with a cry, using his killer move to resist it.

The impact currents were slowly turned around by this and moved to the left of jade shaking island. But before they could move away, they were drawn back by white bone island's immortal formation.

The one guarding white bone island was Hua Die, and she almost groaned when she saw the sea current coming towards her.

In the discussions of Miao Ming Shen's group, the impact current was to be repelled and slowly weakened, the best outcome was to break it up and scatter it completely.

But Fang Yuan was actually attracting the impact currents actively to hit the sea islands.

This was something that Miao Ming Shen and the rest wanted to avoid at all costs.

"Chu Ying is too crazy!" Hua Die soon had no time to think as the impact currents crashed into white bone island, the entire formation resounded with a scary creaking sound, before a huge wave was created.

There were also many sea beasts caught in the waves, Hua Die put up her best effort to resist them.

Like this, the impact currents, under the constant manipulation of Fang Yuan, hit the five islands one after another.

With each impact, the power of the currents was reduced by one level, they then circled around the island and became drawn to the next point.

After the impact currents crashed into the last island, they had less than half the power and momentum as before.

At this time, Fang Yuan activated the immortal formation once again, actually making the impact currents turn around and crash into the second last island.

Thus, the Gu Immortals defending the sea islands felt great fear again.

After the impact currents struck five times and returned to jade shaking island, the power of the currents hitting the island was almost nonexistent, they had almost turned to being ordinary currents.

The five islands shook lightly as the immortal formation stabilized completely. The impact currents quickly calmed down and began to flow at an even rate consistently.

In contrast, the hearts of the four Gu Immortals stirred with huge waves of disbelief and shock!

They did not expect that Fang Yuan would resolve the impact currents using such a method.

The impact currents, while still present, had become a protective layer that surrounded the island. Around the five islands, the impact currents flowed rapidly, faster than ordinary seawater, protecting the five islands while at the same time, helping the immortal formation to stabilize the five islands' location.

If they had followed the plan of Miao Ming Shen and the others to destroy the impact currents, this sea area would surely be destroyed beyond recognition.

Fang Yuan's move, however, cleverly avoided this drawback and instead made full use of the impact currents, turning the original calamity into a blessing and greatly enhancing the natural foundation of this sea area.

This was truly an incredible achievement!

Miao Ming Shen and the others were all impressed.

It was really difficult to do this.

Not to mention the arrangement of the immortal formation, just the matter of manipulating impact currents alone, even water path Gu Immortals were not even capable of doing that. To perfectly weaken the impact currents to a certain level, one needed to make precise calculations and deductions. When the impact currents return to jade shaking island, their power must be reduced to almost nothing. A bit more or a bit less would have greatly affected the overall situation and would not have gotten the incredible near-perfect balance it had now.

"The biggest problem has been resolved, the next step will be for you to repair the immortal formation, as well as restructuring the ecology of the island, as for the things beyond the impact currents, you can ignore them." Fang Yuan smiled.

He was quite satisfied with this result.

If new impact currents formed, these existing currents would engulf them and protect the islands under the effect of the immortal formation.

Fang Yuan would leave his will and a large amount of immortal essence here, as long as they remained, the five-islands chain would be very safe.

Chapter 1902: Bullying Rank Eight

The impact currents were like hungry tigers at first, but after Fang Yuan's arrangements, they became the pet cats that defended the five-islands chain.

After Fang Yuan completed this set up, the situation was already resolved.

What followed were some finishing touches.

These were not hard to do, but they were quite strenuous and required time and effort.

Fang Yuan was not going to bother himself with them.

Thus, Fang Yuan discussed with Miao Ming Shen, they left Feng Jiang and Fairy Hua Die here while the rest returned with him.

White light shined, Fang Yuan, Miao Ming Shen, and Gui Qi Ye returned to the starting island.

Ren Xiu Ping was currently looking at the missions on this merit point.

He was an enslavement path Gu Immortal, he had many desolate beasts and a few ancient desolate beasts in his hands. These beasts all had various abilities, his methods were quite wide-ranging.

However, even Ren Xiu Ping still felt the difficulty of mid-sized missions.

Fang Yuan and the others appeared beside him, causing his heart to jump as he secretly thought: "How could these three suddenly appear at the same time? Is it a coincidence?"

Fang Yuan nodded at Ren Xiu Ping and smiled slightly.

Ren Xiu Ping was stunned, this unexpected attitude of Fang Yuan made him not know how to respond for a moment.

Fang Yuan walked towards him as the obelisk's words transformed, showing all of its large sized missions.

Fang Yuan swept his gaze around it and quickly received one of the missions.

Next, he shared this with Miao Ming Shen and Gui Qi Ye.

With another flash of light, the three of them vanished on the spot.

Ren Xiu Ping watched the entire process, his expression turned grim: "Chu Ying received a different level of mission from me, it is one tier higher. It seems that his merit points fell earlier because he was exchanging for another title to receive higher tier missions. This is very likely to be the title — really good person!"

The title of 'good person' could exchange for mid-sized missions, while 'really good person' could exchange for large sized missions.

This was a simple relationship, the Gu Immortals could easily guess it just by seeing the names.

But the problem was, so what if they realized it?

"Mid-sized missions are already so hard, large sized missions must be even harder!" Ren Xiu Ping felt gloomy internally: "And why were Miao Ming Shen and Gui Qi Ye able to move together with Chu Ying? Did they receive the same mission?"

This discovery was quite alluring to Ren Xiu Ping.

Mid-sized missions were difficult but if they had help, the difficulty would be shifted.

"Even though the merit points would be divided if many people receive the same missions, as long as we control it well, our efficiency at completing missions will increase, our overall gains will increase instead. Isn't Chu Ying doing the exact same thing now?"

Ren Xiu Ping was a savvy person, after thinking about it, he understood Fang Yuan's intentions.

Fang Yuan did not plan to hide it, in fact, he had purposely released the information.

Miao Ming Shen's group could be roped in as allies, why couldn't Ren Xiu Ping?

Their hatred earlier?

Hehe.

How could hatred compare to the benefits in front of them?

Ren Xiu Ping was not crazy, he was astute, thus, there was a chance of cooperation.

Ren Xiu Ping definitely had an alliance agreement with Shen clan.

But it did not matter.

The Merit Obelisk had such rewards that could eliminate the agreement restraints on a Gu Immortal.

Even without Fang Yuan's reminder, Ren Xiu Ping must have seen that himself already.

The second large sized mission was naturally harder than mid-sized missions, but it was no problem for Fang Yuan.

After spending some effort, Fang Yuan resolved the big issues and left Miao Ming Shen and Gui Qi Ye to settle the minor problems.

When he returned to the Merit Obelisk again, he waited a little while before Hua Die and Feng Jiang returned.

Their return meant that the first large sized mission was completed.

Fang Yuan gained five hundred merit points, while Miao Ming Shen and the rest each gained around eighty points.

Fang Yuan looked at the numbers on the merit board as he calculated, this large sized mission gave a total of nine hundred and seventy-three points.

Fang Yuan and Miao Ming Shen's group split up these points, Fang Yuan gained the bulk of them, getting five hundred points was about the same as completing a large sized mission alone.

Except that he spent way less time and effort on it.

Hua Die and Feng Jiang looked at each other, seeing the joy in each other's eyes.

In this mission, they helped Fang Yuan resist the waves and settle the minor problems at the end. They only spent some immortal essence, time, and effort, but they gained more than eighty merit points from it.

Feng Jiang thought about the beehive island mission he completed alone, he spent a group of bees, including his desolate beast yellow gyro bee, but only got eighty points in the end.

Comparing the two, helping Fang Yuan complete a large sized mission was much easier and reaped greater rewards.

"Go and join with Miao Ming Shen to complete the second mission. I'd advise that we should all exchange for a group title. With a group title, we will be able to communicate with each other." Fang Yuan suggested.

A group title was not cheap, it required a hundred merit points.

But Feng Jiang and Hua Die did not hesitate, they listened to Fang Yuan and exchanged for this title.

Fang Yuan shared the second mission with them as Feng Jiang and Hua Die teleported to where Miao Ming Shen and Gui Qi Ye were.

Fang Yuan received the third large sized mission and went ahead to deal with it.

After Miao Ming Shen and the rest completed the second mission and returned to the starting island, the four immortals gained a sum of merit points listed on the merit board.

Miao Ming Shen and Gui Qi Ye also spent merit points to exchange for a group title, it allowed the four immortals to communicate with Fang Yuan constantly.

At this point, Fang Yuan already completed his arrangements in the new mission, he shared it with Miao Ming Shen and group.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest touched the obelisk and accepted the mission Fang Yuan shared with them.

They were transported to Fang Yuan, he gave them some instructions before returning to look at the next mission on the Merit Obelisk.

Fang Yuan had an advantage in cultivating every path, his value was fully displayed here.

Even for Shen Cong Sheng, many of the missions here were impossible to complete, but Fang Yuan, from his perspective, had methods to solve most missions. What he had to do was to choose those that would give him the most benefits and complete them first.

With the help of Miao Ming Shen and the others, Fang Yuan saved a lot of time and effort, while they were also gaining much more merit points now due to the help of Fang Yuan.

The cooperation between them was of mutual benefit, but it was a problem for Ren Xiu Ping and Shen Cong Sheng.

These people watched as Miao Ming Shen's group rose in position on the merit board, surpassing them and becoming part of the top rankers, it was truly infuriating but there was nothing they could do.

Looking at Fang Yuan's merit points, he had reached several thousand! He was truly ahead, far surpassing any other immortal.

Because of their huge difference, the immortals lost all desire to catch up to him.

"Immortal Gu need at least ten thousand merit points to exchange, Chu Ying is not far away already." Many people saw this and felt complex emotions, they were in admiration but also felt dejection.

"This is so strange, how can Chu Ying successfully complete so many different types of missions?"

"He must know many secrets about this place, it is a pity that we cannot fight inside here!"

"Miao Ming Shen and his group have truly dog shit luck, how could they gain the help of Chu Ying like this?"

The immortals were extremely jealous.

Shen Cong Sheng sighed, the number of times he had sighed in the last ten days was more than the sum of the previous few years.

The ranking on the merit board was very glaring, Shen Cong Sheng's position was even lower than Hua Die and Feng Jiang.

He was a great rank eight Gu Immortal, he actually was losing to two rank six Gu Immortals, how could he allow this? It was too embarrassing.

"If I can receive a large sized mission, my rank eight strength will be fully utilized, I will definitely gain a lot of merit points. But how can I let others receive the same mission as me?

The 'really good person' title was obvious, but what was the title to share missions?

They needed to test this.

And these experiments would test Shen Cong Sheng's luck, their merit points would also be wasted.

This would aggravate their situation from the already terrible situation now.

"I can make my Shen clan Gu Immortals use their merit points, but what about Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua? If I do that, will I just push them towards Chu Ying's side?"

Shen Cong Sheng had some reservations.

He knew that his influence was continuously falling now.

After learning that Gu Immortal agreements could be removed using the rewards on the Merit Obelisk, Shen Cong Sheng became more cautious regarding his attitude towards Ren Xiu Ping and others.

Fang Yuan and Miao Ming Shen could cooperate to do missions together, he had a good lead.

Shen Cong Sheng wanted to copy him, he had to unite Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua, these two people cultivated paths that Shen clan lacked.

Shen Cong Sheng was already regretting it, he should not have forced Miao Ming Shen and the rest to spend their merit points to exchange for different rewards.

This action made the immortals go against him mentally, it was a wise action back then, but now it was a terrible idea.

This was not Shen Cong Sheng's fault, after all, he did not know anything about the Merit Obelisk earlier.

The decisions he made back then was very appropriate due to the circumstances.

There were many types of missions on the merit obelisk, mid-sized missions started to become difficult.

Thus, the more paths one cultivated, the more advantage they would have in completing missions.

Fang Yuan had already united Miao Ming Shen and the rest, Shen Cong Sheng started to learn from his mistake, he became more gentle in his approach towards Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua.

His rank eight reputation was still around, while Ren Xiu Ping's alliance agreement was not removed yet, and most importantly, Ren Xiu Ping had a grudge against Chu Ying and Miao Ming Shen.

All these reasons ensured that Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua were still on Shen clan's side.

When Fang Yuan returned to the Merit Obelisk, a new large sized mission appeared — the demonic immortal in regret crying sea has lost his senses, please cooperate with the formation and kill him!

"Regret crying sea appeared?" Fang Yuan was slightly stunned before accepting this mission.

At this point, four missions regarding the merman city had appeared, but the merman saintess selection competition had not started yet.

The influence of Fang Yuan's rebirth had greatly altered the missions on the Merit Obelisk.

With this mission, Fang Yuan would be able to retrieve regret Gu earlier.

This was a great thing!

Once he gets regret Gu, he would be able to advance his Immortal Gu to a higher rank, his progress would be faster than in his previous life.

Chapter 1903: Response Gu

The sky was cloudy, there were vicious winds and choppy waves.

This was regret crying sea area, Fang Yuan and Miao Ming Shen's group had already been here for some time.

"I regret it! I should not have killed so many people."

"I painfully regret it! I should not have chased after power, it would have been much better if I had stayed behind to look after my parents as a filial son!"

"I truly repent! I deceived everyone and concealed Immortal Gu, I let a friend, who trusted me the most, carry the blame so I could get benefits!"

Waves of crying sounds resounded in the immortals' ears like immortal killer moves that messed with their emotions.

This was the center of the regret crying sea area.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest stayed in the sky while watching Fang Yuan who was in deep contemplation, they waited patiently.

Even though they did not have much formation path foundation, they also found the grand formation at the bottom of the sea.

This was clearly the work of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, Miao Ming Shen and the rest looked at it and felt how minuscule they were.

Fang Yuan was like this in his previous life, he sighed that this formation was as vast as the sky, he would need at least dozens of years to comprehend all the profundities of this large formation.

But now, this time needed decreased drastically.

"I need about eight years to fully comprehend and gain complete understanding of this formation." Fang Yuan thought.

The reason for such an improvement was none other than Fang Yuan's earth path attainment level.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan did not have grandmaster attainment level in earth path, but this formation was a super immortal formation that was primarily earth path.

"There are no actions from regret Gu." Fang Yuan stared at a certain area at the bottom of the sea.

Fang Yuan was not surprised by this situation.

In order to stay in Dragon Whale Paradise, Fang Yuan destroyed the stone lotus island in advance. Without the stone lotus island, the venerable method used on regret Gu could not find its location, how could it activate?

According to the memories that Fang Yuan obtained on the stone lotus island, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had entered the stone lotus island and borrowed regret Gu.

Even though the stone lotus island had Red Lotus' will and his lingering methods, how could it resist a living venerable?

Red Lotus' will gave in, allowing Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable to borrow regret Gu, he even wanted to snatch Red Lotus' inheritor.

This inheritor was naturally Fang Yuan.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan chose the stone lotus island but this time, he took everything from the stone lotus island in advance, he came to the Dragon Whale Paradise because he wanted to inherit this Paradise Earth true inheritance.

"In the previous life, regret Gu flew out and transported me away. Right now, it is showing no signs of movement, it seems that I need to take action myself." Fang Yuan gained some realization.

Venerable methods were grand and powerful, Fang Yuan was teleported by regret Gu to the stone lotus island without putting up resistance.

Seeing that regret Gu did not activate, Fang Yuan was quite happy about it.

After comprehending it for several hours, Fang Yuan recollected his scattered thoughts.

He thought about it for a moment before saying to Miao Ming Shen: "We need to use the formation to get rid of this demonic immortal. However, when Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable set up this formation, even though it has unparalleled power, it can only suppress and seal, it has no offensive power. My idea is, we will set up a supplementary formation outside and activate it to kill the demonic immortal trapped within the formation."

Miao Ming Shen and the rest nodded upon hearing this idea, they agreed with it.

If they tried to break the formation and release the demonic immortal, it would be extremely dangerous.

It was obvious that this mysterious demonic immortal was someone of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's generation. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had died already but this demonic immortal was still alive.

In terms of lifespan, he had already lived for more than a hundred thousand years.

Who could live for so long?

Even Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, who had the longest lifespan among venerables, only lived for twenty five thousand years.

Having a longer lifespan than a venerable, just this point alone made the demonic immortal extremely terrifying.

"Everyone, no need to overestimate the demonic immortal." Fang Yuan smiled: "This formation has a lifespan extension method in addition to its sealing ability, this demonic immortal is in constant hibernation to extend his lifespan, this is the reason he is still alive."

Miao Ming Shen and the rest showed a more relaxed expression after he said that.

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable is truly merciful, not only did he not kill the person, after suppressing this demonic immortal, he even extended his lifespan!"

"Does Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable have Heavenly Court's lifespan extension method? According to Heavenly Court's method, not only a hundred thousand years, they can hibernate for millions of years."

"Sigh, how can we possibly try to understand the method of a venerable?"

Fang Yuan turned his gaze to Miao Ming Shen and said: "But for me to set up the supplementary formation, I need a Gu Immortal to suppress each formation core. When the supplementary formation is activated, the more Gu Immortals there are and the more formation cores there are, the greater the power of the supplementary formation will be. And in my plan, I need at least eight Gu Immortals to suppress the formation cores."

The good feelings of Miao Ming Shen and the rest faded away.

Including Fang Yuan, there were only five Gu Immortals here. Fang Yuan's words meant that they had to invite at least three more people.

That was an interesting situation.

Because with the addition of Zeng Luo Zi and Tu Tou Tuo, they still needed one person.

And other than Shen clan's Gu Immortals, there were only Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua left.

This was not acceptable to Miao Ming Shen's group. Shen clan had suppressed them, while Ren Xiu Ping was their enemy and Tong Hua was a traitor.

Who do they invite?

Gui Qi Ye, Hua Die, and Feng Jiang showed difficult expressions.

However, Miao Ming Shen smiled and responded sincerely: "Brother Chu, the most important thing right now is the Paradise Earth true inheritance, it is a rare opportunity, so we should seize it! This is such a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity! What hatred do we have that we can't put aside for a while? If we want to settle the score, we can do it after we leave. In my opinion, Zeng Luo Zi and Tu Tou Tuo can be invited, Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua can also be invited, and it will be even better if Shen clan's Gu Immortals can also come."

After saying that, Miao Ming Shen added an additional sentence: "Of course, everything is up to you, Brother Chu."

Gui Qi Ye and the other immortals' expressions changed, they wanted to say something but after Miao Ming Shen's statement, they could not say anything.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, Miao Ming Shen was truly Miao Ming Shen after all!

Fang Yuan said warmly: "Brother Miao is truly magnanimous, I am in deep admiration. Let's do that, I will set up a few supplementary formations first, the four of you will guard a formation core each and activate the formations to infiltrate the underwater formation. After that, I will invite the other Gu Immortals in."

Miao Ming Shen said again: "I am friends with Tu Tou Tuo and Zeng Luo Zi, I can write them a letter to make sure they know what decision to make."

Fang Yuan nodded: "That would be good."

Eventually, Fang Yuan obtained a few information path mortal Gu from Miao Ming Shen.

Miao Ming Shen not only wrote letters to Zeng Luo Zi and Tu Tou Tuo, he even wrote to Ren Xiu Ping, Tong Hua, and Shen clan, inviting them on behalf of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan took a few glances at the content, there were no issues. Miao Ming Shen expressed his intention to work together in the letter, he said that their grudges could be put aside for a while, he also praised Fang Yuan's methods and urged them to cooperate with him.

Fang Yuan could not help but reassess Miao Ming Shen.

The truth was, Miao Ming Shen's letter was only the icing on the cake, this letter was not going to change anything.

Fang Yuan had a lot of confidence in successfully recruiting these people to begin with.

Even if Miao Ming Shen objected, Fang Yuan would still invite the other Gu Immortals. Miao Ming Shen knew that he was not someone crucial to Fang Yuan, he could be replaced, in order to gain more benefits in the future, he relented. If this is not a talented person, who is?

The process of recruiting Tu Tou Tuo and Zeng Luo Zi went very smoothly.

Fang Yuan only said a sentence and they quickly joined him, they even showed deep excitement.

After all, Fang Yuan was bringing Miao Ming Shen's group to rise in ranking on the merit board, everyone could see how they suppressed Shen Cong Sheng.

Fang Yuan invited Tong Hua next, she hesitated and said she needed to think about it.

After that, Fang Yuan invited Ren Xiu Ping, he agreed to it without even thinking, he was even faster than Tu Tou Tuo and Zeng Luo Zi.

Ren Xiu Ping also brought slightly surprising news to Fang Yuan, Shen clan's Gu Immortals wanted to join as well.

Shen Cong Sheng was the leader of the Shen clan Gu Immortals, without his consent, none of them would dare to defect over to Fang Yuan.

Thus Fang Yuan met with Shen Cong Sheng soon after.

"Chu Ying." This time, Shen Cong Sheng had a warm attitude, he also treated the rank seven Chu Ying as a rank eight equal.

"The reason why I came here is because of Heavenly Court's information. Not long ago, Duke Long and Qi Sea Ancestor had a battle, I'm sure you have heard of it. In this battle, I captured Gu Yue Fang Zheng, in order to get him back, Heavenly Court gave me some important information."

"It turns out that this Dragon Whale Paradise has a rank eight response Immortal Gu, this Gu is extremely important to me and my Shen clan, I have been looking for it for many years."

"Shen clan is willing to cooperate with you, Chu Ying. If you see this Gu on the Merit Obelisk's reward list, I hope you can pass it. If you encounter this Gu in a mission, my Shen clan would like you to capture it for us. We will offer you a huge reward!"

Fang Yuan's expression changed: "Response Gu? This Gu worm is among the top ten of the List of Mystical Gu, it can emit a voice and anyone who hears this voice and responds to it will become enslaved. A rank eight response Gu can enslave rank eight Gu Immortals, this is such a precious Gu that your clan is unable to obtain, if you want to work with me, what rewards are you offering me? After all, within this Dragon Whale Paradise, we cannot set an agreement."

Shen Cong Sheng laughed loudly: "I have already prepared it. This cooperation will use the reputation of my Shen clan, you can record the entire process. Furthermore, I have something for you, this is a portion of our sincerity, please do accept it."

Saying so, Shen Cong Sheng took out a set of immortal materials and handed them to Fang Yuan.

The immortal materials had a lot of value, even Fang Yuan felt a little excited upon receiving them.

Regret Gu was right in front of him, he needed quite a bit of resources to advance all of his Immortal Gu, this set of immortal materials from Shen Cong Sheng had fixed this problem, it was something Fang Yuan really needed.

Fang Yuan nodded as he accepted the immortal materials.

Shen Cong Sheng added: "I hear that your current mission has a super immortal formation set by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable himself. I would like to go there, response Gu might be in it, even if it is not there, my Shen clan Gu Immortals can lend a hand to help you with this mission."

Fang Yuan pondered for a while before nodding: "It is my honor to receive the help of Lord Shen Cong Sheng."

Chapter 1904: Territory Gu

Within the regret crying sea area, immortals were present.

Miao Ming Shen and the other three each stayed in a supplementary formation, they activated their formations as the power continued to seep into the underwater formation.

Fang Yuan was setting up his immortal formation now.

His aura was radiating at rank seven level, his body was covered in a light green halo, his eyes were filled with blue light, resembling lightning in the sea.

Waving his hand, a large number of mortal Gu flew into the sky like a swarm of bees, circling around and forming the shape of a supplementary formation.

Next, Fang Yuan took out immortal materials and used his killer moves to fill up this supplementary formation.

The newly arrived Ren Xiu Ping and others looked at Fang Yuan with gleaming eyes, they were silent upon seeing his formation arrangement.

The Gu Immortals all had complex expressions, even Shen Cong Sheng was the same.

"Being able to use immortal materials to set up formations, he is a formation path grandmaster."

"Chu Ying cultivates transformation path, to think that he has such attainment in formation path, this is very rare. How does he dual cultivate?"

"Perhaps he found a way to cultivate both transformation path and formation path without conflict, like how Heavenly Court's Thunder Ghost True Monarch cultivated lightning path and soul path, or how Nine Spiritual Fairy cultivates transformation path and enslavement path."

"It is not as simple as just a formation path grandmaster, Chu Ying's proficiency in creating formations is very high, and most impressively, he does not lack formation path immortal killer moves, his efficiency at creating formations is truly amazing!"

The immortals watched with increasing shock as Fang Yuan displayed his incredible formation path attainment.

"With such methods, he can handle a lot of missions on the Merit Obelisk."

"Most of the Merit Obelisk missions involve channeling of rivers and managing the ecology, this is very advantageous for Chu Ying."

"No wonder he could complete so many formations!"

"Ordinary formation path Gu Immortals need Immortal Gu to create immortal formations. But Chu Ying is a formation path grandmaster, he only needs to use immortal materials. This is too terrifying."

The Gu Immortals could not help but feel envy and jealousy, especially towards Miao Ming Shen and group who had joined Chu Ying much earlier and had a head start.

Ren Xiu Ping was already starting to consider if he should abandon Shen clan after this mission and defect to Fang Yuan instead.

Looking at the current situation, Fang Yuan was very magnanimous, earlier, even though Ren Xiu Ping was enemies with him, he had completely ignored it at the moment.

Ren Xiu Ping's worry was that Fang Yuan already had Miao Ming Shen's group, even Tu Tou Tuo and Zeng Luo Zi had a closer relationship to Fang Yuan than him.

"In Chu Ying's perspective, he could simply cooperate with the people he liked. Why would he seek the cooperation of an enemy like me?"

Ren Xiu Ping had a thought: "Even though he had formation path grandmaster attainment level, being able to use immortal materials to set up formations, his greatest limitation is also immortal materials. If he lacks immortal materials, I can contribute them to him and deepen our cooperation and relationship."

Ren Xiu Ping decided to give up some of his personal benefits, that was the only way he could entice Fang Yuan into cooperating with him.

"This formation has been created, Ren Xiu Ping, please go and defend it." Fang Yuan spoke at this time.

He had already set up several formations, this was like the previous few ones, even though they were made in the sky, once they were completed, they would sink into the sea.

"Sure, sure." Ren Xiu Ping smiled as he flew down, he entered the formation without checking it closely.

Ren Xiu Ping did not have formation path attainment, even if Fang Yuan created the formation before his very eyes, he could not understanding the profundity of this supplementary formation, but he believed that with Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements, Fang Yuan could not harm him.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable restricted Gu Immortals from fighting each other, it allowed them to trust each other to a large extent.

Fang Yuan continued to set up formations.

One, two three...

One by one, Gu Immortals entered their formations, the supplementary formations were getting stronger.

Ren Xiu Ping's expression was not good now.

Fang Yuan seemed to have an endless supply of immortal materials!

During this period of time, he saw domination copper, earthly limit astral qi, green jade wind, dark inkstone, heaven flying jade...

Fang Yuan's deep wealth silenced all of the immortals.

Ren Xiu Ping even gasped in shock several times.

With such wealth, how could he possibly compare?

And the thing that made Ren Xiu Ping the most dejected was Fang Yuan's attitude.

He spent all of these immortal materials to create formations, he did not even blink or hesitate, he was completely indifferent about the cost!

Even though Fang Yuan lacked immortal materials, that was for the sake of advancing his Immortal Gu. The immortal materials used to create these formations were merely just a tiny portion of Fang Yuan's treasury, even if he had to create another hundred supplementary formations, he could easily afford it.

Thus, Fang Yuan's actions were simply showing that he was incredibly affluent in the eyes of Ren Xiu Ping and the other Gu Immortals!

After expending some time and effort, all the supplementary formations were finally created.

Shen Cong Sheng and the rest went into their own formations that were scattered all around the underwater formation, if one watched from above, it would resemble the tail of a peacock.

Every single supplementary formation resembled the feathers that formed the eye of a peacock tail, they gathered strength that flowed all the way into the underwater formation.

The supplementary formations looked similar but they all had different effects.

This was because Fang Yuan modified every supplementary formation according to the respective Gu Immortal using it, for example, Miao Ming Shen's supplementary formation had space path immortal materials, it could raise his efficiency. Ren Xiu Ping's supplementary formation had several spaces in it that could accommodate desolate beasts, it would allow him to use his enslavement path expertise.

Other than that, the supplementary formations also had specific locations. Fang Yuan placed the weaker immortals like Hua Die and Feng Jiang at the periphery. Shen Cong Sheng who was the strongest was closest to the underwater formation.

Fang Yuan also created a supplementary formation for himself.

He entered it.

This supplementary formation was a refinement path Gu formation, its only use was to amplify the power of Fang Yuan's refinement path killer moves.

Within the supplementary formation, Fang Yuan activated his killer move — Refinement Formation Rain!

At once, rain started to drizzle above the sea.

Countless raindrops entered the underwater formation, the might of refinement path was displayed as Gu worms were refined by Fang Yuan one by one.

Shen Cong Sheng and the others did not find this rain powerful initially, but after a while, their eyes were opened wide.

Because during this short period of time, Fang Yuan had already refined the outer layer of the underwater formation.

"What killer move is this? It worked against this underwater formation!"

"It looks like a refinement path killer move?" Some were uncertain.

"Such a powerful refinement path killer move... does Chu Ying cultivate refinement path too?" Some found it unbelievable.

"This should be the effect of that supplementary formation!"

The Gu Immortals thought about it for a long time, they subconsciously decided to attribute it to the power of Fang Yuan's supplementary formation.

If Chu Ying also had such terrifying attainment in refinement path, able to refine the formation of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, wouldn't he be a triple cultivator?

How would Ren Xiu Ping, Miao Ming Shen, and all these other elites who cultivated one path feel!

Even if it was the power of the supplementary formation, these Gu Immortals were still immensely shocked.

Shen Cong Sheng's pupils shrunk slightly, compared to the supplementary formation's power, he was more shocked at Fang Yuan's ambition.

He already understood it.

All of them controlling the supplementary formations were like crowbars while the underwater formation was like a tightly sealed wooden box.

The power of the supplementary formation invaded the underwater formation, it was like the crowbars trying to pry open the box.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan controlled the supplementary formation that was the core of this entire formation, it could flow in using the crack opened by the crowbars, to invade and turn these wooden boards into his own possession!

"Such formation path attainment, such ambition... he wants to take the entire formation for himself!"

"Chu Ying..." Shen Cong Sheng had a solemn expression, he secretly engraved this name into his heart.

This was not the first time Fang Yuan was using this refinement formation rain killer move.

This move used rank eight water refinement Immortal Gu as the core. Fang Yuan used many Gu worms to suppress the rank eight aura, disguising it as rank seven.

After rebirth, he annexed Lang Ya Sect and gained rank eight Immortal Gu Water Refinement, he created this move.

After returning to Southern Border, he used this killer move to refine Chi Qu You's formation and captured many Gu Immortals inside the formation.

This time, Fang Yuan used it with rank seven aura again, with the concealment of the supplementary formation, Shen Cong Sheng could not tell that it was truly rank eight.

The power of a rank eight killer move was truly extraordinary, the underwater formation was slowly refined by Fang Yuan bit by bit.

The more he refined it, the greater his control over the formation, with the help of his supplementary formations, he progressed with great speed without much problem.

However, after he refined thirty percent of the formation, refinement formation rain's effect fell drastically, his progress slowed down.

"Refinement formation rain is just a killer move, the actual effect depends on my understanding of this underwater formation." Fang Yuan expected this, he was not surprised, he was sufficiently patient.

He decided to spend some time here, to get regret Gu and the other Immortal Gu in the formation, his investments were worth it.

Originally, he was worried about the other Gu Immortals.

But now that Shen Cong Sheng had been invited here, Fang Yuan was not afraid that other Gu Immortals would use this time to surpass his contribution ranking.

The rate of formation refinement got slower and slower, eventually, Fang Yuan hit a brick.

This was an earth path rank seven Immortal Gu, its body was flat like a disk, yellowish brown, with a head and a tail, and four tentacles that look like hooks, growing evenly around the disk.

"This is territory Gu. Once a Gu Immortal plants it deep into the soil, it will emit a profound power that affects the surrounding soil and spreads out until it reaches its limit, everything that is within a thousand li of that territory will be controlled by the Gu Immortal." Fang Yuan recognized this Gu.

Territory Gu was very commonly seen.

Especially in Southern Border.

Many villages, even if they were not proficient in earth path, would try to get a rank three or four territory Gu. The village would plant this Gu in the soil and let a Gu Master in a position of authority use it, to raise and maintain their control over this territory.

Territory Gu was a very useful Gu worm but it was very expensive, it was often used by forces. Individual Gu Masters did not need it.

Territory Immortal Gu was actually kept within Dragon Whale Paradise, this Gu was quite useful to Fang Yuan as well.

Fang Yuan could conveniently use this Gu worm to manage his immortal aperture. He could alter the landscape of the territory that he creates using territory Gu.

Even if it was not useful, Fang Yuan still had to refine this earth path Immortal Gu. It was the key obstacle now, it stopped Fang Yuan from progressing further.

Chapter 1905: Demonic Immortal Breaks Free

"It is a little troublesome, I need to make deductions. Everyone, take a rest for now." Fang Yuan spoke.

The obstacle of territory Gu not only blocked Fang Yuan but also the other Gu Immortals. No matter how they activated the supplementary formation, they could not penetrate the formation anymore.

The Gu Immortals started to rest, but not without talking among themselves.

"We finally met with an obstacle."

"I thought that Chu Ying would be able to continue refining it endlessly."

"Don't joke, this is a formation that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable created personally, how in the world can this Chu Ying possibly refine such a formation?"

"But if he cannot refine it, what will happen to our mission?"

"Indeed, even though Chu Ying is a formation path grandmaster, deduction is the expertise of wisdom path. What can he deduce?"

The Gu Immortals had complex emotions.

On one hand, they could finally let out a sigh of relief after seeing Fang Yuan face an obstacle.

On the other hand, the fact that Fang Yuan was stuck meant that they were also not able to progress and gain more benefits.

The Gu Immortals wanted Fang Yuan to break through this obstacle but they were also inherently unwilling to see him succeed.

"Alright, I deduced it, let's continue." Fang Yuan said.

"What?" The immortals were stumped, his speed was too terrifying.

Fang Yuan flew out of the supplementary formation and floated in the air: "To get through this obstacle, we need to modify the supplementary formations a little, everyone, don't be anxious to take action."

Next, he willed as immortal essence got rapidly expended, supplementary formations followed his will and thought, changing locations. Some supplementary formations moved back while others moved in front, getting closer to the underwater formation.

Eventually, Miao Ming Shen's supplementary formation was closely placed beside Ren Xiu Ping's formation, they were tightly connected together.

Fang Yuan said to them: "Next, the two of you will lead the supplementary formations while the others help out."

Ren Xiu Ping and Miao Ming Shen nodded, they had complex expressions, not expecting that they of all people would actually cooperate.

After modifying the supplementary formations, Fang Yuan entered his supplementary formation again, he did not rush to activate refinement formation rain, instead he gave specific instructions to the immortals within these formations, using his own steps and methods to activate these supplementary formations in a particular manner.

The power of the supplementary formation changed, it was like a thin cluster of sand, falling through the cracks of the underwater formation and slowing down its operations bit by bit.

And this change was what Fang Yuan needed to make use of.

He quickly activated refinement formation rain and successfully refined territory Gu after a while!

After passing this obstacle, a new sense of ease was felt by the immortals as the supplementary formation's power surged like a wave and rampaged in the underwater formation. Only after it took over sixty percent of the formation did it stop at a new obstacle.

A huge wave of shock emerged in the hearts of Shen Cong Sheng and the rest.

"So powerful!"

"To think that this Chu Ying is so impressive."

"More than half of this underwater formation belongs to him now."

"The supplementary formations he designed are very profound, they can be adjusted according to situations. This is not a fixed formation, it is a transformative formation!"

Fang Yuan's performance surpassed their highest expectations, they could not help but feel deeply astonished.

Three days and two nights later, Fang Yuan refined a few more earth path Immortal Gu and a vast number of mortal Gu. At this point, the sixty percent of the formation was finally under Fang Yuan's control.

"But the remaining forty percent is the core of this underwater formation. With just the supplementary formations and myself, we cannot break through it in the short term." Fang Yuan knew his own limits. He had already reached the current limit of his abilities after reaching this point.

After all, this earth path formation was created by Paradise Earth, his earth path attainment level was supreme grandmaster!

Fang Yuan tried to use the sixty percent that he refined to interfere with the remaining forty percent.

Fang Yuan tried to use the underwater formation against itself.

Guh.

A moment later, Fang Yuan suddenly coughed out blood as his soul shook, his face turned pale. Many supplementary formations including the one he was in broke apart, the Gu Immortals within fell into the water as they shouted in shock, each of them faced varying levels of backlash.

Fang Yuan's plan failed, even though he controlled sixty percent of the formation, he could not do anything to the remaining core forty percent!

"As expected of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, even after over half of it was refined, it still remained unmoved." Fang Yuan's heart shook.

He sighed to himself as he called out: "Everyone, I am sorry, I did not see the profundity of the formation and caused you to get injured."

The injured Gu Immortals shook their head, they quickly replied that they were fine.

In their opinion, it was outstanding that Chu Ying could reach this stage, he far exceeded their expectations.

Fang Yuan squinted his eyes as he thought: "It seems that we can only dismantle the formation now."

After resting for a while, he started to dismantle the formation.

Because the external sixty percent was already refined by him, the dismantling was very successful.

But this was not a normal dismantling process, Fang Yuan only took apart sixty percent of the formation, thus during this process, Gu worms were destroyed when the formation was taken apart. But Fang Yuan paid attention to the Immortal Gu and protected them, he successfully obtained them. As for the mortal Gu, even if some of them were destroyed, it was not a big deal.

Miao Ming Shen, Ren Xiu Ping, and the rest watched with wide opened eyes!

When they controlled the supplementary formation earlier, they could not sense the exact situation within the formation, there was only a faint connection.

Now that Fang Yuan dismantled the formation, they could see all of the Gu worms that he was getting.

"So many Gu worms!"

"I see so many long-lost earth path mortal Gu, they were all created when Paradise Earth was still a Gu Master."

"There are also Immortal Gu, oh heavens, there are eight Immortal Gu!"

"Most of these Immortal Gu are rank seven, there are few rank six Immortal Gu!"

"Chu Ying took them all!"

"Indeed, he did not even give us a single one..."

The Gu Immortals watched as Fang Yuan took his Immortal Gu, they were staring in a daze, some of them were even salivating intensely.

Most of these were earth path Immortal Gu, they were not suitable for use but Immortal Gu were unique, they could be traded for other Immortal Gu!

Tu Tou Tuo's eyes were bloodshot, he was almost spewing fire from them!

He was an earth path Gu Immortal, watching as Fang Yuan kept the earth path Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture, he felt his mouth turning dry and his heart palpitating intensely.

While dismantling the formation, he gulped several times, he wanted to speak but could only swallow his saliva in the end.

He really wanted to snatch these Immortal Gu!

But his logic told him that it would be the most stupid move to do so.

Even a rank eight like Shen Cong Sheng could not do anything, how could he?

In the end, Tu Tou Tuo heaved a deep sigh, he swallowed all of his envy and jealousy into his stomach along with his saliva.

His mind moved quickly, thinking of how to get these Immortal Gu. He knew that he was not crucial to this plan, so the only way was to deepen his cooperation and relationship with Chu Ying by displaying his value, it would help in the future when he asks Chu Ying to exchange Gu.

The only good thing was that Chu Ying cultivated transformation path and formation path, he did not cultivate earth path. Thus, there was a high possibility that Chu Ying would sell these Immortal Gu in the future.

The pitiful Tu Tou Tuo did not know that Fang Yuan's earth path attainment level was at grandmaster, it was even higher than his!

After Fang Yuan dismantled the outer part of the formation, the immortals came to congratulate him.

"Congratulations, congratulations."

"Chu Ying, you've earned a fortune this time. Even though you used so many immortal materials, you gained a large number of Immortal Gu! It is truly a huge profit."

"To speak the truth, my saliva is about to drip to the ground."

"Outstanding methods, all I feel is admiration towards you."

"Chu Ying, I am Tu Tou Tuo, I am quite interested in these earth path Immortal Gu that you obtained. If you wish to sell or exchange them, please inform me, I am sure that you will be satisfied with my offer."

Fang Yuan thanked them one by one with calm emotions.

He simply had too many Immortal Gu already!

It could scare them all to death if he said the exact number.

And this batch of Immortal Gu that he just obtained was not his biggest gain recently.

Earlier in the River of Time, Fang Yuan defeated Heavenly Court, even though he lost the stone lotus island, his gains were huge.

He dismantled six Immortal Gu House from Heavenly Court, even though many Immortal Gu died in the battle, there were many Immortal Gu left.

For example, the core Immortal Gu of the river suppression lotus sealing formation, Suppression and Bone Seal; the two time path core of Moment Stage, Instant and That Time; Immortal Gu Permanence in Eternal Yacht; the Early Autumn, Mid Autumn, and Late Autumn of Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform; and the Immortal Gu in Sun and Moon Temple, Sun Day and Moon Month.

These Immortal Gu were mostly rank seven, some were rank eight!

As for Shark Flow Lever, even though it was completely destroyed without a single one left, it had a special construction style, it used a combination of desolate beasts and Immortal Gu. While Fang Yuan took his loot and gains from the battlefield, he reverse-deduced most of the contents of Shark Flow Lever using the clues he found. This gave him a huge inspiration, currently, Fang Yuan's clone was already making deductions to try to incorporate Twelve Zodiac battle formation into his Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Right now, there was only forty percent of the underwater formation left in front of Fang Yuan and the others.

Using refinement formation rain would have little to no effect already.

The power of the supplementary formation could no longer do anything.

Even though Fang Yuan tried very hard, there was no progress. He understood that this underwater formation was like a hard tortoise shell, its defense was very tight.

"Should I wait for my clone Wu Shuai to raise my earth path attainment level or should I attack directly?" Fang Yuan thought about it, he decided to save time and attack now.

After all, he had so many people with him now, he had to make good use of them.

Immediately, he asked these Gu Immortals to attack while he and a few other Gu Immortals stayed to manipulate the supplementary formation.

Boom boom boom!

All sorts of killer moves were unleashed upon the underwater formation, causing huge ripples and waves.

The formation only had forty percent left, after being attacked by so many strong immortals, including a rank eight Gu Immortal like Shen Cong Sheng, its operations were hindered as all sorts of flaws appeared.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed, he quickly used the supplementary formation to invade the formation using these loopholes.

"I regret it!" Suddenly, from within, a loud crying voice resounded in the area.

"What was I doing? I should not have attacked the formation."

"I regret it! Why did I listen to Chu Ying?"

"I should not have come to Dragon Whale Paradise, now I am completely trapped, I truly regret everything."

...

The immortals quickly stopped their actions, their morale fell to rock bottom as regret Gu exerted its influence on them.

Only Fang Yuan remained unmoved, bright light shined in his eyes as he thought: "The demonic immortal within the formation is spreading the power of regret Gu to weaken its influence on him. He wants to escape!"

Bam bam bam!

Loud sounds were emitted from within the underwater formation.

The formation had flaws to begin with, right now, these gaps spread as they formed into a huge crack.

Shen Cong Sheng shouted loudly as he temporarily suppressed the effect of regret Gu, his eyes were bloodshot as he attacked the formation's crack fiercely.

Immortal killer move — Grand Collision!

Boom!

The power of this move cooperated with the demon within, the formation broke apart as the sealed demonic immortal flew out like a black arrow.

Shen Cong Sheng was overjoyed, he flew closer: "Ancestor Shen Shang, I am a descendant of Shen clan, I am your junior!"

Chapter 1906: He Is Actually Fang Yuan!

The sudden change occurred in front of all the immortals.

Shen Cong Sheng got close to the mysterious demonic immortal, he showed an agitated expression.

"Finally, I've finally found you, Ancestor Shen Shang!" Shen Cong Sheng shouted in a slightly trembling voice.

His true motive in coming here was to save his ancestor, Shen Shang.

Shen Shang was the most outstanding Gu Immortal in Shen clan, he had outstanding talent that was publicly recognized. In fact, when he was still a rank six Gu Immortal, a wisdom path rank eight great expert had said that he was the 'hundreds of years eastern immortal leader, with half of a venerable's talent', it meant that he would become the leader of Eastern Sea's immortals in hundreds of years when he reaches rank eight, his talent was so high it could compare to half a venerable.

However, Shen Shang pursued strength and gradually fell into the demonic path, he started to commit heinous deeds.

His clan treasured his talent and even though they punished him, it was not a severe punishment, they protected him continuously.

Shen Shang did not change his ways, he became more daring and as a righteous path Gu Immortal on the surface, he acted like a demon.

Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world was kept in the dark, Shen clan managed to conceal the fact but they could not hide it from Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable took action, suppressing him, but did not expose his identity publicly.

Shen clan did not dare to publicize it, they only announced that Shen Shang had died from his tribulation.

After Shen Cong Sheng captured Gu Yue Fang Zheng, Heavenly Court contacted him and told him about Shen Shang's information, in exchange for Fang Zheng.

Therefore, Shen Cong Sheng learned that Shen Shang was still alive, and that he was imprisoned within Dragon Whale Paradise.

In order to enter Dragon Whale Paradise, Shen Cong Sheng mobilized the whole of Shen clan to investigate and search in secret.

Right at this time, Ren Xiu Ping targeted Miao Ming Shen and attacked them, exposing clues leading to the blue dragon whale.

After Shen clan learned of this, Shen Cong Sheng led them to force Ren Xiu Ping to submit, they learned that Miao Ming Shen had a way to find the exact location of the blue dragon whale.

Miao Ming Shen gathered eight immortals to search for the Paradise Earth true inheritance in the blue dragon whale, Ren Xiu Ping and Shen Cong Sheng learned about it and followed them.

After that, it led to a series of events.

After Shen Cong Sheng came to Dragon Whale Paradise, he tried all the ways possible to find Shen Shang's location, after a few missions, Shen clan Gu Immortal Shen Qi got the information of regret crying sea.

Shen Cong Sheng guessed that the demonic immortal in regret crying sea was likely Shen Shang!

However, he could not be happy for long because he heard of terrifying news.

Chu Ying actually accepted the mission to kill Shen Shang!

This shocked Shen Cong Sheng, he quickly contacted Fang Yuan, lying that he was looking for response Gu and offering a large amount of immortal materials to express his goodwill.

Thus, Fang Yuan brought Shen Cong Sheng into regret crying sea.

Shen Cong Sheng waited secretly and did not make a move, only at the last moment, he acted and saved Shen Shang with one attack.

This change made everyone dumbfounded other than the Shen clan Gu Immortals.

Immediately, Miao Ming Shen and the rest had dark expressions, their hearts sank to rock bottom.

Shen Cong Sheng was a rank eight Gu Immortal to begin with, they had another Shen Shang who was a rank eight Gu Immortal now as well. Back then, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had to suppress him personally, he definitely had outstanding battle strength that was not to be underestimated.

With Shen Shang, Shen clan's strength rose greatly. Not only in Dragon Whale Paradise, but even in Eastern Sea, there would be a shocking change.

Currently, in Eastern Sea's righteous path, Shen clan would be the only super force with two rank eight Gu Immortals!

Shen clan would become the strongest force in Eastern Sea.

This would have huge impact and bring immense benefits to Shen clan.

Back then, Heavenly Court exposed this secret to them, it was no wonder that Shen Cong Sheng immediately released Fang Zheng without caring about Qi Sea Ancestor, who was hinting that he wanted to get Fang Zheng.

"You are a descendant of my Shen clan?" Shen Shang floated in the air, looking at Shen Cong Sheng, his eyes shined with brilliance as he nodded: "Indeed, you are a member of Shen clan. What year is it now?"

Shen Shang had a hoarse voice, it was even more course than crows.

He wore a grey robe that was tattered, his face was pale and his hair was messy, his eyes were bloodshot and red. His peak rank eight aura radiated from his body with an intense force.

Shen Cong Sheng answered his question and told him that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had died long ago.

"So long has passed." Shen Shang sighed deeply: "Lord Paradise Earth died after all, sigh..."

His attitude towards Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was a bit strange.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable suppressed him but he actually called Paradise Earth 'Lord'.

After sighing, Shen Shang looked towards Fang Yuan and the other immortals.

He gazed around and understood the situation, he cupped his fists and smiled: "Good, it seems that my Shen clan has many talented people."

Afterwards, he focused his gaze on Fang Yuan as he spoke in a gentle tone: "Friend, I was able to escape thanks to you. It was mostly due to your effort, do you wish to join Shen clan and become our external supreme elder?"

He actually wanted to recruit Fang Yuan.

Indeed, Fang Yuan had displayed sufficient value already.

Just his formation path grandmaster status was something Shen clan wanted. And looking at his attainment and age, it was possible that he could break through to formation path great grandmaster in his lifetime.

Shen Cong Sheng cupped his fists towards Fang Yuan, adding: "Chu Ying, I lied earlier but I did not have a choice. Saving our Ancestor Shen Shang is extremely important to Shen clan, I hope you can understand."

Fang Yuan nodded with a plain expression, he even had a smile on his face: "Of course I understand, if it were me, I would do the same."

"But Shen clan wants to recruit me? Hehehe..." Fang Yuan laughed as he shook his head.

Shen Cong Sheng said coldly: "Friend Chu Ying, why are you laughing?"

Fang Yuan raised his eyebrows: "On what foundation is your Shen clan trying to recruit me? You guys are simply unqualified."

Shen Cong Sheng's gaze turned cold as ice.

His Shen clan was an Eastern Sea super force, they owned seven large sea areas and thousands of middle and small sea areas, they even had two rank eights now. With such strength, they were not qualified to recruit a tiny lone immortal?"

"Hmph, Chu Ying, don't be too arrogant."

"My Shen clan is giving you a chance, this is the magnanimity of our Ancestor Shen Shang."

"Don't think too highly of yourself!"

Shen Xiao and Shen Qi quickly spoke, they flew out of the supplementary formations, gathering with Shen Cong Sheng and Shen Shang.

Shen Shang's bloodshot eyes had deep killing intent, he looked at Fang Yuan and spoke with an icy voice: "Chu Ying? I need to remind you, you were all sent here by the Merit Obelisk, Paradise Earth's method restricts you from fighting each other. But I have been trapped here for countless years, I am not restricted by the Merit Obelisk, so all of you can be attacked by me."

The expressions of Miao Ming Shen and the rest changed, their worst nightmare had come true!

What should they do now?

Right when they were helpless, they suddenly heard Fang Yuan laughing loudly as he pointed his finger at Shen Shang who was in the sky, provoking him to attack.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest were dumbfounded.

Was this courage or stupidity?

They could not tell.

Shen Shang's eyes shined with blood red light as he lowered his voice that was filled with anger: "You are courting death, then go die!"

Saying so, he opened his mouth as a blood colored sound wave in a ball shape shot towards Fang Yuan.

The sound wave was very fast, in almost an instant, it flew through the sky and landed on the supplementary formation.

Boom!

The supplementary formation collapsed instantly, it did not even last for a moment.

An intense explosion occurred, a huge sea wave surged into the sky, it was tens of feet tall.

Before the wave landed, the explosion had already caused damage to the surroundings, Miao Ming Shen and the rest had to fly into the sky, away from their supplementary formations.

All of the supplementary formations were destroyed, Miao Ming Shen and the rest had ashen expressions.

Shen Shang's attack was definitely at rank eight level, it was terrifying! From their perspective, there was little chance that Chu Ying survived that.

The truth was, they did not care about Chu Ying's situation right now, they were more worried about themselves.

Because Shen Shang had proven his words from earlier with action, he could really attack Miao Ming Shen and the others!

"Ancestor is so powerful!" Shen Cong Sheng squinted, he knew the inside details. Shen Shang did not cultivate sound path primarily, the sound path method he used earlier was not his true strength.

"Chu Ying is dead meat!"

"Good that he died, I disliked him from the start."

"Indeed, he only had rank seven cultivation level but acted so arrogantly because he knew things about the Dragon Whale Paradise, he truly had no regard for us."

"He dared to provoke a rank eight, he truly wanted to die... die...."

Shen Xiao said as he suddenly stammered.

After the huge waves crashed down, new enormous waves were formed.

Within the steam and mist, a shiny ship that was covered in silver-white light appeared in front of all of the immortals.

Chu Ying's arms were behind his back, he stood at the deck as he carried the same smile as before.

Shen Shang saw this as his pupils shrunk, he gasped with shock: "Rank eight Immortal Gu House?"

The other Gu Immortals were all stunned!

They were so familiar with this Immortal Gu House, no, in the current five regions, which Gu Immortal did not know about this Immortal Gu House?

"This is... Myriad Year Flying Warship!" Ren Xiu Ping cried out, he felt his scalp going numb.

"Chu Ying actually has Myriad Year Flying Warship, who in the world is he?" Shen Xiao was tongue-tied.

The immortals stared at Fang Yuan with fixed gazes, he gradually dispelled familiar face as he showed his true appearance.

After seeing his true appearance, all of the immortals' hearts shook, none of them could stay indifferent.

Hua Die screamed out loud: "It's Fang Yuan!"

She was too shocked, she had always felt that Fang Yuan was high and mighty, far away from people like them, to think that he was around her the entire time.

It was truly unbelievable!

"It's Fang Yuan!!" Shen clan's Gu Immortals gritted their teeth, some were breathing and gasping loudly.

"So that was it." Miao Ming Shen gulped as he swallowed his saliva. Chu Ying was a fake identity of Fang Yuan, after all, how could such a powerful lone immortal appear in Eastern Sea suddenly?

It was Fang Yuan after all!

Who was Fang Yuan?

He had inherited many venerable inheritances, he was someone who could not be assessed with common sense.

No wonder Chu Ying had such attainment in transformation path and formation path. This was just a fragment of Fang Yuan's true strength.

Now everything made sense.

Shen Cong Sheng's expression was pale as he gritted his teeth, in just a short time, sweat had gathered on his forehead already.

So it was this great demon Fang Yuan!

No wonder he had such an attitude, even against two rank eights, he showed such disdain towards Shen clan.

It was normal!

Shen Cong Sheng suddenly felt that it was a logical situation, all of his anger towards Chu Ying's arrogance vanished completely without a trace!

Fang Yuan dared to provoke even Heavenly Court and kill their members, how could Shen clan even compare?

After his anger subsided, he felt intense fear afterwards.

He actually met with Fang Yuan, this was such a problematic person!

Shen Cong Sheng sighed in his heart, his luck was really bad, why did he meet Fang Yuan of all people?

At this moment, his rank eight strength could not give him confidence, he was panicking internally.

At this moment, Shen Cong Sheng heard Shen Shang's voice: "Who is Fang Yuan?"

Shen Cong Sheng looked at Shen Shang who had a confused expression.

He felt that this was very strange!

This Gu Immortal only had rank seven cultivation level, he had only changed his appearance.

Why were they all so afraid?

Shen Shang looked at Shen Cong Sheng with a gaze that had slight questioning, it seemed to be saying: You are a great rank eight, why are you afraid of a rank seven, what is there to fear!

Even though Fang Yuan showed his appearance, he did not reveal his rank eight aura, it was still concealed.

Shen Cong Sheng blinked as he shuddered internally.

Could he remain calm?

Could he look at Fang Yuan using common sense and cultivation level?

He was a ruthless demon who dared to trample on Heavenly Court, he destroyed six Immortal Gu Houses belonging to Heavenly Court earlier, he even slaughtered a bunch of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals!

He was ruthless and scheming, even Heavenly Court was without options against him.

Now that Shen clan offended him, forget about two rank eights, even if they had a group of rank eights, Shen Cong Sheng would not feel safe at all.

Chapter 1907: Human Path Quasi-supreme

At this point, Fang Yuan was no longer like before.

Heavenly Court was the reason for his overwhelming fame and dominance. Even though he only displayed rank seven cultivation level, it was enough to intimidate most rank eight Gu Immortals in the world.

"Ancestor." Shen Cong Sheng sent an information path mortal Gu to Shen Shang, it contained everything they knew about Fang Yuan.

Shen Shang received the mortal Gu as his divine sense swept through it, he looked towards Fang Yuan with a new type of gaze.

"Fang Yuan? Even Heavenly Court cannot do anything against you, hahaha, interesting!" Shen Shang's eyes burst out with blood red light, he laughed wildly: "To think that a person like you would appear in the world, this is wonderful, because now... I won't feel lonely."

Saying so, a strong aura burst out of his body, overwhelming the surroundings and dominating everyone's hearts.

Not only did Shen Shang not feel threatened by Fang Yuan's information, he even became extremely motivated to fight.

Looking at Shen Shang's action, Shen Cong Sheng felt a sense of confidence in his heart: "I'm likely not Fang Yuan's match, but with Ancestor Shen Shang here who is not an ordinary rank eight Gu Immortal, the outcome is still unknown!"

While he was thinking that, a silver light shot out and filled Shen Cong Sheng's vision.

"Damn it!" The alarms in Shen Cong Sheng's mind rang wildly, he quickly retreated.

At the next moment, Myriad Year Flying Warship flew over, drawing a beautiful arc of light in the air as it traveled.

If he reacted slower and stayed on the spot, Shen Cong Sheng would have been hit by Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Shen Cong Sheng did not dare to imagine the result of that collision.

This was the advantage of an Immortal Gu House.

Activating immortal killer moves took time, but using an Immortal Gu House to charge and rampage would instantly allow one to unleash an offensive method.

Myriad Year Flying Warship shot off again.

Fang Yuan mobilized Myriad Year Flying Warship and went after Shen Shang, ignoring Shen Cong Sheng completely.

Shen Shang did not dare to test Myriad Year Flying Warship with his bare body either, he was forced into being chased around by Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Shen Cong Sheng and the other Shen clan Gu Immortals wanted to help out but they were helpless when they found out that they could not attack Fang Yuan.

"Damn it!" Shen Cong Sheng gritted his teeth, in this situation, Shen clan's superiority in numbers could not be used, they could only watch as Fang Yuan fought against Shen Shang.

As for Miao Ming Shen and the rest, they did not dare to participate in such a battle, they were retreating already, hiding at a corner of the battlefield.

"Shen Shang, as an ancestor of Shen clan, all you can do is run around?" Fang Yuan mocked from within Myriad Year Flying Warship.

But even inside Myriad Year Flying Warship, he was still restricted by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's method. Fang Yuan had many subordinates in the sovereign immortal aperture but he could not let them out.

He could only control Myriad Year Flying Warship alone.

If he could let out his subordinates, his numbers would far surpass Shen clan.

"Hmph, arrogant junior!" Shen Shang was angered by Fang Yuan's words, he stopped in the air and used an immortal killer move.

Shen Shang's flying attainment was very high, he was able to fly rapidly, capable of catching up to Myriad Year Flying Warship.

In the process of escaping, he had been preparing his killer move, he finally unleashed it now.

Immortal killer move — Night Song!

The melancholic song quickly spread across the battlefield, and the sadness contained in it was like a tidal wave, constantly filling the hearts of the people.

The song had a slow tempo, it focused on the person's vocals, along with the sounds of drums and zithers, it was traditional yet sad.

Hua Die and Feng Jiang who were at the periphery were already crying.

Miao Ming Shen, Ren Xiu Ping, and the rest all had sad expressions, they could not help it.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, Myriad Year Flying Warship shined with radiance as it helped him to block the power of night song.

But Shen Shang had already achieved his goal.

He activated night song, not to directly deal with the Gu Immortals here, but to create a battlefield environment.

The song enveloped the sea and sky, a trace of twilight mist spread out from the sound waves, permeating the entire field, and after a few breaths, the entire regret crying sea turned pitch black.

The Gu Immortals were trapped in this dark area and could not see anything, all they could hear was the sorrowful night song, their morale and battle intent fell drastically. If this continued, they were going to be defenseless.

Even though Fang Yuan was barely affected, the surrounding darkness meant that he had lost sight of his target as well.

Fang Yuan immediately activated his investigative method, to try to find Shen Shang's location.

But Shen Shang sensed something as he laughed: "Fang Yuan, you fell for my trap."

Saying so, he activated a killer move — Sensory Injury.

Fang Yuan grunted immediately, he was directly hit by it.

He was shocked as he quickly realized: "This is a human path killer move! No wonder my Myriad Year Flying Warship could not guard against it."

Immortal Gu Houses had both offense and defense, they provided a huge assurance to the Gu Immortal and were very safe.

But this defense was not perfect.

When Fang Yuan designed Myriad Year Flying Warship, he considered most paths but human path was his weakness, he was not a human path grandmaster back then.

By the time he gained the attainment level, Myriad Year Flying Warship was already built, it could not be changed, he could only adjust it a little but there could not be major modifications.

And most importantly, Fang Yuan lacked defensive human path Immortal Gu.

"Shen Shang definitely has a high rank human path Immortal Gu!" After Fang Yuan was hit, he understood a bit of his enemy's foundation.

In terms of information, Fang Yuan was the one at the losing end.

He did not know much about Shen Shang, but Shen Shang knew a lot about him.

Fang Yuan had trump cards of course, like his rank eight cultivation level, five restriction profound light qi, and others, but he intended to keep these methods as a secret, he did not want to expose them now.

Within this Dragon Whale Paradise, Fang Yuan could not attack Shen Cong Sheng, Miao Ming Shen, and Ren Xiu Ping. If they brought this information out of Dragon Whale Paradise, it was easy for others to find out.

Thus, Fang Yuan decided to use the methods that he had already exposed before to fight.

Immortal killer move — Daybreak Sword!

Myriad Year Flying Warship's aura surged as a blinding white light shot out.

From the silver-white light bubbled the water of the River of Time, from which countless strands of silver light emerged.

The silver rays quickly condensed and took shape, transforming into many sharp sword-like blades that shot out violently.

The group of flying swords whistled past, pointing straight at Shen Shang.

Daybreak flying sword was a genuine rank eight killer move, its power was immense, but when Shen Shang saw the group of flying swords, he laughed loudly and did not dodge.

Silver-white flying swords landed on his body.

Shen Shang's body surged with a mysterious aura, he did not die but was covered in injuries.

But soon, all the injuries over his body disappeared and turned into dao marks.

"Incredible! The records in the clan are indeed correct, Ancestor Shen Shang was most proficient at healing." Shen Cong Sheng saw this scene and exclaimed in his mind.

When Shen Shang was still young, he was a healing physician. When he was a Gu Master, he began to travel Eastern Sea, and because of his powerful and unique healing methods, he soon became famous and well-known. He was also praised for his charitable acts, often helping the poor and needy without charging the slightest consultation fee, he received a warm welcome wherever he went.

Precisely because of his fame and reputation established in his youth, when he fell into the demonic path later and committed all sorts of demonic acts, Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals did not manage to link these crimes to him.

Within Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan squinted his eyes and felt something amiss: "This healing method is another human path killer move!"

Under normal circumstances, the injuries of Gu Immortals would have dense dao marks that were difficult to heal.

But Shen Shang possessed human path methods, he could heal himself with extreme efficiency and yielded quick results.

The group of flying swords continued to shoot out, many of them piercing through his body.

However, these wounds were completely healed almost instantly.

Immortal killer move — Mutual Injuries!

Shen Shang saw that the time was ripe and quickly unleashed the killer move that he had already prepared.

In Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan grunted as hundreds of wounds instantly formed on his body, wounds burst open and blood splattered everywhere.

The wounds were filled with human path dao marks, which then spread rapidly from the wounds, scattering everywhere while being connected as one.

Alarm bells rang in Fang Yuan's heart!

These human path dao marks were like a hanging rope around his neck, once the numbers increased, it would endanger Fang Yuan's life.

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan activated his wisdom path killer move first!

In an instant, the thoughts in his mind blossomed like fireworks, all sorts of thoughts collided, converged and fused into each other.

"Shen Shang's methods are bizarre, he was able to bypass Myriad Year Flying Warship to directly injure me!"

"Such a terrifying killer move... His human path attainment level is definitely more than a level above mine, I'm afraid he's a human path quasi-supreme grandmaster!"

"Any killer move needs to sense its target first, it can only take effect after it senses its target. How did he sense me?"

"I see. The previous night song killer move was just a trap to lure me into detecting him. He then followed this connection and found his way to me."

Everything in this world was interconnected.

When a fist hits a sand dune, a pit would appear on the sand, while the fist would also be covered in sand and mud.

Previously, Eastern Sea wisdom path Gu Immortal Hua An deduced Fang Yuan, but instead, Fang Yuan followed this connection and deduced Hua An's situation.

Not long ago, Heavenly Court Gu Immortals moved to blockade the stone lotus island with the river suppression lotus sealing formation, and it was with this layer of suppression and sealing that Fang Yuan was able to follow this connection and destroy the river suppression lotus sealing formation.

Now, Shen Shang did the same thing to sense Fang Yuan, it followed the same logic.

In just half a breath of time, Fang Yuan had already figured it out.

He immediately made his move, making Myriad Year Flying Warship retreat while scattering the daybreak flying swords, while he began to activate a healing killer move on himself.

His reaction was so swift that it left Shen Shang slightly stunned.

At the next moment, this demonic immortal, who was suppressed by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable himself, laughed with a hint of madness: "Fang Yuan! Do you think you'll be safe if you don't attack me? Hahaha, watch closely!"

As he said that, he activated a killer move again, his five fingers spread wide and his palm pressed against his chest.

Immortal killer move — Light Injuries!

Shen Shang grunted as he was hit by his own killer move, his expression turned pale.

Within Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan's body shook as he coughed out a huge mouthful of blood.

Chapter 1908: Black Fire

Non-conflicting dao marks!

The sovereign immortal body's greatest advantage was also its greatest weakness, at this moment, it was fully exposed.

All along, Fang Yuan had been consciously avoiding this flaw, but Shen Shang's killer move was too peculiar, it could not be guarded against.

Who could have thought that night song killer move was just a trap?

Shen Shang was chased by Myriad Year Flying Warship, it was a normal thing to use this killer move to conceal his own traces.

If Fang Yuan did not use an investigative method, Shen Shang would hide within the darkness, he would not be able to do anything.

The human path dao marks on Fang Yuan's injuries grew rapidly!

The light injuries on Shen Shang's body also affected Fang Yuan due to the killer move mutual injuries.

And in Fang Yuan's case, because of non-conflicting dao marks, his light injuries became heavy injuries.

But thankfully, all sorts of healing killer moves had their full effect when used on Fang Yuan as well.

Thus, as he used a powerful healing method on himself, Fang Yuan instantly recovered.

Immortal killer move — Heavy Injuries!

Shen Shang snickered as he started to hurt himself, with greater intensity than before.

Fang Yuan's body shook intensely, his vision turned dark as his seven orifices started to bleed.

"No! In terms of healing methods, I cannot compare to Shen Shang, I need to find another way." Fang Yuan understood as determination flashed in his eyes.

Immortal killer move — Heavy Injuries!

Immortal killer move — Heavy Injuries!

Immortal killer move — Heavy Injuries!

Shen Shang continued to injury himself as he turned crazy, he laughed loudly as blood spewed out of his mouth.

He heavily injured himself but rapidly healed as well, continuing the cycle.

This was such a strange fighting style, it made all the Gu Immortals dumbfounded.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest had nervous expressions, they were very worried.

Shen clan's Gu Immortals were very excited.

Even though they could not see Fang Yuan's condition, his flying swords had disintegrated while Myriad Year Flying Warship continued to back off.

"Ancestor Shen Shang actually forced back Fang Yuan! Impressive." Shen Cong Sheng was very excited, he could also see the rise of Shen clan.

Miao Ming Shen's eyes shined with bright light as he thought to himself: "Not good, even though Fang Yuan has Myriad Year Flying Warship, Shen Shang's offensive methods bypass this Immortal Gu House, it counters Fang Yuan. He is just a rank seven after all while Shen Shang is a genuine rank eight Gu Immortal."

Gui Qi Ye and Tu Tou Tuo were very confused: "This Shen Shang was suppressed by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable back then, it is not normal that he could live for so long."

"And the strange thing is, he does not lack Immortal Gu! When Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable suppressed him, didn't he take away or destroy his Immortal Gu first?"

"Ugh!" Right at this moment, Shen Shang's wild laughter came to an abrupt stop.

Surprise and confusion appeared on his face.

His connection to Fang Yuan was weakening rapidly.

How did Fang Yuan do it?

How could he break and get around this method so quickly?!

Immortal killer move — Self Cleansing!

Self cleansing could eliminate harmful dao marks on the user's body, Fang Yuan used this killer move to quickly get rid of the human path dao marks on his body.

The blood red light in Shen Shang's eyes flickered, he started to mutilate himself even more intensely, causing the human path dao marks on Fang Yuan's body to grow rapidly.

As long as a single human path dao mark remained on Fang Yuan's body, he could use this connection to attack Fang Yuan while bypassing Myriad Year Flying Warship.

But right now, Fang Yuan had already stabilized the situation.

Myriad Year Flying Warship gradually flew closer as Fang Yuan's voice resounded from within: "It is my turn now, Shen Shang."

Twelve Zodiac ancient battle formation!

Bam.

With a loud sound, the huge grey stone giant appeared again.

The giant moved extremely quickly, its two hands grabbed towards Shen Shang as they spread open.

Shen Shang squinted and snorted coldly, he quickly retreated, attempting to pull some distance from the giant.

Under Fang Yuan's manipulation, the grey stone giant only attempted to capture Shen Shang, it did not attack fiercely.

The grey stone giant had very powerful offensive methods, even though this was not the River of Time, it still had peak rank eight strength.

But he was currently using capture as the objective instead of hurting Shen Shang, Shen Shang had no choice but to dodge.

The battle went into a deadlock.

Shen Shang dodged the Twelve Zodiac battle formation while using killer moves to mutilate himself.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan manipulated Myriad Year Flying Warship as he healed himself, using self cleansing to get rid of harmful human path dao marks.

Myriad Year Flying Warship and the grey stone giant worked together, chasing after Shen Shang and obstructing him.

Shen Shang was already having some trouble dodging Myriad Year Flying Warship, with the addition of the grey stone giant, he fell into a disadvantage.

Every time he was about to get caught, Shen Shang would emit a loud scream that caused sound waves to burst out, opening a path for him.

Both sides continued to fight, rampaging in the battlefield, it implicated Miao Ming Shen's group, as well as the Shen clan immortals.

Hua Die and Feng Jiang were first to give up, they were transported away from the battlefield.

Followed by Tong Hua, Tu Tou Tuo, Gui Qi Ye and the rest.

After that were Shen clan's immortals, Miao Ming Shen, and Ren Xiu Ping.

Eventually, only Shen Cong Sheng was left in the battlefield, not everyone was qualified to watch a battle between rank eights after all.

Shen Cong Sheng's expression became increasingly dark.

The battle was tilting in Fang Yuan's favor, Shen Shang was getting into a difficult spot while Fang Yuan was having an easier time now.

"This lad has deep wisdom path attainment, he has countless thoughts in his mind, he can multitask easily. In this aspect, I am at the losing end." Shen Shang gritted his teeth, at this point in the battle, he felt like he had fallen into a swamp, the more he struggled, the deeper he sank.

The battle had already left his control!

Suddenly, Fang Yuan walked out of the cabin, arriving at the bow of the ship.

He pointed at Shen Shang as a time path killer move was unleashed.

Shen Shang was caught off guard, he could not dodge, after getting hit by this move, his movement slowed, the rate of time on him had been halved.

The grey stone giant used this chance to grab Shen Shang, it squeezed.

Shen Shang laughed loudly, his hair was messy and his eyes were bloodshot, he had no fear: "Go ahead and kill me!"

Fang Yuan snorted, he ordered the grey stone giant, it gripped to form a cage of ten fingers, imprisoning Shen Shang and preventing him from moving.

After understanding Shen Shang's offensive methods, Fang Yuan easily countered it. As long as he was captured and not killed, he could not do anything to harm Fang Yuan.

Shen Shang struggled, he screamed wildly but could not escape.

Shen Cong Sheng saw that the situation was bad, he wanted to help but was quickly faced with backlash, he could not get away from Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's restrictions.

"I finally succeeded." Fang Yuan let out a breath of air.

Shen Shang lived up to his reputation, this person who was suppressed by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable personally really had some skills.

His methods were peculiar and strange, they were hard to guard against, Fang Yuan had fallen for them earlier.

Of course, Fang Yuan still controlled the situation without wasting many of his hidden trump cards.

In the worst case, Fang Yuan could return to the starting island, with this assurance, he could not lose to begin with.

"Ahhhh...." Shen Shang shouted loudly, his face was distorted.

Fang Yuan's brows slowly started to furrow.

Shen Shang's current situation was quite strange, he constantly laughed and struggled madly without using any immortal killer moves.

At the next moment, his bloodshot eyes turned pitch black, the black color spread until it filled his eyes.

With a light sound, a lump of black fire started to burn on his body.

Within the fire, Shen Shang's body shook like he was having a spasm, he drooled uncontrollably as he waved his limbs around, he growled like a wild beast that was out of control.

The black fire on Shen Shang's body was not eye-catching, but once it spread to the grey stone giant's hands, the giant screamed in pain as it got burned by the fire.

After both hands got into contact with the black fire, they started to melt, completely defenseless against this strange black fire.

Fang Yuan's gaze turned colder, the peculiarity and strength of this black fire was far beyond his imagination.

Seeing that the situation was bad, Fang Yuan quickly deactivated the ancient battle formation.

At the next moment, the grey stone giant vanished while twelve immemorial year beasts appeared in the sky.

Among them, two immemorial year beasts contacted the black fire and lost their reasoning, they rolled around in the sky, growling in pain as they struggled intensely.

Thankfully, the other ten immemorial year beasts acted like this was their biggest threat, after regaining freedom, they quickly fled from the black fire as far as they could.

Fang Yuan and Shen Cong Sheng frowned deeply with solemn expressions.

This black fire was too strange, the two of them could not tell what path this black fire belonged to!

At the same time, they felt an extreme feeling of threat, their skulls felt numb as they sensed this danger.

The black fire was like the enemy of all lifeforms!

The two immemorial year beasts were already covered in the fire, they growled as they fell to the ground.

Fang Yuan had a strong premonition, if these two immemorial year beasts fell into the seawater, the black fire would cause an even greater tragedy.

But he did not do anything, he went into Myriad Year Flying Warship and retreated.

Shen Shang who had lost the restriction of the grey stone giant floated in the air and laughed wildly like a lunatic.

Shen Cong Sheng called him several times but it went unheard. Seeing this strange situation, Shen Cong Sheng also wisely chose to retreat.

Right when those two immemorial year beasts were about to enter the water, a golden-white pillar of light shot out from the underwater formation, pushing these two immemorial year beasts up into the sky.

The underwater formation that had only forty percent left burst out with unprecedented power as it operated at full force!

The golden-white light expanded as it covered Shen Shang as well.

The black fire continued to burn Shen Shang and the two immemorial year beasts but the white-gold light pillar immobilized them on the spot.

Such a change caused Shen Cong Sheng to be stunned.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan made his move, daybreak flying swords flew out and pierced the white-gold light pillar, stabbing into Shen Shang.

"Stop it!" Watching that his ancestor was attacked by Fang Yuan, Shen Cong Sheng shouted anxiously.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly as he activated his flying swords with even greater intensity.

This odd black fire was very harmful, seeing that the underwater formation had taken action to stop it from even entering the sea, it was obvious.

Shen Cong Sheng could only watch helplessly.

Fang Yuan willed again as his flying swords split into two groups, the other group went to attack his immemorial year beasts.

Due to the attack of the daybreak flying swords, the black fire still burned but it had weakened by a very slight amount.

Daybreak sword was a rank eight killer move, yet it nearly had no effect!

Fang Yuan continued to attack, but the black fire suddenly changed, transforming into lumps of silver-white mist.

Chapter 1909: Shen Cong Sheng's Immortal Materials

"This black fire can still transform?" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light, he shook his head immediately after, the silver-white mist still had a strange aura, it did not belong to any path .

The silver-white mist did not seem to be fundamentally different from the black fire, and while enveloped by it, Shen Shang was still going crazy, the two immemorial year beasts were also continuing to howl.

When Fang Yuan fired his daybreak flying swords again, he discovered that the power of the daybreak flying swords actually boosted the silver-white mist, causing the latter to increase in size.

Suspicious, Fang Yuan immediately changed his mind and went on a furious rampage with wind blades instead.

The silver-white mist was weakened again, but the rate of decline was still very small.

After the attack lasted for a while, the silver-white mist suddenly turned into three large whirlwinds, covering Shen Shang and the two immemorial year beasts.

Fang Yuan's wind blades shot into the whirlwind and began to boost the latter's power again.

Fang Yuan started to experiment and wisely began to swap his tactics.

Other Gu Immortals might have to stop but Fang Yuan cultivated all paths, he had an astonishing number of Immortal Gu at his disposal, he also had attainment level in many paths, he was even more skilled at transitioning to different paths.

Under Fang Yuan's attack, the strange black fire kept transforming and getting smaller and smaller.

The two immemorial year beasts were the first to die without their corpses left, Fang Yuan was soon left with only Shen Shang as his target.

"Wait, wait! Fang Yuan, I have a huge amount of wealth to gift to you." Shen Cong Sheng could no longer watch this continue, he called out loudly.

To his joy, Fang Yuan actually stopped.

Fang Yuan looked at Shen Cong Sheng and smiled: "Do you want me to let your clan's ancestor go? You should know that this is a demonic immortal, the very demonic immortal that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable suppressed personally in the past. You've seen his current state, crazy as a beast, delirious, and consistent with what is described on the Merit Obelisk. You still want to save him?"

Shen Cong Sheng looked deeply at the imprisoned Shen Shang in the pillar of light and made up his mind: "I believe this madness is only temporary. It would be too much of a coincidence if Ancestor Shen Shang happened to fall into permanent madness right when I was about to rescue him, right?"

"And what price can you pay for that?" Fang Yuan asked.

"How about you take a look at this?" Shen Cong Sheng pulled out an immortal material.

It was a bag.

The bag was not large and seemed to be the size of a grown man's fist. However, the surface of the bag was covered with a pattern that seemed like gems or blue swirls.

If one stared closely, one would notice that these sapphire-like swirls were constantly rotating.

But when one came back to one's senses, these lines were still lines, as if the scene had just been an illusion.

Fang Yuan, however, raised his eyebrows and lightly smiled: "So it's the treasure blue beaver's stomach pouch."

Treasure blue beaver was an immemorial desolate beast, often traveling between Eastern Sea and immemorial blue heaven. Now that immemorial blue heaven had shattered, the treasure blue beaver also went extinct. In history, the Gu Immortal who slaughtered the most treasure blue beavers was Old Immortal Kong Jue.

Old Immortal Kong Jue was one of the three supreme grandmasters of refinement path, comparable to Long Hair Ancestor. The treasure blue beaver that he went after and paid attention to was naturally extraordinary.

Not to mention, this stomach pouch alone was half an immortal aperture, it contained space path and water path dao marks, there was a whole small world inside of it, which could hide countless treasures. A Gu Immortal could obtain it and merge it into his or her immortal aperture, increasing the size of their grotto-heaven.

Because of this characteristic, the treasure blue beaver had been hunted down and killed extensively by Gu Immortals. It was no surprise that treasure blue beavers went extinct.

The stomach pouch of the treasure blue beaver could be said to be the most valuable thing in its body. And in today's world where treasure blue beavers were extinct, the value of this stomach pouch was even higher than normal!

In short, this was an extremely rare and highly valuable treasure.

Fang Yuan reached out his hand and directly took this stomach pouch from Shen Cong Sheng's hands.

The stomach pouch was light and the surface was very slippery.

Fang Yuan inspected it and found that nothing was tampered, so he put it into his immortal aperture in front of Shen Cong Sheng without any concern.

Next, he smiled: "Anything else?"

Shen Cong Sheng took a deep breath and pulled out a long black rod with much difficulty: "And this one too, catch it."

He gathered strength and threw the black rod at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stretched out his arm to catch it, the rod was very heavy, but he also had a lot of strength path dao marks on him, it was naturally easy.

Unlike Shen Cong Sheng who was a pure sound path Gu Immortal.

This black rod was taller than Fang Yuan, it had the thickness of a goose egg, the surface was also very rough, the weight was not light, as if it was a crude iron tool.

However, Fang Yuan could feel a dense aura of life from it.

This was an ancient desolate plant!

But it had no roots, no branches, nor leaves, there was only the trunk.

At the top of the trunk, there were countless star marks, some of them were five-edged, some two-edged, compactly arranged, all of them were emitting pale starlight.

"Falling star rod tree." Fang Yuan spoke.

Shen Cong Sheng nodded his head and exclaimed: "Fang Yuan, your extensive knowledge is to be admired."

The growth conditions of this tree were still a mystery as it had been extraordinarily rare and low in quantity since ancient times.

It had the unique trait of constantly attracting stars, falling into the trunk of the tree and turning into a single star mark. That was why it was called falling star.

According to rumors, one of the motives that Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had when he traveled the world alone was to collect this tree.

The value of the falling star rod tree did not just lie in itself.

By planting it in the immortal aperture, the Gu Immortal could use it to create an entire system of orbiting stars. It was a unique ecology that brought incremental gains every year, and the total amount of gains over time, day after day, year after year, was almost impossible to estimate.

Like the treasure blue beaver's stomach pouch, Fang Yuan placed the falling star rod tree into the immortal aperture once again, the natural demeanor that he had almost gave Shen Cong Sheng the illusion that this rare immemorial desolate plant belonged to Fang Yuan in the first place!

"What else?" Fang Yuan smiled: "These alone can't exchange for a rank eight great expert."

Shen Cong Sheng gritted his teeth and said: "I'm sure this immortal material will be able to satisfy you."

This time, he took out a lump of water.

The water was constrained in a ball, constantly creating waves. The waves were not just on the surface of the water, but even within the water, it was rising endlessly.

Although there were countless waves, they were uncluttered.

The water waves rose and fell in unison, advancing at one moment and retreating at the next, it could be called an orderly advance and retreat.

When Fang Yuan saw this, his eyes shined with bright light and he said: "Advancing and retreating tidal water."

Indeed, this was one of the three great waters of the world, advancing and retreating tidal water.

It was a rank nine immortal material!

This point alone made it far more valuable than the treasure blue beaver stomach pouch and the falling star rod tree combined.

Not to mention that it had many wonderful uses.

"I have a total of twelve portions of the advancing and retreating tidal water here, I can give them all to you." Shen Cong Sheng gave his offer.

Fang Yuan could not help but sigh lightly: "Shen clan is worthy of being a super force of Eastern Sea, you really have impressive assets."

Shen Cong Sheng smiled: "We are flattered."

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan said: "But that's not enough."

"It's not enough?" Shen Cong Sheng's pupils shrank as he showed an awkward expression.

Fang Yuan sneered and began to use his daybreak swords again, stabbing Shen Shang one sword at a time.

Shen Shang was still insane and kept on growling.

Shen Cong Sheng gnashed his teeth as he watched his ancestor being attacked: "My ancestor is insane now, he is not the same as an intact rank eight Gu Immortal. We both know that!"

"But as you said before, there should still be times when he doesn't go crazy, shouldn't there?" Fang Yuan was still sneering.

"Fang Yuan!" Shen Cong Sheng said in a low voice.

"What?" Fang Yuan raised his hand, a large number of daybreak flying swords shot towards Shen Shang.

Shen Cong Sheng almost gritted his teeth till they shattered: "Alright, what else do you want, Immortal Gu?"

"Of course I won't be that greedy." Fang Yuan shook his head and said with ease: "I want immortal materials, but not like the three that you gave me. They are all too highly ranked, I need a large number of rank six and seven immortal materials, the larger the variety and quantity, the better it will be."

"Shen clan is one of the super forces of Eastern Sea, you own seven large sea areas and thousands of middle and small sea areas, you'll even have two rank eight existences in the future. This little request should not be hard, right?"

"Of course... not." Shen Cong Sheng's expression was heavy: "But what will our Shen clan get? A crazy rank eight? He is a hidden threat himself. And it's a hidden threat that can even force the merciful Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable to personally take action to eliminate!"

Shen Cong Sheng was definitely a qualified leader.

When it came to the clan's interests, he was logical to the point of being almost emotionless.

Undeniably, Shen Shang's insanity had caused his value to plummet immensely. And the terrifying hidden danger he was carrying further reduced this value to almost a negative number.

Shen clan wanted as many rank eights as they could. But they did not want a crazy rank eight without any reasoning!

A rank eight without sanity was just a burden, unable to differentiate enemy and friend, they were a laughing stock for others, and would even bring calamity to Shen clan because of their reckless killing.

Shen Cong Sheng saw the hidden threat within Shen Shang and kept the worry in his heart. He also did not have the slightest confidence that he would be able to solve this problem.

Therefore, when he took out these three valuable resources in exchange for Shen Shang, he showed great sincerity.

Fang Yuan laughed and pointed his finger at Shen Shang: "He is your ancestor, the person you went to great lengths to save."

At this point, he paused: "Of course, this is by no means the only thing you will get. You'll also gain... my friendship."

"Oh?" Shen Cong Sheng showed a look of sudden interest: "How so?"

"In today's world, with the earth veins frequently shifting and the five regions fusing as one, it's bound to be a chaotic world. Although Shen clan is in Eastern Sea, it is by no means a paradise. Eastern Sea has the most resources and wealth that lure people's greed, even when the five regional walls exist, there is a steady stream of Gu Immortals coming here, what do you think will happen in the future?"

Fang Yuan spoke casually: "In this situation, what is the use of the differentiating righteous path and demonic path? If Shen clan and I join forces, it will be a strong partnership. Of course, we can keep this partnership hidden as much as we want. Your esteemed clan is extremely affluent, while I am free to do anything I want without burden."

"Central Continent is far more powerful than the other four regions, so if they attack Eastern Sea in the future, will Shen clan want to surrender or remain self-reliant? Even if you surrender, will all the super forces in Eastern Sea surrender? This is why, there is never a shortage of enemies, but allies like me are extremely rare to come across."

"The fact that you and I have met here is truly a great opportunity. If we continue to fight, it will only lead to a lose-lose situation. But if we help each other, it will be a win-win situation. Currently, we are dealing with the Paradise Earth true inheritance and Shen Shang, in the future, we will cooperate to deal with Central Continent and manipulate the entire state of the world!"

Chapter 1910: Everyone's Immortal Materials

Fang Yuan's words made Shen Cong Sheng go silent.

The sea breeze ruffled his clothes as he hovered in the air, deep in thought.

Fang Yuan stopped attacking with his daybreak swords and allowed him to ponder quietly.

The future of the five regions chaotic war had already been foreseen by all the major forces. Shen clan was a super force in Eastern Sea, but in such a chaotic situation, it was also like a rocky boat in a stormy sea.

Shen Cong Sheng was not stupid, other leaders of their respective forces also had great foresight, they were considering what direction they should take in the future when chaos ensues.

This was a big change, and if one was not careful, the tide of the great era would drown all those who did not plan well ahead of the storm!

This certainly included super forces.

Throughout history, even in relatively peaceful times, countless super forces had disappeared. Not to mention the great era when a venerable would appear, almost all of the existing order would be overturned, and in the midst of this, countless super forces would be destroyed and created, the situation of the five regions would become completely altered beyond recognition.

How should one attempt to live in such an era?

This was something that every Gu Immortal with foresight was wondering about.

Should they cooperate and join forces with Fang Yuan?

This was the question Shen Cong Sheng had to think about now.

In terms of qualifications, Fang Yuan was perfectly qualified to work with Shen clan, in fact, Shen Cong Sheng was still a little worried that Shen clan was the unqualified party. Because he himself was not a match for Fang Yuan.

But if he rescued Shen Shang and resolved the hidden threat in his body, along with Shen clan's Immortal Gu House... They would have the foundation to cooperate with Fang Yuan.

Shen Cong Sheng knew that Shen clan needed external allies like Fang Yuan.

It might be unlikely in times of peace, but in the future, when the five regions chaotic war starts, there would be a great chance that Shen clan would be in danger and at the point of extermination.

At this time... Fang Yuan would certainly be unreliable!

It would be a blessing if he did not gang up on Shen clan in the first place.

Shen Cong Sheng knew very well about Fang Yuan's demonic nature.

But what about the time when Shen clan needs to deal with an equivalent super force? For example, Xie clan, Cai clan, Hua clan, Tang clan, and even Song clan...

Shen clan was situated near the center of Eastern Sea, surrounded by many super forces, it was as if they were caught in a siege.

Without seeking a direction to break out and grow while they could, during the five regions chaotic war, they would end up as fodder for other powerful enemies.

Under such circumstances, if Shen clan could pay a large sum of resources in exchange for powerful help like Fang Yuan, why should they hesitate?

Fang Yuan possessed a rank eight Immortal Gu House, multiple venerable inheritances, and was able to repeatedly trample Heavenly Court underfoot. Such a powerful battle power was what Shen clan needed, it was something every super force desired.

If they did not cooperate with Fang Yuan now, what would they do if he worked with their enemies in the future?

In the current situation, Heavenly Court had to repair fate Gu, Fang Yuan wanted to deal with Heavenly Court, he needed a large amount of low ranked immortal materials, this was a great chance to cooperate with him!

Just like Fang Yuan said, this was a chance for both Shen clan and himself.

Both sides had their own needs.

Of course there were still many concerns, working with a demon like Fang Yuan was indeed very risky.

For example, if he goes back on his word in the future, he would still be free to do as he pleased, nobody including Heavenly Court could do anything about it, what could Shen clan possibly do with him?

Moreover, it is impossible to make an alliance agreement here, both sides lacked a basis for trust.

But in reality, even if there was an agreement, could they not break it themselves?

What if Fang Yuan goes back on his word in the future?

As long as they cooperated and achieved mutual benefits, why would Fang Yuan decide to turn on them?

Risk was definitely present, but how could anything in the world contain no risk?

Risk was secondary, profit was the main thing.

Shen Cong Sheng would not want anything that was high risk with low returns. But when the risk was great and the reward was also great, Shen Cong Sheng would never let it go!

The thing that Shen Cong Sheng appreciated the most was not Fang Yuan's battle strength, but his decision to share the mission with Miao Ming Shen, and even with himself.

From this, Shen Cong Sheng could tell that Fang Yuan was different from ordinary demonic path Gu Immortals! He was rational, he had the ability to think and act like the righteous path.

Pondering for a long time, Shen Cong Sheng nodded slowly with a solemn expression: "This is a chance, for both you and me. Hehehe, fine, why not take a gamble? In the future, if one remains stagnant, they will fall off. If Ancestor Shen Shang regains his senses, I will definitely try to persuade him to stop attacking you."

"These are all the low ranked immortal materials that I currently have, please accept them." Shen Cong Sheng displayed his sincerity once again.

Fang Yuan kept them all into his immortal aperture, he had stopped using daybreak sword, he slowly retreated: "Good! I'm going down to retrieve the underwater formation."

Retrieving the underwater formation was a lot of work for Fang Yuan, but in the end, he succeeded.

Fang Yuan stabbed and injured Shen Shang, although the white-gold pillar of light did not stop it, the daybreak swords still caused damage to the pillar, thus damaging the underwater formation.

The underwater formation was already only forty percent left, Shen Shang had broken out of it, which caused a huge opening, in Fang Yuan's eyes, it was full of cracks that he could target.

If he continued to fight, before Shen Shang dies, the underwater formation would probably collapse first.

Once it collapses, it was very likely to implicate the Immortal Gu inside. Fang Yuan could not control which Immortal Gu would be injured or destroyed, but if regret Gu gets destroyed, Fang Yuan's plans would be severely thwarted.

This was also one of the reasons why Fang Yuan and Shen Cong Sheng had joined forces.

The formation was taken away by Fang Yuan, the white-gold pillar that extended towards the sky dissipated, while Shen Shang regained his freedom.

"Ancestor." Shen Cong Sheng shouted while retreating.

Fang Yuan manipulated Myriad Year Flying Warship and cautiously retreated.

Shen Shang was still shrieking, fallen into a state of insanity, there was not the slightest sign of awakening.

"Shen Cong Sheng, do you need me to lend a hand?" Fang Yuan asked.

"No need." Shen Cong Sheng stared at Shen Cong Sheng, unable to figure out what state or condition he was in, there was nothing he could do: "We'd better wait until ancestor awakens on his own."

"Fine." Fang Yuan said as he controlled Myriad Year Flying Warship, moving further away.

Just at this moment, Shen Shang suddenly moved, his body was like an arrow, flying away.

"Ancestor!" Shen Cong Sheng cried out and chased after him.

Fang Yuan likewise maneuvered Myriad Year Flying Warship to chase after him.

But Shen Shang was extremely fast, Myriad Year Flying Warship was only a little bit faster.

Fang Yuan did not dare to use Myriad Year Flying Warship to directly stop Shen Shang. Because of this, Shen Shang managed to fly out of regret crying sea.

Shen Cong Sheng and Fang Yuan wanted to continue their pursuit, but they were stopped by an invisible barrier.

"Damn it!" Shen Cong Sheng's face was livid, he almost cursed out loud.

This was the method of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, which he had already experienced before, it prevented the foreign Gu Immortals from running around, so every mission had a certain limitation on where they could go.

This constraint did not take effect on Shen Shang, but it obstructed Fang Yuan and Shen Cong Sheng.

The two of them could only watch as Shen Shang flew away in a blur, eventually turning into a small black dot in the sky.

"It looks like he won't come back." Fang Yuan sighed.

Shen Cong Sheng looked stiff and watched for a long time before finally regaining his usual demeanor. He turned to Fang Yuan and forced a smile: "In that case, let's go back first."

Fang Yuan consoled, "Brother Shen, there is no need to be overly concerned, although your ancestor escaped, he cannot leave Dragon Whale Paradise. If he comes to his senses, he will definitely try to contact you by all means. If he is still insane, that would be even easier for us. The Merit Obelisk will not watch him endanger the environment and people, there will surely be more missions to come, just like this one, to kill your Ancestor Shen Shang."

Fang Yuan's words were reasonable, Shen Cong Sheng listened and nodded repeatedly, the look on his face eased a little.

Under the Merit Obelisk, the atmosphere was tense and heavy.

Two groups of people were distinctly separated.

One group consisted of Miao Ming Shen, Zeng Luo Zi, Tu Tou Tuo, and the rest.

The other group consisted of the Shen clan members, with Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua around.

"I wonder what's going on in regret crying sea..."

"Yeah, that is Fang Yuan after all. This demon has defeated Heavenly Court time and again, he is really scary."

"My clan has two rank eight Gu Immortals that can help out each other. Especially with Ancestor Shen Shang here, Fang Yuan isn't anything to fear."

"Don't forget, the reason why Fang Yuan was able to defeat Heavenly Court was because they were in the River of Time."

"But our first supreme elder is also restricted by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, so he can't fight Fang Yuan anyway."

"Sigh..."

The Shen clan Gu Immortals whispered, while Miao Ming Shen's group remained silent.

They were eager to teleport back and see how the battle progressed, but they were afraid that as soon as they teleported over, they would be affected by the horrific aftermath of the battle, and they might get caught up in it and die a terrible death.

No one was willing to take a foolish risk, so they were all here anxiously waiting for the results of the battle.

Two white lights flashed as Fang Yuan and Shen Cong Sheng appeared together.

"They're back!"

"Why don't we see Ancestor Shen Shang?"

"Fang Yuan is still alive, damn it!"

The immortals' thoughts were shaking as their expressions changed.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan, thanks to this information of yours, it will save me a lot of time and effort." Shen Cong Sheng exclaimed.

Fang Yuan smiled and waved his hand: "This is my sincerity. As I said, it will be a win-win situation if you and I cooperate."

The group of immortals were shocked again and became dumbfounded.

What the heck was this!

You two were just fighting each other earlier! Why were you suddenly on good terms?

What actually happened?

Where was Ancestor Shen Shang?

The Gu Immortals could not help but feel startled and amazed.

Shen Cong Sheng laughed: "I have reached an agreement with Fang Yuan to cooperate for now. Take out all the immortal materials you have on you."

"What?" The Shen clan Gu Immortals were dumbfounded.

Shen Cong Sheng nodded his head and emphasized: "This is the agreement we made, transfer all your rank six and seven immortal materials to him now."

"First supreme elder, this..." The immortals looked at each other.

Shen Cong Sheng showed a solemn expression and said in a deep voice: "This is an order!"

The Shen clan Gu Immortals were speechless.

What has happened?!

Oh great first supreme elder, what in the world are you thinking?

They were simply wondering if the first supreme elder in front of them had been controlled by Fang Yuan!

The Shen clan Gu Immortals dawdled before finally taking out their respective immortal materials and handed them over to Fang Yuan on the spot.

Fang Yuan smiled and received them one by one.

He knew that the Shen clan Gu Immortals would definitely not hand over all the immortal materials, but it did not matter, the materials that Fang Yuan needed for his refinement had been mostly obtained already.

After Shen clan's Gu Immortals had finished handing them over, Shen Cong Sheng looked at Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua.

"Us too?" Ren Xiu Ping could not believe it as his expression turned livid.

Shen Cong Sheng's gaze was cold as he nodded: "Shen clan will reward you for this."

Ren Xiu Ping almost cursed out loud.

Your Shen clan is cooperating with Fang Yuan, what does that have to do with me?!

I came to join your force but you treated me like this. This is just too...

Shen Cong Sheng saw Ren Xiu Ping's hesitation and smiled slightly: "Do you still not believe in me, even if you don't trust me, my Shen clan's credibility is not worth your trust?"

"Lord, please forgive me, of course I believe you. It was just that I could not react in time." Ren Xiu Ping laughed and endured the pain while transferring most of his immortal materials to Fang Yuan.

Tong Hua had an extremely ugly expression but she had no choice but to follow him.

Chapter 1911: Negative Merit Points

Seeing that Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua were not spared as they handed their immortal materials to Fang Yuan, Miao Ming Shen and the rest became worried.

If Fang Yuan extorted them too, what would they do?

Reject him?

That was likely impossible.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest could not stay in Dragon Whale Paradise forever, they needed to return to Eastern Sea.

Even though it was unreasonable for Fang Yuan to take immortal materials from them, it was basically extortion, but for the sake of their future, Miao Ming Shen and the rest still had to lower their heads.

In this world, strength was the major deciding factor, followed by logic.

Just as Miao Ming Shen and the rest prepared themselves mentally, Fang Yuan ignored them as he looked towards the Merit Obelisk.

Shen Cong Sheng had also seemingly forgotten about Miao Ming Shen's group.

Only Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua looked towards Miao Ming Shen's group, the former had deep hatred while the latter had a complex emotion.

Fang Yuan looked at the Merit Obelisk.

Undeniably, he had completely failed in this mission to exterminate the demonic immortal Shen Shang.

This mission had vanished on the Merit Obelisk, not only that, Fang Yuan even found that a lot of merit points got deducted.

The others were not spared, they had all lost their merit points too.

"First supreme elder, your merit points!" Shen clan's Gu Immortal shouted.

Shen Cong Sheng had an ashen and solemn expression.

He had lost the most merit points, even surpassing Fang Yuan's losses.

Even though Fang Yuan fell from his first place position, he still had single digit merit points. Meanwhile, Shen Cong Sheng had negative merit points!

This situation surprised Fang Yuan as well. After all, this did not happen in his previous life.

"Brother Shen, it seems that the Merit Obelisk punished you the most because you attacked the underwater formation and released Shen Shang. Meanwhile, I did not work properly and even took away the underwater formation, that's why I lost merit points as well." Fang Yuan analyzed.

Shen Cong Sheng's expression changed, he showed some anxiety: "I just received information from the Merit Obelisk, I need to get a positive amount of merit points in ten days. Otherwise, I will be kicked out of the Dragon Whale Paradise, I will not be allowed to enter again."

Fang Yuan had a thought, with his wisdom path attainment, he quickly analyzed the hidden information behind this.

"It seems that Dragon Whale Paradise can be explored repeatedly. We can still return? But how do we find it?"

The biggest problem was finding Dragon Whale Paradise's location in time.

Fang Yuan took a glance at Miao Ming Shen.

"Miao Ming Shen is able to sense the blue dragon whale and enter it, is this the qualification needed?"

Long ago, Fang Yuan had made some deductions.

Miao Ming Shen's ability to sense the blue dragon whale was very mysterious, Fang Yuan could not tell what it was.

With Fang Yuan's knowledge and attainment level in many paths, he could tell that even though Miao Ming Shen cultivated space path, the method he used was not.

This was very strange.

Precisely because it was too strange, Fang Yuan was wary and did not capture Miao Ming Shen to interrogate him about this method.

All sorts of clues pointed out that this method was not his own creation but originated from Dragon Whale Paradise itself, it came from the Merit Obelisk.

Shen Cong Sheng looked at his merit points, he frowned that the glaring number, he walked towards the Merit Obelisk: "Fang Yuan, I don't have much time, I can't talk anymore."

Fang Yuan nodded: "Go ahead, Brother Shen. If you need help, leave an information path Gu worm at the obelisk and I will definitely help."

Seeing the two being so friendly, the immortals behind them had weird expressions.

Shen Cong Sheng was a righteous path leader, while Fang Yuan was a publicly recognized demon in the five regions, was it okay for the two of them to have such a good relationship?

Shen Cong Sheng heard Fang Yuan's words and smiled at him.

He believed Fang Yuan's sincerity, but he believed that the price to get Fang Yuan's help would be extremely high.

Thus, if he could resolve the problem, he would rather do it himself.

Shen Cong Sheng quickly accepted a mid-sized mission and left.

In Shen Cong Sheng's case, this type of mission was the most efficient in earning merit points.

Fang Yuan was the second to walk to the Merit Obelisk.

He continued to choose a large sized mission.

"Hmm? A large sized mission to reclaim Immortal Gu..." At the next moment, he found a brand new mission on the Merit Obelisk.

This mission requested him to take back Immortal Gu, they were the ones that he took after dismantling the underwater formation.

Fang Yuan looked at the content of this mission closely.

This mission had a lot of details, it described the amount that each Immortal Gu was worth in points.

Fang Yuan counted the numbers, it was exactly what he had gained.

Next, he browsed through it, he found that this mission was basically created for him personally by the Merit Obelisk.

The truth was, earlier when Fang Yuan dismantled the formation, he had not checked through these Immortal Gu. Now with this mission, he could learn about their details without having to experiment personally.

From this, Fang Yuan learned that he gained three rank eight Immortal Gu, rank seven were in the highest quantity, and a good number of rank six Immortal Gu.

Each Immortal Gu had a huge resale value, even the lowest rank six Immortal Gu was worth ten thousand merit points.

The immortals behind him went into waves of gasps.

They also saw the mission on the Merit Obelisk.

At once, all of them had varying expressions, they were filled with envy and jealous that could not be concealed.

With this exchange rate, Fang Yuan only needed to contribute one rank six Immortal Gu to get at least ten thousand merit points. This was a huge amount, much more than what Fang Yuan had accumulated earlier!

It was absurd.

Earlier when manipulating the refinement path formation, they put in effort. After the battle started, they avoided the aftermath of their conflict and expended a lot of immortal essences while feeling great fear.

This mission to kill the demonic immortal failed, they did not gain anything.

But look at Fang Yuan!

He gained a huge number of Immortal Gu, if he exchanged them for merit points, the sum would be unthinkable.

Comparison created jealousy.

These immortals felt horrible, they were indignant and even angry but were not brave enough to act brazenly in front of the great demon Fang Yuan.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest were still fine, but Shen clan's Gu Immortals, Ren Xiu Ping, and Tong Hua felt even worse!

After all, the other party had only lost immortal essence.

But they had even lost most of their immortal materials.

This situation was too bizarre!

Not only were there no gains, they even had to expend their own resources, this was truly a terrible feeling.

Fang Yuan did not want to give up a single Immortal Gu.

Immortal Gu were unique, such opportunities seldom knock twice.

If he needed merit points, he could simply earn them, why would he give up on his precious Immortal Gu for such petty gains.

Most of these Immortal Gu were earth path, for ordinary Gu Immortals, they would definitely sell those that were not their own path, Immortal Gu required resources to feed after all.

But Fang Yuan was different.

He cultivated all paths, earth path suited him well. Furthermore, he recently gained a lot in earth path attainment level, he wondered, should he use these Immortal Gu to form a third Immortal Gu House?

Chapter 1912: Refining Immortal Gu

Earlier, Fang Yuan already had a grand plan to build three Immortal Gu Houses.

Right now, he had already created Myriad Year Flying Warship and Cooking Luck Pot, the final Immortal Gu House was not created yet.

Even though he obtained Divine Bean Palace and Dragon Palace during this period of time, these Immortal Gu Houses were used by his clones, they were necessary for his plans in the future, he could not use them personally to fight enemies.

And most importantly, Divine Bean Palace and Dragon Palace were not suited for his needs.

In Fang Yuan's plan, he needed an Immortal Gu House that focused on defense.

Myriad Year Flying Warship specialized in speed, it made up for Fang Yuan's weakness in movement, it was also crucial for fighting inside the River of Time.

Cooking Luck Pot was designed before Qin Ding Ling appeared, Fang Yuan planned to use it to suppress Heavenly Court's weaker luck, to expand his own advantage.

The final third Immortal Gu House was meant for defense and healing. During the battle of fate Gu, there would definitely be intense fights and little time for recovery. Fang Yuan needed a powerful defensive Immortal Gu House in the battlefield so that he could gain precious time to heal himself.

This Immortal Gu House had to be able to resist even venerable methods to an extent!

"Earth path is sturdy, it excels in defense to begin with. I will use these earth path Immortal Gu to create my third Immortal Gu House, that will be perfect." Fang Yuan thought about it and made up his mind.

Fang Yuan had no idea now that clone Wu Shuai already obtained a method to create an earth path Immortal Gu House from his dream realm exploration.

This Immortal Gu House was called Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, it suited his requirements.

However, Fang Yuan and his clones had shared attainment but not linked memories, they needed to communicate to gain each other's memories.

Eventually, Fang Yuan accepted a large sized mission to combine two sea areas.

"Who wants to come with me?" Fang Yuan did not rush, he turned around and asked.

The immortals looked at each other.

"Me." Miao Ming Shen was the first to react and step forward.

Behind him, Gui Qi Ye and the rest also followed.

"What about you?" Fang Yuan looked at the Shen clan Gu Immortals.

The Shen clan Gu Immortals were dumbfounded.

They had just turned on Fang Yuan earlier, they could not adjust their mindsets so quickly in this period of time.

Shen clan's Gu Immortals were not like Miao Ming Shen's group, the latter had experienced the benefits of working with Fang Yuan. In their first cooperation with Fang Yuan, it ended up as a failure.

Shen Xiao shook his head: "Thank you for the offer lord, we would like to look around first."

Shen Xiao rejected Fang Yuan politely, the other Shen clan Gu Immortal did not object to his statement.

Fang Yuan did not mind it, he smiled towards the last two people, asking: "Ren Xiu Ping? Tong Hua? What about you?"

Ren Xiu Ping had a grim expression, he did not speak, only shaking his head.

Tong Hua was currently startled and did not dare to say or do anything.

Fang Yuan expected them to act like this from the start. After all, he had just taken their immortal materials.

This showed Shen Cong Sheng's political ability as well.

Shen Cong Sheng ordered Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua to give their immortal materials to Fang Yuan, it seemed to have ruined their relationship, but the truth was, it made them helpless to do anything but stay with Shen clan.

In fact, they would even want to stay with Shen clan after leaving Dragon Whale Paradise to replenish their loss of immortal materials.

At the same time, this was a way for Shen Cong Sheng to suppress Tong Hua and Ren Xiu Ping. It made them realize who was calling the shots. Within Dragon Whale Paradise, they had to obey Shen clan, even after they leave, they still had to listen to Shen clan! After joining my Shen clan's boat, they still wanted to leave? Hehe, life was not that easy.

Fang Yuan knew Shen Cong Sheng's scheme, but he did not say anything.

With or without Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua, it did not matter, Fang Yuan's core benefits were untouched.

The five regional walls were still around, but the super forces were already starting to gather members and accumulate strength. Fang clan took in Old Ghost Bai Jun and Eagle Concubine, Shen clan took in Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua, was there anything weird? Longevity Heaven was even more overbearing, it united the entire Northern Plains Gu Immortal world, using the Huang Jin super forces to take in all of Northern Plains' lone and demonic immortals.

As for Central Continent, they achieved it long ago. The ten great ancient sects of Central Continent were subsidiaries of Heavenly Court, while most Gu Immortals or super forces were attached to the ten great ancient sects, controlled and kept under their watch.

Eventually, Fang Yuan brought Miao Ming Shen's group to the mission's location.

Floating in the sky, they looked down.

The Immortals saw these two sea areas, one blue and one green, with the blue sea towering high and the green sea hanging low. A large amount of seawater fell from the blue sea and rolled down into the green sea.

The seawater in both seas could not mix together, at the place where they met, the blue and green seawater touched each other, emitting a sneering sound, as a huge amount of clouds rose endlessly.

At the area where the two seas intersected, fish and insects were absent, this was almost a desolate place.

It was obvious that there was a major ecological problem.

Fang Yuan sighed: "It's not simple to combine the two sea areas, it is necessary to take into account all the different aspects. We might as well explore and gather information individually. After that, we will assemble and discuss a plan."

Miao Ming Shen nodded: "That is reasonable."

Fang Yuan looked at Miao Ming Shen and smiled at him.

Although his own identity was exposed, Miao Ming Shen still cooperated with him. He was able to swiftly change his attitude and continued to follow Fang Yuan's orders, this showed that he was something with great mental fortitude.

The immortals scattered and flew around the place, doing their investigations.

Fang Yuan was the only one who remained at the same place, using investigative methods while dividing his attention to look into the sovereign immortal aperture.

His greatest gain this time was regret Gu.

In his last life, he had followed the design of Regret Pool to use regret Gu as the core and create a refinement path Gu formation.

This life, however, did not need to be so troublesome. Fang Yuan had annexed the entire Lang Ya blessed land and possessed the extremely useful Long Hair refinement path formation, all he had to do now was to add regret Gu into this formation.

The formation certainly needed to be adjusted, Fang Yuan had already deduced it in advance.

At the moment, he only had to watch as regret Gu was placed in the vacant core position.

"Lord, Fang Yuan is a current generation demon, aren't we a little too close to him?" In the process of detection, Gui Qi Ye took the initiative to fly to the side of Miao Ming Shen, looking worried.

Miao Ming Shen patted Gui Qi Ye's shoulder: "Old Gui, you want to ask me why I treated Fang Yuan in this manner, almost acting like his subordinate, right?"

Gui Qi Ye smiled in embarrassment: "Lord, you are very perceptive."

Miao Ming Shen's face was slightly solemn and he sighed: "I am left with no other choice. This is my first time entering Dragon Whale Paradise but there was a mishap. Shen clan discovered this place, do you think they will let this precious land go and allow us to come and explore it again in the future?"

"According to the nature of super forces, they will want to keep it all to themselves!" Gui Qi Ye said with certainty.

"Precisely." Miao Ming Shen's eyes shined brightly: "We will definitely be suppressed and forced to surrender by Shen clan once we go out. If we do not surrender, we will be annihilated. But now we have a choice besides submitting to Shen clan."

"You refer to... Fang Yuan? I see, lord has great foresight, I am too foolish." Gui Qi Ye suddenly realized.

As lone immortals who knew such a precious place like the Dragon Whale Paradise, Shen clan would definitely take action against them in the future. Ren Xiu Ping alone was a strong enemy, not to mention the super force Shen clan.

Miao Ming Shen chose to be close to Fang Yuan in order to use his prestige as a shield and try to preserve the freedom of being a lone immortal.

When Shen clan decides to take action against them, they would have to take Fang Yuan's feelings into account.

In the worst case, he would give up his status as a lone immortal and become the subordinate of either Fang Yuan or Shen clan.

This meant that he still had some room for planning and was not at a dead end.

Unlike Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua who had joined Shen clan long ago. Without external pressure, the super force would naturally take advantage of them. Could they refuse to hand over the immortal materials when Shen Cong Sheng asked them to do so? Did they dare to refuse?

By the time the group of immortals reached Fang Yuan, he had already finished arranging regret Gu.

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, the hairy man Gu Immortals were ready, they were high in morale as they prepared themselves to refine a large number of Gu.

Fang Yuan's time path clone was organizing and planning the immortal material inventory, before fine-tuning and improving the Immortal Gu recipes according to the immortal materials at hand.

Fang Yuan needed to do it himself in his previous life, but with the whole of Lang Ya Sect helping him in this life, there was almost no need for him to intervene.

Thus, he saved a great deal of time.

With the fate battle getting closer and closer, this time was extremely valuable and precious!

Chapter 1913: Flame Cloud Pillar

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The Long Hair refinement path formation buzzed continuously, the fire within the formation raged towards the sky, heat waves were pushing everywhere.

A rank six Immortal Gu was bathed in fire and light, suspended in midair, its surface gradually melting like wax.

"Hold steady!" Lang Ya land spirit controlled the formation as he shouted: "Open the inventory, let out the immortal material."

The hairy man Gu Immortals controlling the other formation cores quickly opened the inventory doors.

Thus, lumps of dog shit flew out of it slowly.

These were all immortal materials.

Some flickered with starlight, seemingly embedded with blue diamonds, they were the faeces of star desolate hounds.

Some had sharp spikes and looked dangerous, they were the faeces of remnant heavenly dogs.

And there were pure and clean ones that resembled white jade, they were the excrement of the jade statue white hound.

Star desolate hound, remnant heavenly dog, and jade statue white hound were ancient desolate beasts.

The dog shit slowly flew into the fire, melting rapidly in the flames. Some turned into smoke, and some were reduced to liquid.

The formation activated as three hairy man Gu Immortals took action at once, cooperating to process these dog shit immortal materials.

First, smoke spread out to surround the rank six Immortal Gu, before liquid started to flow and gather.

Lang Ya land spirit took charge of the refinement, it was extremely stable during the late stage processes.

Right when they were about to succeed, when the final portion of immortal material fused into it, an accident occurred. The flame changed color as the incomplete rank seven Immortal Gu within broke apart rapidly.

Lang Ya land spirit was shocked, he quickly activated the formation.

The power of regret Gu activated as the color of the flame within the formation returned to normal, not only that, the incomplete rank seven Immortal Gu was also restored to its former state.

They only lost that last portion of immortal material.

The Lang Ya hairy men calmed their emotions and continued to refine Gu.

After less than an hour, the flames inside the formation gradually dissipated, and rank six Immortal Gu within was refined into rank seven.

Rank seven — Dog Shit Luck!

The hairy man Gu Immortals were very excited while Lang Ya land spirit was also filled with emotions.

Originally, they were proud of their refinement path ability. Now with the help of regret Gu, they were simply a dragon flying through the air, their advantage expanded out of control.

At the same time, in Dragon Whale Paradise.

Fang Yuan sat on the cloud with Feng Jiang and the rest, watching Miao Ming Shen fly around the place.

The ecology of the two sea areas had almost been adjusted completely. The final difficulty was that there was still a shattered space between the two seas.

Miao Ming Shen was trying to get rid of this space, by eliminating it, the two sea areas could finally fuse into one.

Miao Ming Shen was a space path Gu Immortal, he was specialized in dealing with these shattered spaces.

Fang Yuan and the rest were free to idle and watch.

"Oh? Immortal Gu Dog Shit Luck has been advanced successfully. Progress is smooth." Fang Yuan sensed the commotion within the sovereign immortal aperture.

While his main body was doing the merit missions, three Immortal Gu had already advanced inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Their progress was really fast!

When ordinary Gu Immortals refine Immortal Gu, they would take years to do so, they would be very nervous and careful with each attempt, the risks were huge.

But Fang Yuan's situation was different.

Lang Ya land spirit, the hairy man Gu Immortals, Long Hair refinement path formation, as well as the abundance of immortal materials, it allowed him to refine Gu with ease.

The three Immortal Gu that he had refined and advanced were from luck path, he had obtained them from dismantling Cooking Luck Pot.

Luck path was his focus now.

The dog shit luck Immortal Gu that he just advanced was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's former vital Gu, it had an incredibly powerful supplementary effect.

The only problem was that it was stuck at rank six and could not display its power. Now that it was rank seven, it could be used to some extent.

Fang Yuan had rank eight cultivation level now, his requirement for Immortal Gu also increased, he needed higher ranked Immortal Gu. Rank six was too low, while rank seven was barely good enough, rank eight suited him the most.

But if Fang Yuan wanted to refine a rank eight Immortal Gu, he would not be able to afford it. The investment needed was too high, and the risks were huge, he was likely to gain nothing.

After all, he could not ignore the outside world to cultivate, the external environment was very harsh, if he did not stop Heavenly Court from repairing fate Gu, his situation would deteriorate even further.

Currently, rank seven Immortal Gu were still barely usable to him.

Furthermore, these rank seven luck path Immortal Gu that he refined could be used to construct Cooking Luck Pot. At rank seven, Cooking Luck Pot would be able to affect rank eight.

"Hah!" Miao Ming Shen suddenly shouted, breaking Fang Yuan's chain of thoughts.

Miao Ming Shen flashed with a blue halo, it spread out around him and soothed the shattered space, uniting it until the cracks were restored entirely.

"Lord has amazing methods!" Feng Jiang and the rest praised.

At this point, the large sized mission was completed.

"Outstanding methods, yours are superior to mine." Fang Yuan did not stint on praise. He had space path Immortal Gu and space path methods too, he could even use other paths to mimic the effects of space path.

But compared to Miao Ming Shen, even if he could achieve the same effect, the cost would be higher.

After all, experts focused on their own fields, Miao Ming Shen was a space path cultivator, while Fang Yuan barely researched about space path, he made little progress in this path.

Miao Ming Shen quickly cupped his fists: "Lord is too kind, I am not worthy of such praise."

Fang Yuan replied with some praise again as everyone went back to the Merit Obelisk.

In this mission, Fang Yuan gained the most benefits, followed by Miao Ming Shen.

Fang Yuan's merit ranking rose to the top again.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest were no longer surprised. They had seen Fang Yuan's ranking jump up and down like a monkey. He was often in the first and last place.

Fang Yuan's gaze focused.

At this point, the other Gu Immortals were started to accumulate merit points. If Fang Yuan's ranking fell again, he would not be able to get to the first position so easily again.

They continued accepting and completing missions.

Fang Yuan's merit points soared continuously.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest followed after him the entire time, Fang Yuan used the advantage of cultivating all paths to resolve problems, while Miao Ming Shen and the rest resolved the minor issues for him.

This cooperation ensured that Fang Yuan remained at the top of the ranking, his status was getting more unmovable.

Miao Ming Shen and the rest also benefited, they started to break away from Shen clan's group, becoming the second group on the ranking list.

The first group was naturally Fang Yuan alone.

Shen Cong Sheng did not turn to Fang Yuan for help in the end, he got back on track by completing multiple mid-sized missions within the allotted time limit.

His luck was not bad, he received one or two sound path related missions. As for other missions, even though he cultivated sound path, he had many methods to mimic the effects of other paths.

Shen Cong Sheng was a rank eight after all, his cultivation level methods were beyond the rest.

By the time Shen Cong Sheng's ranking rose to the middle, Fang Yuan's Cooking Luck Pot was reassembled already.

Rank seven Cooking Luck Pot.

A top tier Immortal Gu House that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally created, it had the power to affect rank eight.

The first thing that Fang Yuan did was to inspect his own luck.

Boom!

As if he heard a roar that seemingly resounded in his ears, Fang Yuan looked up and saw a giant flame cloud pillar, burning brightly and rising up into the sky, as if it was trying to hold up heaven and earth.

His luck was like a giant pillar, flames that were bright-red like blood surged. On the surface of the giant pillar, the end of the many traces of the flame carried a touch of black color in it.

"My strength is rank eight, my battle strength rivals Duke Long, I also have countless Immortal Gu, Immortal Gu Houses, and killer moves, so my luck is grand and vast."

"Blood-red flame means slaughter. The black color at the ends of the flame means a deadly situation. The deadly black qi has corrupted the surface of the pillar, it is trying to get in, this means that my death threat is coming from an external source. It must be Heavenly Court."

"Heavenly Court has yet to repair fate Gu, once they succeed, the black death qi will definitely expand by several times, it will eventually corrupt my entire luck pillar."

Fang Yuan looked again, within the huge pillar, there were countless faint phantom images flickering continuously.

At times, he saw a red lotus, a white crane, a beast phantom, or a lump of soil...

Fang Yuan wanted to investigate deeper but he saw that his vision turned blur.

Immediately, his body shook and his throat felt wet, he almost spit out blood uncontrollably.

Fang Yuan rapidly healed himself and looked above him, he saw that Cooking Luck Pot was floating quietly, there was a vast amount of luck inside while a crack had formed on the surface of the pot, luck was leaking towards the outside.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly to himself internally.

His luck was too strong, even though this was rank seven Cooking Luck Pot, he could only barely see his luck.

After he looked at it for a long time, he would suffer backlash and Cooking Luck Pot would also be damaged.

The newly created Cooking Luck Pot needed to be fixed now. The crack was huge, the damage was severe, if left unattended, the crack would get larger and larger, he had to fix it immediately.

After checking his luck, Fang Yuan was both happy and worried.

He was happy that his luck was good, this was not strange, he had immense foundation, as well as methods in luck path.

The worry was that his hidden threat had started to appear, if he did not stop fate Gu from recovering, Fang Yuan's crisis would become more dangerous. And because the fire pillar was burning intensely, it also meant that he could not last too long.

These types of burning luck often meant that the Gu Immortal was unrivaled in a short period of time, but it could not last long. After the pillar stops burning, his luck would fall into a period of weakness.

But that was in the future.

Fang Yuan made some deductions, his luck would be maintained at this level at least until Central Continent's fate Gu battle, it could even be improved further.

Fang Yuan continued to receive missions, while the refinement path Gu Immortals within the sovereign immortal aperture also started to advance strength path Immortal Gu.

Missions to eliminate the black fire started to appear on the Merit Obelisk.

After Shen Shang escaped from regret crying sea, he was still in a state of madness, he unconsciously damaged the surroundings of the places he went to.

Fang Yuan was very interested in this odd black fire and immediately started to investigate it.

But he made no progress.

The black fire was very stubborn, even though it was a small lump, it could transform countless times when attacked, it could last for a long time.

As missions to clear the black fire appeared, Fang Yuan, Shen Cong Sheng, and the rest started to work together to complete them.

"Did you notice, this type of mission is getting rarer." On this day, Shen Cong Sheng talked to Fang Yuan while dealing with the black fire.

"Perhaps your Ancestor Shen Shang is about to regain his senses. With the location of these missions, we should be able to deduce his whereabouts." Fang Yuan analyzed.

"Indeed." Shen Cong Sheng had an expectant expression.

Right at this time, a rank eight Gu Immortal flew towards them in the sky.

Who else could it be but Shen Shang?

"Ancestor, this is great, you finally regained your senses. I have already negotiated with Fang Yuan, we will work together." Shen Cong Sheng was overjoyed, he quickly went over.

Shen Shang flew over and nodded towards Fang Yuan, he had a haggard expression, he frowned deeply as he said some shocking things: "The situation is quite troublesome, I have a huge problem. Before I resolve it, I need to be sealed again. Fang Yuan, you are proficient in formation path, I would like you to set up a formation to seal me if necessary."

Chapter 1914: Super Mission

In the eyes of super forces, there was no such thing as eternal friend or enemy in the world.

This is the way of survival of super forces.

If this was not followed, super forces would not last for a long time. Naturally, Shen clan was not such a force, as it had existed even before the era of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, and had grown and flourished during Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's time, surviving to this day!

As an old generation member of Shen Shang, Shen Shang was not opposed to Shen clan and Fang Yuan joining forces, he even felt joyful about it.

This was because none of the Shen clan members here were a formation path Gu Immortal. If Shen Shang wanted to use a formation to seal himself, he would naturally have to use Fang Yuan's method.

Hearing Shen Shang's words, Shen Cong Sheng had a weird expression. He had gone to great lengths to save his ancestor, but he did not expect that his ancestor would now instead ask to be sealed by a formation again.

However, the reason for this was completely understood by Shen Cong Sheng, he was now silent as he looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's face turned a little grim: "Shen Shang, although your clan has joined forces with me, the Immortal Gu from the underwater formation already belongs to me. Now you are asking me to use these Immortal Gu and create an immortal formation to seal you... This is quite hard for me to accept."

Shen Cong Sheng quickly added: "We can negotiate this Fang Yuan. We can even trade Immortal Gu."

At this point, seeing that Shen Shang had regained his senses, he did not want to give up.

Fang Yuan shook his head slowly, he had a serious expression: "Shen Cong Sheng, did you forget about the contents of our missions earlier? The mission states that we need to eliminate the demonic immortal within the formation, that is Shen Shang. What does that mean?"

Fang Yuan paused before continuing: "It means that the Merit Obelisk does not think that Shen Shang will recover, it has decided that his problem is too severe to treat. Even if I create the formation, it will not help him."

Shen Cong Sheng's expression changed, he wanted to speak but Shen Shang stopped him.

Shen Shang smiled towards Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, no need to have such concerns. I am not asking you to contribute your Immortal Gu, the Gu worms we will use for the formation are all mine. Look."

Saying so, he took out an Immortal Gu from his immortal aperture.

The Immortal Gu was like a silkworm, pale yellow in color, curled up in a ball and not stretched, making it even more exquisite.

"Shen Cong Sheng may have already explained my situation to you." Shen Shang said to Fang Yuan: "I'm most proficient in healing, and this is the human path Immortal Gu I created back then — Heal Injury. Using this as the core, I later developed a human path killer move called 'saving dead healing injuries', if the difficulty isn't too high, I can even revive a dead person on the spot!"

Fang Yuan looked at the Gu worm in front of him, he felt a little amazed.

This was a pure human path Immortal Gu, the shocking thing was that this was a genuine rank eight Immortal Gu.

Rank eight human path Immortal Gu!

Seeing that the immortals were silent, Shen Shang smiled and said again: "Have you found that human path methods are the most effective in dealing with the black fire?"

Shen Cong Sheng shook his head: "Not yet, but we know that healing killer moves will take effect if we use them on the black fire. But whether we use offensive or healing killer moves on the black fire, there is no difference."

Shen Shang nodded: "Watch."

Saying so, a wave of aura burst out of his body.

Watching him prepare a killer move, the surrounding Gu Immortals quickly retreated with deep alertness.

After Shen Shang regained his senses, he had no intention of harming anyone, he slowly stretched out his hand, aiming at the black fire in the distance.

His palm suddenly burst out with a stream of bright yellow light.

The light stream surged and spiraled forward, it was not fast, but eventually shot into the black fire.

The black fire only endured the yellow light for a moment before quickly dissipating.

Shen Shang stopped his killer move and said to the group of immortals: "As you have just seen, this is my killer move, saving dead healing injuries."

"It's true that human path killer moves are quite effective against the black fire." Seeing the truth, Fang Yuan immediately nodded his head, acknowledging Shen Shang's statement.

"They are indeed." Shen Cong Sheng rejoiced: "The previous underwater formation was an earth path immortal formation, it was difficult to resolve the problem on ancestor. But if you use our ancestor's human path Immortal Gu, there will be greater hope."

Fang Yuan, however, did not agree just yet, he gazed at Shen Shang: "You are a human path quasi-supreme grandmaster?"

Astonishment flashed in Shen Shang's eyes as he nodded: "That is correct. I didn't expect that you are also proficient in human path."

Different professions were different worlds, this was the same for paths.

Since Fang Yuan could estimate Shen Shang's human path attainment level, it meant that he also had some level of attainment in it.

All of the immortals turned their gazes towards Fang Yuan while feeling surprised, they sighed to themselves: This great demon renowned in the world was truly unfathomable!

Fang Yuan asked: "Do you have the formation chart?"

Shen Shang showed a helpless smile: "I have a formation chart but it is incomplete, I seem to have created it myself, but I can't remember the entire thing."

"What do you mean?" Shen Cong Sheng tensed up.

Shen Shang sighed deeply: "I've lost my memory. Every time I fall into madness, a part of the memories I grasp will disappear. This is why I need to solve the problem in me as soon as possible, if it's too late, I'm afraid I won't even know who I am anymore."

Fang Yuan smiled and said: "Shen Shang, you're lucky to have met me."

Shen Shang nodded his head and agreed: "This is indeed my good luck. It is very difficult to set up human path formation that meets my requirements, there are many conditions to do so. Firstly, you need the human path Immortal Gu, secondly, you need to deduce and modify the formation chart, and finally, you need to set up the formation. Setting up the formation requires formation path attainment, deducing and modifying the formation chart requires wisdom path attainment, and because it is a human path immortal formation, it also requires human path attainment."

"Any other Gu Immortal who specializes in formation path, even with rank eight cultivation, would not be able to satisfy my requirements. But you, Fang Yuan, meet all three of these conditions. So now, I really have to rely on you. Please do help me out!"

"Fang Yuan, whatever reward you need, feel free to ask, my Shen clan will definitely do our best to satisfy you." Shen Cong Sheng made a solemn commitment.

Fang Yuan nodded, as soon as Shen Shang said his request to set up the immortal formation, he realized that this was a good opportunity.

Not only would he be able to obtain a generous amount of immortal materials from Shen clan by just setting up the formation.

What he cared more about was Shen clan, Shen Cong Sheng, and Shen Shang.

By cooperating with Shen clan, he could influence the Eastern Sea Gu Immortal world even more deeply and affect the situation of the entire world.

Although Fang Yuan's human path attainment level was already grandmaster, he still had no clue on how to deal with those human path killer moves of Heavenly Court. It would be a completely different story if Shen Shang were to deal with them.

Heavenly Court was too powerful and had countless years of accumulation. Fang Yuan was not able to resist them alone, he needed the help of others to work together and fight against this giant.

Fang Yuan pondered for a moment and said his conditions.

To the surprise of Shen Shang and Shen Cong Sheng, the conditions Fang Yuan proposed were very relaxed and not harsh at all. Fang Yuan did not have much demand for immortal materials, nor did he ask for Immortal Gu.

The only condition that had to be fulfilled was the requirement that Shen Cong Sheng and Shen Shang must take action and become the enemy of Heavenly Court to stop it from repairing fate Gu.

But in fact, there was no need for Fang Yuan to bring it up, it was already the consensus of all the super forces in the world that they had to prevent the successful restoration of fate Gu!

Many of the ambitious people in the world were even more worried about fate Gu than Fang Yuan! After all, none of them were otherworldly demons, once Heavenly Court succeeds in their plan, their status and position would be unshakable.

A few days later, a brand new formation was built at the bottom of the sea.

Shen Shang entered the formation, with the main formation core controlled by Shen Cong Sheng and assisted by Fang Yuan.

The formation was slowly activated as a stream of profound white light formed chains that tied Shen Shang like a mummy.

Shen Shang was silent, sitting in a cross-legged position, soon his entire body was enveloped in a layer of pale white light mist.

A moment later, the formation came to a halt.

Fang Yuan, Shen Cong Sheng and the others found nothing, they could not detect a single bit of black fire within Shen Shang's body at all.

Shen Shang sighed: "I have searched countless times before, the only time this black fire will appear is when I go mad again."

Fang Yuan's eyes shimmered uncertainly: "Are you sure that you can't remember all the things about the black fire?"

Shen Shang just shook his head.

Shen Cong Sheng sighed: "In that case, we will have to wait. This mission will be placed here for now, I will send a person specifically to stay behind to guard the formation."

This arrangement was very reasonable.

The Gu Immortals were restricted in their range of movement in Dragon Whale Paradise and could not travel in and out of places as they wished. Using the Merit Obelisk's teleportation ability, as well as the group title, they were able to communicate instantly, and if Shen Shang went mad, they would quickly gather together.

Those arranged within the formation were bound to be Shen clan's members, sometimes it was even Shen Cong Sheng himself who went to stay guard.

With this burden, Shen clan was not Fang Yuan's match at all in the competition for the merit board ranking.

Time continued to pass day by day, Fang Yuan's merit points rose from thousands to tens of thousands, and then from tens of thousands to even higher.

In the process, he also exchanged for titles from time to time. It was just that the secrets behind many titles were not clear to him either. In the previous life, Miao Ming Shen's group had not explored it to this extent yet, so Fang Yuan could only guess and make deductions.

Fortunately, even if his deductions were wrong, the exchanged titles were all of some use.

Having so many merit points, Fang Yuan did not exchange for any Immortal Gu.

He did not lack any Immortal Gu, what he lacked were some rare immortal materials.

There were instances where Fang Yuan spent his merit points to exchange for immortal materials from the Merit Obelisk that would help the hairy man Gu Immortals' refinement.

Fang Yuan had a large amount of immortal materials, but there were still some missing among the rarer ones. The Merit Obelisk made up for the last gap in resources.

By the time Fang Yuan made a new breakthrough, the first super mission appeared.

"Get rid of the black fire on the heavenly spine?" Fang Yuan was slightly startled: "Why is there still black fire that hasn't been eliminated?"

Some time before, missions regarding the black fire had appeared one after another. The immortals completed these missions to clean up Shen Shang's mess.

"Could it be that this isn't left behind by Shen Shang?" There was a sudden flash of realization in Fang Yuan's mind.

It was very simple to verify this conjecture, with the aid of the Merit Obelisk, Fang Yuan directly teleported to the mission location.

At the next moment, he was at the top of the clouds, the highest point in the sky.

There was no wind and the sun was warm.

"This is?" Fang Yuan's pupils shrank as he looked up to see countless lumps of black fire burning silently.

The scale of the black fire was extremely large, as if this was a field of dark clouds in a rainstorm!

The total amount of black fire that Fang Yuan and the immortals had previously gone to great lengths to annihilate was a minute fraction of the black fire in front of him now.

"The scale of this black fire is appalling, it cannot have come from Shen Shang. In that case, there was already a hidden black fire problem in Dragon Whale Paradise from the start!"

Chapter 1915: Shen Shang's Inheritance

The black fire was not burning in the air, it was attached to giant bones.

The giant bones were milky white and had a sacred aura.

The giant bones had a main trunk that extended from east to west, it could pierce through heaven and earth, it was like a dragon of the nine heavens that stretched beyond Fang Yuan's vision. On both sides of the bone, there were countless neatly arranged branching giant bones that extended outwards, as if they were giant ivory tusks.

The entire skeleton was like the spine and ribs of a giant, singlehandedly holding up the sky!

"Heavenly spine..." Fang Yuan murmured, the sight before him was imposing, he was underneath the giant bones, being as small as a mosquito.

These bones were like gnarled trees, and the black fire gathered like clouds, covering most of the bones.

After evaluating it, Fang Yuan figured out a few details: "This heavenly spine is actually a rank nine bone path immortal material!"

That alone was incredible.

The heavenly spine should not be a human bone, which Gu Immortal had such a massive body?

Since it was not a human bone, it was a beast bone.

But how could there be such a fierce beast that could reach the level of rank nine?

It was impossible!

Rank nine was the level of a venerable, historically, they only appeared in the human race. Throughout history, there were only ten of them, while the rest of the races had rank eight existences at most, there were also immemorial desolate beasts or immemorial desolate plants as well.

Was it possible that there were rank nine desolate beasts or plants in this world?

Only such an existence would leave behind such a grade of immortal material after death.

"Other than that, is it something that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable created personally?" Fang Yuan was filled with questions.

This was very unlikely.

Because Fang Yuan had already seen through the function of the heavenly spine, its one and only use was to reinforce this Dragon Whale Paradise.

If Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable wanted to reinforce this paradise, he could have used earth path methods, or even sound path methods. These were his expertise, why would he bother to choose bone path?

"Also, why did Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable set it up like this, to specifically reinforce Dragon Whale Paradise? It's as if Dragon Whale Paradise is very unsafe and could collapse at any moment."

"But the truth is, the blue dragon whale is a legendary immemorial desolate beast, its strength is near the pinnacle of the world. There are simply very few existences that can threaten it. If something can threaten its life, would there be a point in reinforcing Dragon Whale Paradise?"

"The biggest question is, why is there such a huge black fire on the back of the heavenly spine?"

This was clearly not caused by Shen Shang.

If Shen Shang was able to leak black fire of this scale, how could he still come back alive and volunteer to seal himself?

"What kind of connection is there between the black fire here and the black fire on Shen Shang's body?" Fang Yuan kept deducing, and in the process, he saw a branching rib completely melt away in the black fire.

The black fire was fiercely corroding and constantly destroying the heavenly spine!

What would happen if the heavenly spine is completely destroyed?

Fang Yuan did not know, but it was definitely not something good.

He tried his hand as he manipulated Myriad Year Flying Warship, activating daybreak flying sword to attack the black fire.

As he expected, the black fire was like a sea, his attack was like throwing stones into the sea, unable to create any difference.

Fang Yuan tried for a while, but he had no choice but to stop. Even a character like him felt overwhelmed at the moment.

This was the difficulty of a super mission.

After pondering for a bit, Fang Yuan left the place, returned to the starting island, he went over to the underwater formation.

Shen Shang was still conscious, Fang Yuan informed him of the situation at the heavenly spine.

"Do you have any impressions of this place?" Fang Yuan inquired.

Shen Shang shook his head in distress: "No recollection of that at all. But it definitely has a connection with my black fire. If I can figure out the mystery of the black fire, I might be able to gain insight on the plan of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable back then, as well as the deepest secrets of Dragon Whale Paradise!"

At this point, Shen Shang paused: "I want to see it for myself, is that okay?"

"Of course." Fang Yuan responded immediately. Since he had told Shen Shang about this situation, he was not going to hide it.

To attempt to complete a super mission, relying on him alone seemed insufficient, he would have to gather the strength of all the Gu Immortals.

Soon, the group of immortals gathered together as one and arrived at the heavenly spine.

Seeing the sea of black fire clouds that filled the sky, the group of immortals had a change of expression as they marveled at it.

The group of immortals tried to exterminate the black fire, but the progress was extremely slight. It seemed that the larger the black fire was, the more difficult it was to eradicate it.

Among the immortals, only Shen Shang's human path methods were sufficiently effective, the others were all outmatched by him.

After the plan to remove the black fire had lasted for several days, Hua Die was the first to give up.

It was not that she could not take it mentally, but the immortal essence expenditure was too high.

"This mission is too hard, I suggest we give up." Miao Ming Shen secretly approached Fang Yuan and discussed with him in private.

Even without him having to say anything, Fang Yuan had already wanted to give up.

By now, the immortals had done their best but only managed to eliminate a small area of the black fire. And such a scale was not even one-thousandth of the entire black fire.

"If I were to truly utilize my rank eight battle strength, this would certainly be much more efficient, but the result would still be too poor. Instead, I might as well complete large sized missions one after another, after a few times, I'll be able to accumulate a large amount of merit points."

"I'm afraid only a venerable will be able to handle a super mission like this with ease."

Fang Yuan decided to give up.

Shen Cong Sheng and Shen Shang expressed their understanding.

But they were unwilling to give up, they only let the other Shen clan Gu Immortals follow him.

Shen Shang said to Fang Yuan: "I still want to explore it further, I will move along the main spine and see if I can find any clue or answer."

Fang Yuan looked at him deeply, nodding and leaving directly.

Soon, only Shen Shang and Shen Cong Sheng were left here at the heavenly spine.

"Take a walk with me." Shen Shang sighed.

Shen Cong Sheng followed and took the initiative to ask: "Ancestor, you purposely diverted everyone away, did you recall something?"

Shen Shang shook his head: "I am planning to hand over my human path inheritance to you."

Shen Cong Sheng was startled, he had an ominous feeling from Shen Shang's tone as he quickly said: "Ancestor, you need not be in such a hurry. I believe that there will always be a way to resolve the problem in you."

Shen Shang smiled slightly: "I have not given up hope, but I have to make considerations for our clan. Leaving behind my human path inheritance for the benefit of our clan, it can be considered as me repaying the debt I once owed the clan!"

Shen Cong Sheng was silent.

Shen Shang continued: "At the underwater formation, I was not able to pass you my inheritance, after all, it was a formation set up by Fang Yuan himself. But here, it should be safe."

"I won't pass my human path Immortal Gu to you, because I still need to use them. What I'm passing on to you is my experience in cultivation, and the various killer moves and Immortal Gu recipes I've created."

Shen Cong Sheng said solemnly: "I will definitely not fail to live up to ancestor's good intentions."

Shen Shang smiled bitterly: "My memory is fragmented, what I remember is limited. Let's start from the very beginning, I used to major in sound path, but then in an accident, I refined heal injury Immortal Gu, from which I saw that hope of human path."

"In order to convert to human path, I did many things in secret, all of which were against the rules of the righteous path. Our clan defended me and helped to cover up these incidents, but in the end, I couldn't hide it from Lord Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable."

"When Lord Paradise Earth found me, I was no match for him, I couldn't even take a single blow from him. But Lord Paradise Earth didn't kill me, nor did he imprison me, but instead, because I had spent many years saving lives and helping the injured, he gave me a chance to redeem myself. And he promised me that if I could seize this opportunity, I might even be able to achieve my goal and successfully convert to cultivating human path."

"And so I came here, I cultivated bitterly in the underwater formation that Lord Paradise Earth had set up."

"The memories of my non-stop cultivation are completely blurred, I only remember that in the process, I received the help of the undersea formation and repeatedly broke through, progressing steadily."

"With heal injury Immortal Gu as the foundation, I developed and created saving dead healing injuries, light injuries, heavy injuries, fatal injuries, sensory injuries, seven laborious injuries, and other killer moves."

"Finally, one day, I created the killer move countless injury marks. From this killer move, I deduced the Immortal Gu recipe of injury mark Immortal Gu."

"I refined it and replaced my own vital Gu. With this Immortal Gu, any attacks that cause damage to me will be converted into the respective injury marks."

"The more injury marks I have, the more I can increase the power of mutual injuries killer move. In the battle earlier, Fang Yuan was forced to retreat by me because I used the killer move mutual injuries to cause him to be covered in injury marks."

"Remember that injury mark Immortal Gu is the core of my human path inheritance, while mutual injuries is my main offensive method."

Shen Cong Sheng's heart shook as he listened, the true inheritance of human path created by Shen Shang was so profound that it shook him physically and mentally!

"Ancestor, this true inheritance that you started has great future prospects, perhaps it might be able to create an entirely new sub-path branching from human path." Shen Cong Sheng praised heartily.

"Hahaha." Shen Shang laughed proudly as he patted Shen Cong Sheng's shoulder: "I'm afraid that I won't be able to. The inheritance is left to you, if you are interested in the future, you can switch to human path. If you have no intention of doing so, just choose a suitable successor."

Southern Border.

Virtue Paradise.

A female immortal dressed in a purple silk robe, ornate and mysterious, came down the mountain step by step.

Her skin was white as snow and her black hair hung down to her waist, her eyes were like the deep pool, with a sense of sadness shrouding her face. It was Heavenly Court's leader, the person who had Star Constellation Chessboard, the number one wisdom path great expert in the current world — Fairy Zi Wei!

At the moment, however, Fairy Zi Wei was covered in a thin layer of sweat and looked haggard, but her eyes were shining and her spirit was high.

At the foot of the mountain, Lu Wei Yin had been waiting for a long time: "Lady Zi Wei, it seems you've reached your goal in this journey."

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "This climb has benefited me a lot. I have already obtained benevolence Gu, thank you for your generosity."

Lu Wei Yin also smiled: "Lady Zi Wei, it is not to help you, this is for the sake of the world, to maintain the peace of the five regions."

"But alas, in the current world, demonic immortals are rising. Not to mention Fang Yuan, recently in Western Desert, a blood path rank eight great expert has actually appeared, purposely finding trouble with super forces and repeatedly attacking various resource points. They are acting extremely arrogantly, and the methods are extraordinarily terrifying. The chaos is coming, I only hope that this Virtue Paradise will become an actual paradise safe from the chaos of the world."

Fairy Zi Wei sighed: "I understand what you mean. In the future, there will be generous rewards for you after the changes in the five regions. Farewell."

"Goodbye." Lu Wei Yin moved aside and gave way to her departure.

Chapter 1916: Ultimate Mission

Dragon Whale Paradise.

At the Merit Obelisk, Fang Yuan and Shen Cong Sheng stood as they looked at the merit board together.

The super mission regarding the black fire was still around, but tomorrow was the final day of the three hundred days they could stay here.

Fang Yuan's merit points stood at the top of the board, he had a huge amount. After he found out about the difficulty of the black fire mission, he chose only large and mid-sized missions to earn his merit points.

Miao Ming Shen and others worked alongside him and gained an abundant amount of points as well.

After realizing the difficulty of the super mission, Shen Cong Sheng and others wisely learned from Fang Yuan, now their merit points had also accumulated to a considerable amount.

"Three hundred days have passed by, it feels like we just arrived here yesterday." Shen Cong Sheng smiled bitterly.

This was a genuine land of treasures, by completing various missions, the Gu Immortals would be able to directly obtain Immortal Gu, Immortal Gu recipes, and various killer moves. Even a rank eight Gu Immortal like Shen Cong Sheng was attracted to this place and did not want to leave.

But there was no way, once the time limit was up, they would be kicked out of Dragon Whale Paradise.

"It's a pity that this time, we did not explore all the secrets of Dragon Whale Paradise." Fang Yuan sighed with pity.

There were many more strange things about this Dragon Whale Paradise.

The black fire was one of them.

Where did this black fire come from? How could it transform to so many different forms? Why could its path not be discerned? And why were human path methods so effective against it?

Apart from the black fire, where did the heavenly spine left behind by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable originate? What was the true intent of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable?

What agreement did Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable and Shen Shang make back then? Shen Shang cultivated human path in the underwater formation, yet he was somehow tainted by the troublesome black fire.

Also, apart from Shen Shang alone, Fang Yuan did not see any other Gu Immortals. Were there no Gu Immortals in Dragon Whale Paradise in the first place? And where did the Immortal Gu in the Merit Obelisk come from? If they were all naturally produced, the number was simply too large.

After a moment of silence, Shen Cong Sheng said: "We'll have to leave these secrets for the future when we can explore them again. It's good that we have all exchanged for that title already, so once the blue dragon whale appears in the future, we will be able to sense it and explore it again."

Fang Yuan nodded his head, this was indeed a good discovery.

Just as he had deduced before, the reason why Miao Ming Shen was able to discover the exact location of the blue dragon whale was because of a title.

But it was unknown who had taken this title and quietly transferred it to him.

Of all the titles provided by the Merit Obelisk, there were very few types of titles that could be transferred.

There was also another discovery about titles.

After getting a certain title, the Gu Immortal could teleport to any location within a hundred thousand li radius when they leave Dragon Whale Paradise.

This was something that Fang Yuan had lied to Miao Ming Shen's group before, but it existed in reality.

Right at this time, the words on the Merit Obelisk transformed suddenly.

Be they small sized missions, mid-sized missions, or large sized missions, even super missions were gone, only one ultimate mission was left.

Ultimate mission — Leave with the blue dragon whale and successfully return.

"This is?" Shen Cong Sheng gasped.

Fang Yuan frowned: "This means that above super missions, there are ultimate missions? This description is so vague, I'm afraid it is much harder than getting rid of the black fire!"

At this time, there was a new transformation on the Merit Obelisk.

Shen Cong Sheng stared with wide eyes as he read it: "The mission does not have a time limit, after receiving it, one can stay in the paradise indefinitely. After completing the ultimate mission, one will obtain the qualifications to become the Merit Obelisk Lord and retain their merit points."

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light, he thought to himself: "So Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable made his arrangements already to choose the Merit Obelisk Lord. According to his arrangements, I will be able to become the owner of this rank eight Immortal Gu House. It is a pity, a real pity."

Fang Yuan felt some regret.

He had already uncovered a correct method to obtain the Merit Obelisk, but his strength was limited. He could not even complete the super mission, let alone the ultimate mission.

The ultimate mission was obviously extremely difficult, even a rank eight Gu Immortal would have little hope.

This was easy to deduce.

The Gu Immortals that had come to Dragon Whale Paradise were far more than just Fang Yuan's group. When the previous groups of people came here, some might have chosen to accept this ultimate mission, but the Merit Obelisk was still in an unowned state.

This meant that no one had ever succeeded!

There was another reason why Fang Yuan did not intend to accept the mission.

It was written on the Merit Obelisk that the time limit for this mission was indefinite.

If it took too long and he waited until he completed the mission before leaving, only to find that Heavenly Court had already completely repaired fate Gu, then what was the point of all this?

"Sigh..." Shen Cong Sheng let out a breath of air, he also regained his logic, recognizing the risks involved, he was no longer dreaming about it.

Fang Yuan stretched out his arm and pointed at the mission on the Merit Obelisk, analyzing it: "Brother Shen, this ultimate mission has given us some extra information. After choosing this mission, the Gu Immortal's personal merit points will be preserved. This means that those who haven't accepted it will have all of their remaining merit points cleared as soon as they leave Dragon Whale Paradise."

Shen Cong Sheng nodded repeatedly, his heart clenched: "I'm afraid that's it. When we first came here, the merit ranking list was empty."

As such, the Gu Immortals would have to spend as much of their accumulated merit points as possible.

But exactly how they would spend it would require some consideration on the part of the Gu Immortals themselves.

The next day.

Somewhere in Eastern Sea, three white lights flashed, the three Immortals Fang Yuan, Shen Cong Sheng, and Shen Shang appeared.

All the Gu Immortals gave up on the ultimate mission and chose to leave.

However, Miao Ming Shen's group did not leave with Fang Yuan, they still had reservations towards him.

Ren Xiu Ping and Tong Hua, on the other hand, left along with the rest of Shen clan's Gu Immortals. After this, these two Eastern Sea lone immortals were considered to be completely on board and tied to Shen clan's ship.

Fang Yuan turned around and looked back, only to see the sky was empty, the sea was calm, there was nothing behind him.

He did not want to give up on this, so he, along with Shen Cong Sheng and Shen Shang, kept scouting the surroundings, but found nothing after all.

"The three of us deliberately chose the location of the blue dragon whale, but where is the blue dragon whale now?"

"We can stop looking for it, this is the method of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. Even though the scene in front of us is very realistic, it might just be an illusion for all we know."

"Come to speak of it, we have not seen the true appearance of the blue dragon whale until now."

The three immortals sighed.

There were really quite many secrets involving the blue dragon whale.

The blue dragon whale was a legendary immemorial beast that was enlightened by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, it gained an immortal aperture and could cultivate, it should have intelligence rivaling ordinary people. But the entire time the Gu Immortals explored the paradise, they had never seen the blue dragon whale initiate contact with them.

The traces of the blue dragon whale were also very mysterious. When did it appear, how did it disappear, and where did it go in the process? Nobody knew.

The three Gu Immortals here were unable to find out the truth even after they had personally explored Dragon Whale Paradise.

Fang Yuan sighed internally, his original plan was to obtain both the blue dragon whale and the Merit Obelisk.

But the truth was, he had simply been dreaming.

This was a meticulous arrangement set up by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, it had some sort of mysterious purpose. It was like the Crazed Demon Cave in Northern Plains, which was created by Limitless Demon Venerable himself and was also a huge arrangement, Fang Yuan could only stop at the eighth level and could not enter the most important core, the ninth level.

"Wait, Crazed Demon Cave... crazed demon?" Fang Yuan suddenly had a thought.

Limitless Demon Venerable created Crazed Demon Cave that had demonic sounds that would cause living beings to go insane. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable also had a black fire in the Dragon Whale Paradise that could cause insanity.

Was there some sort of relationship?

"Thinking about it, Dragon Whale Paradise had many insane living beings. For example, the tiger king salamander that I killed..." Fang Yuan pondered.

These living beings were beyond saving, Fang Yuan could not find out the reason, he could only kill them.

Other than the absence of black fire, they had nearly the same problem as Shen Shang.

From this point, it showed how powerful Shen Shang was!

This person, even with black fire on him, had only gone insane for some time, he relied on his immense human path foundation and dao marks to suppress it and regain his clarity.

Even Fang Yuan was not confident in achieving this.

He knew that even though he had many dao marks, they were not of human path.

"Currently speaking, Shen Shang is likely the number one person in the five regions when it comes to human path! Even that Old Man Zheng Yuan in Heavenly Court cannot compare to him."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan inevitably considered the fact that the fate battle was not far away. It was likely that Shen Shang could cause some trouble to Heavenly Court in battle.

The three immortals could not detect the blue dragon whale and decided to bid each other farewell.

They all had significant gains from their expedition to the Dragon Whale Paradise. But the one who gained the most was undoubtedly Fang Yuan.

While alone, Fang Yuan transformed back into the appearance of Qi Sea Ancestor and returned to qi sea under concealment.

The large formation in the depths of qi sea was still in operation, and in the formation, he met Wu Shuai, who was guarding the place.

Wu Shuai had gone to Southern Border in order to trade dream realms with Chi clan. Chi Qu You saw the opportunity and raised the price, Wu Shuai thought of the big picture and did not want to accept Chi Qu You's price, he planned to settle the score after everything was over.

But to think that Wu Yong found out about the loss of the dream realms. He became enraged, he went to Chi Qu You for a discussion.

Chi Qu You naturally denied all accusations, he refused to admit his involvement.

But after this warning, Chi Qu You had to stop and temporarily end the dream realm transactions.

Wu Shuai had no choice but to return to Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan met with Wu Shuai and learned about the current situation of the world.

It was quite bad.

In Southern Border, Wu Yong's influence was growing. Because of the mysterious disappearance of the dream realms, Chi Qu You faced much suspicion. Wu Yong used this chance to consolidate his influence over the entire Southern Alliance.

In Western Desert, however, the clone Fang Di Chang, who Fang Yuan was placing much hopes on, was currently facing a tough predicament.

After he allied with several super forces to repel Heavenly Court, a blood path great expert appeared in Western Desert, he caused chaos everywhere. He seemed to hate super forces, Fang clan became one of his victims.

Other than this, an immemorial desolate beast started to cause havoc in Fang clan's ice-fire desert.

This immemorial desolate beast was very crafty, Fang clan failed many attempts to capture or kill it.

As for Profound Literature grotto-heaven, Li Xiao Bai was having smooth progress.

In Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, Zhan Bu Du was facing a huge problem, his life was at risk.

Chapter 1917: I Am Your Father

Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

The sky could not be seen for the last few months, the entire grotto-heaven was covered in black poisonous smoke.

The poisonous smoke covered the entire sky and rumbled continuously, occasionally turned into dragon shapes that rampaged and caused destruction to the world.

Within Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, there were anguished cries, the future was bleak.

Star Collection City was the largest city in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, it was also now the largest gathering spot of all of humanity here.

The walls of Star Collection City towered high, there were many towers within the city.

Zhan Bu Du was standing on the highest tower, looking up at the rumbling poisonous smoke in the sky.

He looked exhausted and was bruised all over.

Behind him, a female Beast Warrior was healing his wounds.

"My main body has adjusted the speed of time flow in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven to become too fast, it caused frequent tribulations to descend. In this grotto-heaven, any calamity or tribulation will turn into a beast calamity. However, before the former beast calamity is annihilated, the new one will arrive. These beast calamities are spread all over the place, taking the attention of all the Gu Immortals in the grotto-heaven. After gradually accumulating, they all merged together and became the monsters they are today! Sigh... this time, my main body has made a mistake."

Zhan Bu Du's brows were locked in worry.

The Combat Beast Warrior who was treating his wounds advised: "Little Du, you'd better rest. You just fought a fierce battle for three consecutive days and nights without sleep. If this continues, no matter how tough your body is, you won't be able to survive."

Zhan Bu Du sighed deeply: "I am now the strongest Combat Beast Warrior here, I must fight to the best of my ability. If I am on the battlefield, fewer people will be sacrificed!"

"Little Du, you've done well enough. If you hadn't sensed something was wrong and informed everyone beforehand, we would not have had the major cities gather their civilians in advance. In that case, there would definitely be deaths and injuries. You are truly worthy of being our savior, you saved the lives of hundreds of thousands of people." The Combat Beast Warrior said.

Even though she was a senior Combat Beast Warrior, she felt deep appreciation and admiration towards this junior Zhan Bu Du.

Zhan Bu Du had managed to gain the recognition of everyone in this grotto-heaven during this period. Not only was it because of his high battle strength, but more crucially, his love for civilians, his selfless sacrifice, and his repeated battles on the front lines.

Right now, Zhan Bu Du was a great hero, he was a role model and the idol of all the commoners.

But in reality, Zhan Bu Du was only trying his best to preserve his possessions. Whether it was him or Fang Yuan, they had already regarded Beast Calamity grotto-heaven as their own property.

Although Beast Calamity grotto-heaven had preserved most of its vitality because of Zhan Bu Du's timely warning, the things that had been lost were still enough for Zhan Bu Du to feel distress.

"Here we go again!" Zhan Bu Du looked tense suddenly.

The Beast Warriors around him also tensed up and looked up at the sky at once.

Only to see that in the sky, poisonous smoke fiercely swirled and roared like a dragon, a giant dragon made of poisonous smoke descended.

The dragon's body was so huge that it stretched for eight hundred feet, and the dragon head was like a small mountain, ruthlessly crashing into Star Collection City on the ground.

Once it hit, half of Star Collection City would be instantly destroyed, and after the poisonous smoke spread, more than a hundred thousand people would die.

Of course, Zhan Bu Du would not allow this to happen.

With an eagle's cry, an arrow-tailed eagle flew out of his immortal aperture.

Combat Beast Warrior transformation!

In an instant, he transformed into an eagle-headed person, fiercely flapped his wings as he flew high into the air.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Zhan Bu Du attacked madly, sending out countless wind blades that were extremely sharp and fierce like a storm.

Hundreds and thousands of giant wind blades hit the dragon head, the poisonous smoke dragon head lasted for a moment before collapsing.

"It's Little Du."

"He helped us again."

"Worthy of Little Du."

The Combat Beast Warriors reacted one after another, expressing praises.

The civilians located in various parts of Star Collection City, upon seeing this scene, shouted "World Savior Zhan Bu Du", and soon, such voices quickly spread! All over the city, commotions were rising, filling the entire Star Collection City with frenzied cheers.

Zhan Bu Du did not relax but looked up into the sky vigilantly, shouting: "Attention everyone, another wave of attack is coming."

Poisonous smoke surged and more than a dozen poisonous smoke dragons suddenly appeared, rushing towards Star Collection City.

The people's cheering came to an abrupt halt.

The Combat Beast Warriors were instantly pale as paper.

In the past, the attack was at most three to five poisonous smoke dragons, but now the number had multiplied fivefold, and it was simply not something they could resist.

"Is this going to be the end of us?"

"Damn it!"

"I don't want to die!"

Just at the critical moment, the Star Snail Hall suddenly surged with a blinding starlight, and then a giant suddenly appeared and established itself on the battlefield.

The people were overjoyed, Zhan Bu Du also pretended to be extremely surprised, but in his mind he already knew: "The old fellow is finally willing to take action."

This was the current generation Combat Beast King, using the corpse of the Star Sea Snail to transform, he had the highest battle strength in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven and was also the final trump card.

When Fang Yuan had transformed into a bull-headed demon god, he had also fought with the Combat Beast King.

The giant was clad in heavy armor and kept punching, fist shadows shot out violently, like meteors rushing into the sky.

The meteors hit the poisonous smoke dragon heads with extraordinary effect. Several poisonous smoke dragon heads were destroyed on the spot, the momentum of the poisonous smoke dragon heads was ruthlessly stalled, which gave some crucial time for the other Combat Beast Warriors.

Next, the giant's feet stomped on the ground and its hands supported the sky, a hemispherical curtain of starlight rose up, enveloping the city.

The poisonous smoke dragons were temporarily blocked out by the giant curtain of starlight, one by one the Combat Beast Warriors were enveloped in a layer of blue light, floating out and engaging the poisonous smoke dragons fiercely in battle.

The Combat Beast Warriors were merely flesh and blood, they were quickly at a disadvantage.

The poisonous smoke giant dragons kept on coming, no matter how many of them were blown up, there would be new poisonous smoke giant dragons produced.

"If this continues, I'm afraid that today will be the day Star Collection City gets destroyed." Realizing this, the Combat Beast King made up his mind at last.

He called out loudly, his voice echoing through the battlefield: "The situation is urgent, Little Du, go and take the last inheritance. You are our final hope to save everyone today!"

"This old fellow is finally willing to give me the last part of his inheritance!" Zhan Bu Du sneered in his mind.

Currently, he had already obtained the Beast Calamity true inheritance in various important places, and only the last part was missing.

He had been in Star Collection City for many days, but the current generation Combat Beast King had not mentioned anything about it. Zhan Bu Du also had to temporarily pretend that he did not know the last part of the inheritance was in Star Collection City.

"Little Du, go, I'll be guarding this place."

"Quickly go, Little Du, it's up to you."

"We'll buy you time, even if it is the last moment of our lives, we'll do our duty!"

The Combat Beast Warriors urged.

Undeniably, the Gu Immortals in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven were really different from the outside world of the five regions, they had the spirit to sacrifice and contribute their lives.

Zhan Bu Du flew to the underground of the Star Snail Hall and arrived at the last altar.

The altar shined brightly, the qilin heavenly spirit appeared all of a sudden.

"Oh young man, you are qualified to inherit the entire Beast Calamity true inheritance. It's time to tell you the truth about the world." The voice of the qilin heavenly spirit was like that of a young child, crisp and cute.

After receiving the memories, Zhan Bu Du showed a look of shock and disbelief: "So our world is so small, the true way to use Gu worms is not by transformation! This is too unexpected."

"Heavenly spirit, what do I do now?"

The qilin heavenly spirit stood in front of Zhan Bu Du as it lowered its head: "Master, I don't have any method now. Ever since the change in the tributary of the River of Time, the tribulations in the grotto-heaven had been appearing non stop. Among these tribulations, there is one myriad tribulation among them! I'm afraid I cannot escape this now, I will open the door now, master, you need to escape quickly."

The moment Zhan Bu Du inherited the complete Beast Calamity true inheritance, the qilin heavenly spirit acknowledged him as master.

Zhan Bu Du sighed deeply and was about to open his mouth, but suddenly his expression changed drastically, revealing genuine surprise: "No need, my main body has already arrived!"

At the critical moment, Fang Yuan's main body finally arrived.

Looking at the poisonous smoke everywhere, Fang Yuan also felt a headache.

Zhan Bu Du ordered the qilin heavenly spirit to open the grotto-heaven's entrance, Fang Yuan came in here with no obstruction.

Because he was no longer an intruder, and because the qilin heavenly spirit acknowledged a master, myriad beings assimilation transformation was no longer taking effect on Fang Yuan's main body, he was able to come in personally.

Thus, the Combat Beast Warriors in the battlefield saw an unimaginable scene.

A man was floating in mid-air, his aura as strong as the sea. The poisonous smoke dragons seemed to be stimulated by the mysterious visitor, most of them turned towards Fang Yuan to kill him.

"Who is he?"

"Get away!"

"Oh no, it's too late."

The Combat Beast Warriors roared in rage and despair as they watched Fang Yuan being heavily surrounded by the poisonous smoke dragons.

At the moment the poisonous smoke dragons descended on him, Fang Yuan made his move.

Rumble!

In an instant, qi currents surged as wind and waves soared. The sky and earth changed color, all the poisonous smoke receded.

Fang Yuan stood proudly in the sky, the poisonous smoke dragons around him dissipated, even the thick layer of poisonous smoke above his head was torn open to expose a huge hole. Bright light shined down through the round hole, causing Fang Yuan to be bathed in sunlight.

The Combat Beast Warriors opened their mouths one by one, extremely shocked.

As soon as Fang Yuan made his move, he displayed such intense might in battle. Furthermore,he did not use any transformations at all, he had used such great battle strength just by himself.

This scene caused the long-standing cultivation thought process of the Combat Beast Warriors to crumble.

For a moment, the crowd was at a loss.

At this time, Fang Yuan slowly spoke, his voice clearly entering the ears of everyone present: "Little Du, where are you? Father is here."

The group of immortals were surprised again!

Zhan Bu Du flew out, looking surprised and teary-eyed: "Father, you've finally come out of seclusion. Please save the world."

At the next moment, the entire Star Collection City went into an uproar.

It turned out that this mysterious man was actually Zhan Bu Du's father, no wonder he was so powerful!

This was a secluded expert.

They were saved, they were definitely saved!

Fang Yuan sighed and spoke in a tone of bitter loss: "I never expected such a disaster to occur this time when I stayed in closed cultivation. It's a pity that I was isolated from the outside world during my seclusion, if I had known earlier, I would never have let these poisonous smoke dragons wreak havoc for so long."

After saying that, Fang Yuan struck again and quickly dispersed the entire area of poisonous smoke.

However, there was too much poisonous smoke, spreading throughout the grotto-heaven, soon the poisonous smoke was replenished through the smoke at other areas.

"Father, the situation is now under control, let's go down and take a rest first." Zhan Bu Du said.

"Okay." Fang Yuan nodded.

Thus, the two of them slowly flew into Star Collection City amidst countless gazes of adoration, longing, awe, and curiosity.

Chapter 1918: Crucial Person

Heavenly Court.

Star Constellation Chessboard was half a foot off the ground, slowly rotating between Fairy Zi Wei and Feng Jin Huang, blossoming with brilliant starlight.

The specks of starlight were so dazzling that they resembled blue fireflies, lightly jumping, sometimes swirling around the two, sometimes burrowing into their brains and colliding.

The two sat opposite each other, both with their eyes closed and brows knitted tightly, pondering over some difficult question.

The starlight slowly disappeared, Star Constellation Chessboard flew into Fairy Zi Wei's hands.

Fairy Zi Wei slowly opened her eyes, but Feng Jin Huang did not, she fell softly to the ground as she had passed out on the spot.

"This child..." Fairy Zi Wei was not nervous, she merely sighed.

She knew Feng Jin Huang's condition like the back of her hand.

In the end, Feng Jin Huang was only a Gu Master, unlike Fairy Zi Wei who was a rank eight great expert. The original deduction speed arranged by Fairy Zi Wei was very suitable for Feng Jin Huang.

However, Feng Jin Huang insisted that she did not want to slow down the progress and waste Fairy Zi Wei's time because of her own reasons. After all, Fairy Zi Wei was a key figure in Heavenly Court.

When Feng Jin Huang slowly woke up, she found that she had already left the deduction hall and had returned to Central Great Hall.

"Well done, Huang Er!" Duke Long looked at Feng Jin Huang and was extremely pleased: "You have actually improved the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, eliminating the flaw of this physique entirely. You are indeed worthy of being the fated Great Dream Immortal Venerable."

Feng Jin Huang was a little embarrassed from the praise: "Master, to be honest, I was only able to do so by coincidence. Do you remember the killer move shatter dream I created previously? This modification was done based on its results. The entire process was thanks to Lady Zi Wei's deductions, I was only playing a minor supplementary role in modifying the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique."

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "Little Huang Er, you're too modest. It is precisely because you provided the correct direction that we were able to make our deductions. If not for that, I'm afraid that even if I had made many calculations, I would have gained nothing."

Duke Long spoke with great solemness: "Huang Er, this perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique is extremely significant to you, it is the key to your future achievements. You must grasp it well and remember that you must undergo immortal ascension using the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique in the future."

Feng Jin Huang had never seen such solemnity from Duke Long before, she nodded her head: "Yes master, I will definitely keep that in mind."

Duke Long nodded: "You can go, I still have important matters to discuss with Fairy Zi Wei."

"This disciple takes her leave." Feng Jin Huang immediately left obediently.

"This time, Huang Er was able to obtain the perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, you deserve credit for that!" Duke Long said to Fairy Zi Wei.

It was indeed so.

Not only did Fairy Zi Wei play a major role in the deduction, but the original Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique was also obtained because she looked through the memories of Spectral Soul.

Without this foundation, no matter how much inspiration or direction Feng Jin Huang had, she would not be able to make any progress.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "This is my duty. If you hadn't captured Spectral Soul alive, I wouldn't have been able to soul search him. Speaking of which, the one Huang Er has to thank is you, her master."

Duke Long shook his head slightly: "This is shameful, as a master, I actually have very little to teach. I don't know anything about dream path, but fortunately, Huang Er possesses an extraordinary talent in dream path. It is also an honor for me to be able to do something for the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable. How has the practice of the killer move benevolent equality gone recently?"

Fairy Zi Wei's face turned solemn: "There is no problem with benevolence Gu, as for the killer move, I have successfully activated it several times."

"Did you find anything strange?" Duke Long pursued.

Fairy Zi Wei denied: "Not at all."

Duke Long intoned: "This means that benevolent equality is effective. But why haven't we seen any results?"

"Yes." Fairy Zi Wei's eyebrows were knitted: "Using benevolent equality to deal with Spring Autumn Cicada is a plan we have had all along. Looking at Fang Yuan's recent actions, all of them have been well planned and prepared, such as the battle in the River of Time, or the Dragon Palace fight, he had a good head start. He must have been reborn already, but why does no one on our side have memories of the previous life?"

The effect of benevolent equality was just as the name implied. Once Fairy Zi Wei used the killer move, the people that she looked at during the process would experience equivalent changes to their conditions.

For example, after Fairy Zi Wei used benevolent equality, she saw Fang Yuan's rebirth. At the same time, she looked towards Duke Long.

Then if Fang Yuan self-detonated using the killer move spring autumn success, his memories would go back to his past self. Duke Long would receive the same treatment, his memories would also go back to his former self.

"We don't know exactly what happened in Fang Yuan's last life. Previously, it was speculated that we couldn't borrow benevolence Gu, causing benevolent equality to be unusable. But now it seems we indeed gained this method."

"So was this result the effect of Fang Yuan's rebirth, and we actually did not gain benevolent equality in our previous life, or was it because something happened to me in the previous life, causing me to not use benevolent equality on him?"

Fairy Zi Wei was in a predicament.

A while after being awakened and understanding the current situation, Duke Long proposed to use benevolent equality to deal with Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was refined by his disciple, Red Lotus Demon Venerable, Demon Venerable knew the ways to deal with this cicada.

The time of Fang Yuan's rebirth was easily calculable by Fairy Zi Wei, it was at the time when Heavenly Court attacked Lang Ya blessed land.

The Fang Yuan before this and the Fang Yuan after this time had a different style of action and a completely different success rate in his plans.

Before Heavenly Court attacked Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan failed to regain the upper extreme heavenly eagle and was trapped by Lu Wei Yin.

After that, Fang Yuan had countless adequate preparations to deal with Heavenly Court's attack. Heavenly Court's side was repeatedly restrained, their advantages could not be utilized while their disadvantages were infinitely magnified, yet Fang Yuan was just the opposite.

Duke Long pondered: "Actually, there is another possibility. In the previous life, you successfully used benevolent equality, but you saw no one else but Fang Yuan. Or perhaps this person is not a Gu Immortal who is loyal to Heavenly Court."

There was a slight flicker of light in the eyes of Fairy Zi Wei: "If that's the case, then who could this crucial person be?"

Longevity Heaven.

Bzzz bzzz bzzz....

Orange-yellow light flickered endlessly, enveloping the sky of Longevity Heaven.

Next, an aura started from an extremely weak state and grew rapidly, soon filling the world and shaking people's hearts.

Such a change had already attracted the attention of Five Elements Grandmaster, Bull Demon, and Flower Lady.

Five Elements Grandmaster was a lone cultivator of Northern Plains, but after getting trapped by Longevity Heaven, he felt despair after struggling and decided to join Longevity Heaven, he was not stationed in Longevity Heaven permanently.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady were a duo that took the role of North Desolation Immortal together.

"What happened?" Five Elements Grandmaster was very uncertain.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady looked at each other, seeing the joy on each other's faces, the latter giggled: "West Desolation Immortal Bing Sai Chuan has awakened!"

"Bing Sai Chuan?" Five Elements Grandmaster's brows rose, he felt that the name was familiar.

At this moment, there was a loud roar, ripples of light flickered in the sky, rainbows extended like rivers as they pierced through the horizons.

A figure walked down from the river, he had a tall body and soft facial features, but his eyes were extremely sharp and icy, emitting a cold gaze. From his right ear to the left corner of his lips, there was an ugly scar, it was flickering with white light, while emitting the coldness of a thousand year profound ice.

Five Elements Grandmaster was deeply shocked: "I remember now, this is the Bing Sai Chuan who was born in Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's generation, he was a rank eight legend, a time path great expert, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had tried three times before subduing him. He did not die, he is actually the West Desolation Immortal of Longevity Heaven?!"

Longevity Heaven was a bit different from Heavenly Court, it had Four Desolation Immortals and Eight Extremities, a total of twelve positions. Among which, the Four Desolation Immortals were only meant for rank eight Gu Immortals, while the Eight Extremities needed at least rank seven cultivation level, and they had to be elites among rank sevens.

"Greetings, Senior West Desolation." Bull Demon and Flower Lady quickly went to greet him while Five Elements Grandmaster followed after with a reverent expression.

West Desolation Immortal Bing Sai Chuan's seniority was simply too high.

Bing Sai Chuan went up to the three, he nodded after looking around: "I am awake but I do not have much lifespan, time is limited. Give me the information of the current world, I need to know about it."

Longevity Heaven had very comprehensive information.

They had detailed information of the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the reappearance of Dragon Palace in Eastern Sea, and Heavenly Court's Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

"Fang Yuan... he actually extorted Southern Border's righteous path using rank seven cultivation level, while causing huge problems for Heavenly Court time and again in the River of Time. He is truly a world-shaking person!"

"Qi Sea Ancestor... able to fight equally with Duke Long? This is very rare, Eastern Sea has a lot of hidden depths."

"There's also Fang Di Chang, he actually refined Divine Bean Palace. Haha, this world really has no lack of experts!"

After gaining intel, Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly with a heroic aura.

After his laughter, Bing Sai Chuan's eyes shined with bright light: "Since Fang Yuan is the person who destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he is the crucial person who Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable mentioned."

Bull Demon, Flower Lady, and Five Elements Grandmaster were stunned.

Bing Sai Chuan's words involved the deep secrets of history.

Did Giant Sun Immortal Venerable predict that Fang Yuan would destroy Eighty-Eight True Yang Building? If he could predict that, why would he let Fang Yuan succeed?

Bing Sai Chuan did not answer them, he gave his orders: "We cannot let fate Gu be repaired completely, we need to stop them during this Refinement Path Convention. We have to contact Fang Yuan now and make an alliance!"

"What?" The three immortals were shocked.

Bing Sai Chuan frowned: "Can any of you contact Fang Yuan?"

The three immortals shook their heads in a daze.

Bing Sai Chuan's brows furrowed even tighter: "Then what are you waiting for? Do I have to search for the way to contact Fang Yuan myself?"

In the last life, Lang Ya Sect had joined Longevity Heaven, so they easily obtained a way to contact Fang Yuan from Lang Ya land spirit.

But now, Fang Yuan absorbed the entire four races variant human alliance including Lang Ya blessed land, Longevity Heaven was not involved.

Bing Sai Chuan wanted to contact Fang Yuan but he was stuck at the first step.

Chapter 1919: Immortal Gu Responsive Luck

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Northern Plains.

"Are you all prepared?" Xue Er stood in the snow crystal formation as she observed the tens of frost qi lumps.

"We are prepared, supreme elder." A female snowman rank five Gu Master knelt on the ground, speaking reverently.

"Then go, remember to attend to them enthusiastically. Of course, if you suffer any misgivings, do not take it wordlessly." Xue Er thought about it and said.

"Yes." The female snowman Gu Master left.

Xue Er sighed a little.

Ever since she had been placed here by Fang Yuan, she had been dedicated to the development of the snowman tribe. With the aid of Fang Yuan's snow crystal formation, Xue Er worked hard and the size of the snowman tribe quadrupled under her command, turning into a huge variant human tribe.

"My husband has finally brought in the human race... If I had the time, I'd love to go see for myself. Unfortunately, I can't get away here." Xue Er looked at the frost qi, she felt downcast.

She manipulated the formation, carefully maintaining it. Ever since Fang Yuan annexed Qi Sea grotto-heaven, his qi path dao marks had risen greatly, causing a tremendous impact to the sovereign immortal aperture, the effects had yet to stop, still gradually transforming every aspect of the sovereign immortal aperture.

For example, the snowman tribe with Xue Er in charge had been experiencing a surge in frost qi, every few months, Xue Er had to come here personally to manipulate the formation and maintain it.

If the frost qi gathers to a certain extent, beyond the limit, this frost qi would turn into a frost tide.

A frost tide would be a calamity for the physically weak snowmen.

As for the surroundings, it would be heavily damaged too. In fact, when the frost tide spreads out, it would be a problem for the whole of Mini Northern Plains.

Because of the regional walls, the other four mini regions would not be affected by the frost tide.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan sent a letter to inform Xue Er that a city would be placed near the snowman tribe's location. By then, he would need the snowman tribe to gather their people and send gifts while interacting with the newcomers.

Xue Er naturally followed his instructions, but all along, her variant human group had been suppressed by humans all along, asking her to interact with the humans now made her feel some lingering fear from her past.

If possible, Xue Er would like the whole of Mini Northern Plains to be ruled by snowmen.

But that was just an impossible dream.

Fang Yuan was a human after all, when his immortal aperture gets developed to an extent, he would bring in humans to live. That was the sign that an immortal aperture was prospering and growing.

The snowman tribe's group had just moved out when Mini Western Desert's inkman group arrived at its destination.

As the Inkman City Lord, Mo Tan Sang flew high in the sky, quietly awaiting.

"It's coming." Suddenly, his eyes shined with bright light.

In the sky, a dazzling rainbow light flashed brightly.

Around this colored profound light, the earth pushed out in all directions. The colored profound light grew larger and larger, gradually revealing the vague illusory phantom of a city.

This phantom became more and more real, eventually the brilliant light dissipated, adding thousands of miles of land to the original location.

A city was located at the center of the newly added land, it was the Sacred Eagle City of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

The inkman Gu Master group was already kneeling on the ground, praising and cheering at such a mystical sight, only when Mo Tan Sang gave the orders did they stand up.

The gates of Sacred Eagle City opened, the city folks inside had already been informed and quickly gathered into a welcoming party.

The two parties met at the city gates, as contact officially began.

The people of Sacred Eagle City curiously sized up the dark-skinned, white-haired inkmen, the inkmen gradually let go of their worries.

They had also been living under the heavy pressure of the human race for a long time, but they did not expect this new group of people to be so easygoing. The conversations stemmed from a place of equality, which made the inkmen happy from the bottom of their hearts.

"Is this Lord Mo Tang Sang?" The Eagle Warrior who was in charge of Sacred Eagle City flew towards Mo Tan Sang: "From now on, we will be in your care."

"Likewise, likewise." Mo Tan Sang smiled: "You don't have to be too polite, we're all allies here."

Mini Blue Heaven.

The cloud soil gathered into a small hanging continent.

After the starlight flashed, a majestic city was suddenly added to this originally empty continent.

This city was scarred and devastated, It was Star Collection City, which had resisted the poisonous smoke grand tribulation earlier.

In the center of Star Collection City, there was already a brand new Star Snail Hall, which was a mortal Gu House that Fang Yuan had purposely built.

As for the Star Sea Snail that originally served as the hall, it had been put into the treasury by Fang Yuan. This was an immemorial desolate beast, and the shell of the snail was an rank eight immortal material. If it was handed over to the old Combat Beast King, he would not know how to process it, he would only let the dao marks on the immortal material dissipate naturally. That would be too wasteful.

"Is this your father's world? It is so huge." The old Combat Beast King quietly left Star Collection City as he flew around, sighing to himself deeply.

Accompanying him was none other than Zhan Bu Du: "This is Mini Blue Heaven. There are nine other places like this in my father's immortal aperture world. I'm sure we'll be able to live well here."

The old Combat Beast King nodded and asked: "How do we contact the others?"

"Use this. It is an information path mortal Gu." Zhan Bu Du took out a mortal Gu and handed it to the old Combat Beast King.

The Combat Beast King's cultivation was at rank eight but his knowledge was very shallow, this simple information path mortal Gu made him marvel in awe: "I can't believe that Gu worms can be this useful."

"This is how they should be used. The Beast Calamity true inheritance that I received says this as well." Zhan Bu Du smiled shyly: "Please don't blame me, Grandpa Combat Beast King, my father wanted me to keep this as a secret."

The old Combat Beast King nodded: "I understand. I wonder what your father wants me to do?"

"For the time being, we would like Grandpa Combat Beast King and the other warriors to learn the traditional Gu cultivation method. This place is not safe, we have strong enemies outside." Zhan Bu Du said vaguely.

The old Combat Beast King was shook: "Your father is willing to impart the true cultivation way to us?"

"Of course he is. We are all allies." Zhan Bu Du smiled.

Fang Yuan annexed Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

Getting rid of the myriad tribulation in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven expended a lot of his immortal essence and effort, but it could not stop Fang Yuan.

He almost singlehandedly got rid of the grotto-heaven's crisis, Fang Yuan's reputation also rose to its peak.

Next, with the help of Zhan Bu Du, the owner of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, he successfully annexed Beast Calamity grotto-heaven and brought it into his sovereign immortal aperture.

Different from the previous life, Fang Yuan had already made all the preparations now, he deduced everything in advance.

After annexing the grotto-heaven, he split up the grotto-heaven and placed the different parts all over the sovereign immortal aperture.

Beast Calamity grotto-heaven had several major gathering spots, some contained a portion of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's true inheritance.

Fang Yuan placed Sacred Eagle City, Dark Valley, Spirit Spring Forest, Mountain Cliff City, Star Collection City in Mini Western Desert, Mini Southern Border, Mini Central Continent, Mini Northern Plains and Mini Blue Heaven respectively.

Of course, other than that, the many major resource points in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven were also handled properly by Fang Yuan.

Fully absorbing this grotto-heaven would take time.

The fusing of ecologies needed to reach a balance, time was needed for that, as well as the patience of the Gu Immortals managing the place.

Fang Yuan obtained myriad beings assimilation transformation again, the qilin heavenly spirit was also alive at the largest piece of territory.

Fang Yuan gained more than two hundred thousand transformation path dao marks from this!

In the previous life, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven gave him over a hundred thousand transformation path dao marks only. But in this life, because of Fang Yuan's arrangements, there was ample time to trigger the second myriad tribulation.

The original owner of Beast Calamity grotto-heaven only survived the first myriad tribulation before dying. By the time Fang Yuan discovered Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, its second myriad tribulation was approaching.

After passing the second myriad tribulation, Beast Calamity grotto-heaven gained another hundred thousand dao marks.

Thus, in terms of transformation path dao marks, Fang Yuan gained about double of them this time.

The more dao marks he had, the better it was for him.

"Oh, Bing Sai Chuan has awakened, he wants to cooperate?" Fang Yuan received this information and smiled.

Even though Longevity Heaven could not contact Fang Yuan directly, they found a method to do so.

They knew that Southern Border's righteous path had been extorted by him before, they definitely had ways to contact him. Thus, by finding one of Southern Border's super forces, and paying a high price, they would gain this method.

Bing Sai Chuan immediately talked to Fang Yuan, saying that he wished to cooperate with him.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan was a little puzzled, but this time, he understood the reason.

"Bing Sai Chuan wants to work together and gather everyone's strength to try to snatch fate Gu away."

"However, I need them to attack Heavenly Court as well, they will test the water for me and lure away some firepower."

Fang Yuan was wary about many things in Heavenly Court.

For example, Genesis Lotus' painting path method, or the game of chess between two venerables in Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

Fang Yuan agreed to cooperate with Bing Sai Chuan.

This instead made Bing Sai Chuan have some doubts: "Why did Fang Yuan agree to this so readily? He is likely suspicious of us, he wants to see our future actions."

Bing Sai Chuan frowned, he felt that he should find an opportunity to fight together with Fang Yuan and show his sincerity.

But after thinking about it, Bing Sai Chuan could not find any suitable targets.

In the previous life, he had no such worries. Be it the River of Time's stone lotus island or Dragon Palace, he could ally with Fang Yuan to fight.

But in this life, Fang Yuan changed many things. He obtained Dragon Palace in advance, the River of Time battle ended in Heavenly Court's defeat, they had not recovered even now, still being fearful to step into this forbidden ground that Fang Yuan personally created.

Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling looked at Feng Jiu Ge, smiling: "Tell me, since you approached me personally, what is your request?

Towards this exemplary junior who was also the Dao Guardian of the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable, Qin Ding Ling was quite appreciative.

Feng Jiu Ge hesitated for a while before speaking: "I would like to borrow a rank eight luck path Immortal Gu from senior — Responsive Luck."

Qin Ding Ling was slightly surprised, before she realized: "Sure, I agree to your request."

Saying so, she handed responsive luck Immortal Gu to Feng Jiu Ge on the spot.

Feng Jiu Ge was slightly stunned.

Qin Ding Ling said: "I know that you are creating a new killer move, this responsive luck Immortal Gu must be very helpful to you, otherwise, with your nature, you will not ask to borrow my Gu worm."

Feng Jiu Ge nodded, receiving responsive luck Immortal Gu: "That is correct."

He had already created an eighty percent complete destiny song, he found that rank eight fate armor Immortal Gu could not shoulder the grand and vast destiny song, he needed another luck path Immortal Gu as the core.

With Feng Jiu Ge's current understanding, responsive luck Immortal Gu was the most suitable for him.

Qin Ding Ling looked at this Immortal Gu and sighed: "The Immortal Gu recipe for responsive luck Immortal Gu was not actually created by me, I had secretly taken a look at the manuscript written by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. In the future, if you use this Gu to deal with the Northern Plains Gu Immortals, we will give them a taste of their own medicine. I will give this Immortal Gu to you."

Feng Jiu Ge thanked Qin Ding Ling as he said: "This Gu is not enough, I will need to head to the River of Time, view the past and present, and observe the paths of all lives."

Qin Ding Ling frowned: "According to what I know, even though Heavenly Court is working at full speed, we have only created one time path Immortal Gu House as of now. Going to the River of Time now is simply courting death. Let me take a look at your luck, to try to find a hidden chance for you."

Feng Jiu Ge thanked her once again.

Chapter 1920: Convention Begins

The River of Time flowed endlessly.

Heavenly Court.

Discussion hall.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals gathered, there were few Gu Immortals who did not come, this was the largest gathering that Heavenly Court had in the last thousand years.

Duke Long sat at the highest seat, he looked around: "We have explained our plan, go ahead and execute it. Whether we can restore the glory of Heavenly Court will depend on everyone's hard work."

"We will do our best!" All of the immortals resounded, they were very motivated.

The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention that would affect all five regions and the future of the world was about to begin!

Once news got out, the world was shaken.

Thanks to Fang Yuan's intentional spread of news, all the Gu Immortals knew of the importance of this Refinement Path Convention. But mortal Gu Masters had no idea, they thought that this Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was like the usual ones in the past.

Gu Masters started to move, heading towards Central Continent.

Each Central Continent Refinement Path Convention would attract the Gu Masters of the other four regions to participate, it involved all five regions and was a huge event.

But this time was slightly different from the beginning.

Western Desert.

A huge group of Gu Masters stood in front of the regional wall.

A youngster sighed loudly: "Father, if I were not seeing this personally, I simply could not believe there is such an amazing thing in the world."

"This is the regional wall. Once we get past this, we will reach Central Continent." The middle aged Gu Master beside the youngster said: "After entering the regional wall, our vision will be restricted, by then, you need to stay by my side and not get lost. Understood?"

"Yes father, I will." The youngster nodded obediently.

"Mm." Zhang Quan looked at his son Zhang Ping, feeling very proud.

His son had strong refinement path talent, for his future development, Zhang Quan brought him on a journey to participate in the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, to train his refinement path ability and also to gain some knowledge.

"What sound is that?" At the next moment, Zhang Quan looked up in confusion.

Next, his pupils shrunk as he showed great shock.

A huge meteor that was the size of a hill crashed down towards them.

The surrounding Gu Masters screamed in fear.

"Why is this happening? We're doomed!" Instantly, Zhang Quan felt great regret. If he had decided to travel to Central Continent alone, his son would not die with him.

Boom!

The meteor crashed down on the ground, causing an earthshaking explosion.

Zhang Quan and the rest died without intact corpses.

In the sky, an inkman Gu Immortal looked around coldly before leaving.

Similar scenes were happening all over the five regions.

These Gu Immortals were all Fang Yuan's subordinates, they had received his order to prevent people from joining the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

Next, Fang Yuan publicly announced in treasure yellow heaven: "If anyone joins the Refinement Path Convention, you will be making an enemy out of me, one day, I will find you and settle the score!"

The Gu Immortals of the five regions sighed in amazement: The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention had just started but Fang Yuan made his move already. As expected of the Little Demon Venerable, he was rampant and brutal.

Heavenly Court was enraged!

Because the assault of Fang Yuan's subordinates would cause much fewer Gu Masters to join the convention, it would be disadvantageous in repairing fate Gu.

Different from the previous life, Fang Yuan ordered his subordinates to only move around Northern Plains, Southern Border, Western Desert, and Eastern Sea. This way, Central Continent and Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals could not head to the other four regions and save these people.

During this period of time, if Central Continent and Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals head to the other four regions, they would be angering and provoking the other four regions' super forces.

Heavenly Court could only accuse Fang Yuan of his heinous crimes and communicate with the righteous paths of the other regions to get them to take revenge on this terribly demonic act.

The righteous paths of the other four regions responded loudly but they took little action, even if they did anything, they were merely doing it superficially, creating a lot of noise but little effect.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan acted in Central Continent itself and was faced with much obstruction not long after.

In this life, Fang Yuan took action in advance, he immediately gained huge results in battle.

The waves of Gu Masters rushing to Central Continent immediately ceased.

Nobody wanted to die just because of one Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

Furthermore, the four regions' super forces had also stopped their own Gu Masters from joining the convention, it caused this current Refinement Path Convention to be very sparse in attendants.

Central Continent, Unification Sect.

As one of the sign up locations of the Refinement Path Convention, it was filled with people and commotion as well.

"The Refinement Path Convention is about to start! Strange, why do I not see people from the other four regions?" Luo Sheng sighed.

In the previous Refinement Path Convention, he had lost to a Northern Plains Gu Master by chance, this time, he was trying to find that Northern Plains Gu Master again for a rematch.

Luo Sheng was eager to prove himself.

"But Central Continent is too large, the five regions are too broad, geniuses are everywhere."

He looked around and found that three people here were tough opponents for himself.

One was an old man that had been reputed for many years, he was also a refinement path master. Another was a young man, and the last one was a young girl. The former had performed well in the previous convention while the latter was a rising star that had emerged in the last ten years.

"This Refinement Path Convention is still going to be that intense!"

"I must make good use of this opportunity, I cannot fail anymore..."

"I will prove myself, I will let my wife and children be proud!"

Boom!

At the next moment, a huge ancient year beast descended from the sky, crushing the entire hall to ruin.

All of his grand ambitions vanished into thin air.

The young Gu Master with a great future, the genius young girl who was thought of highly, they all died pitifully on the spot, their bones and flesh were mashed together, even the corpses could not be seen clearly.

In the sky, Bai Ning Bing's figure flashed rapidly.

She was in charge of moving around, every destination she reached, she released ancient year beasts. As for the result, Fang Yuan said that she did not need to be concerned with that.

Earlier, Fang Yuan sent variant human Gu Immortals to kill Gu Master participants in advance. Now, he ordered Shadow Sect's immortals to infiltrate Central Continent and use ancient year beasts to destroy the sign-up locations, to create bloodshed as countless elite Gu Masters face their end.

After learning of this situation, Heavenly Court immediately spread news of the truth.

"There really are immortals in this world..."

"The culprit behind everything is Fang Yuan!"

"Fang Yuan, you killed my father, I will definitely take revenge for this immense hatred!"

"Even rank fives are just ants if they do not become Gu Immortals."

"Immortals are high and mighty, why must I sacrifice my life for a mere Refinement Path Convention? Forget it, forget it."

"I must go! If I do not go, wouldn't I fall into that Fang Yuan's scheme?"

Some were fearful, some felt emotional, some backed out, while some became determined.

"They are trying to gather the rage of the people and accumulate human will." In the previous life, Fang Yuan did not know what Heavenly Court was doing, but now, he was deeply aware.

Fang Yuan quickly ordered his subordinates to stop.

Heavenly Court and Central Continent's Gu Immortals gathered rage and hatred, they were about to take action when they found that Fang Yuan's subordinates all vanished without a trace.

"Isn't Fang Yuan trying to destroy the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention? Why did he stop?" The four regions' super forces who were watching the show felt very perplexed.

In a secret meeting in Southern Border, Wu Yong analyzed some of Fang Yuan's thoughts: "Fang Yuan had an early advantage, if he continues, Heavenly Court will deduce the locations of his attackers, he will lose many subordinates."

"Then will Fang Yuan attack again?" Someone asked.

"Of course." Wu Yong said without doubt: "But before that, we need to move out secretly too."

In the previous life, Fang Yuan attacked personally and caused destruction, not long after, he was marked by the killer move people's accusation, he had to hide while his subordinates like Bai Ning Bing took action.

This time, Fang Yuan lurked and concealed himself while ordering his subordinates to cause destruction and bloodshed.

Others were not like Fang Yuan who could defend against Fairy Zi Wei's deductions using wisdom path methods. Thus, Fang Yuan ordered Bai Ning Bing and the rest to hide themselves after causing some level of destruction.

The Refinement Path Convention had just started.

The huge battle had not begun, these subordinates were still very useful to Fang Yuan.

Chapter 1921: Conflict Rises

The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was wildly continuing, but Fang Yuan's group was nowhere to be found.

Fang Yuan gave the orders to retreat so quickly, the Gu Immortals of the five regions felt as if the slaughter earlier was not real.

"What is Fang Yuan doing?"

"The Central Continent Refinement Path Convention is still going on, why aren't you doing anything!"

"You are the Little Demon Venerable, don't bring shame to your reputation."

The four regions' super forces were very anxious as they complained, they wanted Fang Yuan to attack and take the role of charging into battle for them.

But Fang Yuan, who had opposed Heavenly Court all along, went missing now, he was in hiding and could not be seen anywhere.

The four regions' forces were about to feel some resentment towards him, as days passed, they watched as the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention continued to advance, all sorts of refinement path elites were progressing in the competition.

The number of test locations in Central Continent also shrunk greatly. Each area was now guarded by multiple Central Continent Gu Immortals arranged by Heavenly Court.

In this situation, Fang Yuan ordered again, various immortals including Bai Ning Bing, Bing Yuan, and Beast Calamity grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals took action.

Central Continent, Xuanwu mountain range.

"Bai Ning Bing, you have committed too much evil, you will face retribution eventually!" A female immortal from Spirit Affinity House was guarding this place, she said that before escaping.

Bai Ning Bing snorted coldly: "She ran really quickly."

Xuanwu mountain range was a giant resource point of Spirit Affinity House, it had a huge area and was a publicly known immortal material treasure trove.

"Problems will come with waiting, I should act quickly." Bai Ning Bing started to loot the place.

Central Continent, Imprisonment Valley.

"It's here." Steel Rush Warrior looked around.

Frost Butterfly Warrior came along with him: "Open!"

Once the killer move was used, a formation appeared in front of them.

Transformation!

The two rank seven Gu Immortals from Beast Calamity grotto-heaven did not hesitate to use their most proficient method. One turned into a giant with bull head and human body, while the other turned into a mini butterfly person that emanated frost energy.

As immortal killer moves were unleashed, the formation broke after resisting for a while.

"Southern thorns, the entire valley is made of immortal materials." Steel Rush Warrior was overjoyed.

Frost Butterfly Warrior was even more direct, freezing the southern thorns and looting them rapidly.

Central Continent, red river beach.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals who arrived were furious.

They were late, they only saw ruins left.

The blazing red stones that accumulated on the beach were all taken.

A clean sweep!

Fang Yuan was waiting silently earlier, but once he made a move, it shocked the world.

His Gu Immortals were almost fully deployed, even the hairy man Gu Immortals were sent out.

These people were instructed by Fang Yuan, they did not attack the sign-up spots that were heavily guarded, they targeted the resource points with weaker defenses instead.

Each time they broke into a resource point, these people would plunder it dry. After the plunder, they would use killer moves to completely destroy the place beyond salvation.

At once, the whole of Central Continent was set ablaze, all sorts of large resource points were plundered and destroyed.

Every time Fang Yuan succeeded in taking down an area, he would publish the results of his success in treasure yellow heaven.

The five regions' Gu Immortals went into a clamor.

"How does Fang Yuan have so many subordinates!"

"So many Gu Immortals, he has greatly surpassed a normal super force."

"How much strength is he hiding?!"

After feeling shocked, they felt envy and admiration.

Fang Yuan's subordinates had varying battle strength, but even the weakest Gu Immortal could succeed. For the Refinement Path Convention, Central Continent had lowered its defense of these resource points too much.

Many powerful Gu Immortals started to think: "Since these variant human Gu Immortals can plunder successfully, why can't I?"

And many weaker Gu Immortals started to think: "Most of the good stuff will be taken by those experts, but I can still get the leftovers, right?"

Thus, similar to the previous life, the four regions' Gu Immortals could not wait anymore, especially those demonic immortals and lone cultivators.

These people started to attack all the resource points around Central Continent.

The situation in Central Continent fell apart rapidly.

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei had a dark expression.

No matter how great her self-control, seeing all the information sources regarding resource points getting plundered and looted dry, she felt deep anger within her.

"Fang Yuan..." She gritted her teeth, emitting an intense killing intent uncontrollably.

It was this culprit who stirred everyone's desires and made Central Continent the hunting ground of the other four regions, it was plundered casually and suffered huge losses.

Be they Fairy Zi Wei, Duke Long, or Qin Ding Ling, they were helpless.

Central Continent was too big, it was at the center surrounded by the other four regions as well.

They had too few Gu Immortals, they could not send people to all the resource points, their manpower was severely lacking.

This gave thieves and bandits a chance to strike.

"People's hearts have changed." Qin Ding Ling sighed.

Duke Long was indifferent: "Sacrifices are necessary for our grand ambition. We will focus on the Refinement Path Convention, these immortal materials can be given up. Once fate Gu is repaired, we will make them pay back a thousandfold."

Central Continent was currently being ravaged.

Fang Yuan's timing was too impeccable, he chose the perfect moment where Heavenly Court was increasing its defense of the Gu refinement locations, these elites could not be lost as it would severely affect Central Continent's potential. And for the moment, their loss would be detrimental to repairing fate Gu.

Fang Yuan's target was also perfect.

For example, places like Xuanwu mountain range were too huge, it naturally had low defense. As for Imprisonment Valley and red river beach, he had looted them in the previous life, he knew their layout and defensive measures.

Together with his meticulous planning, Fang Yuan's subordinates had a high success rate. The ease of his plunder and immense gains lured all of the other four regions' Gu Immortals.

The Gu Immortals of all four regions quickly moved out to target the various resource points.

Central Continent had not given up on all their resource points, many important resource points were guarded by experts.

At once, all sorts of battles erupted, Gu Immortals fought and the moment they found that one resource point was too hard to take down, they would wisely give up and move to the next location.

Central Continent had so many resource points anyway, why would they be fixated on one area?

Western Desert earth path Gu Immortal Shi Gan Dang destroyed the earth qi rock forest and obtained a large amount of round kun stones.

Forgotten Daoist successfully stole the spirit bank spring water, even though it was defended by Ancient Soul Sect's expert Yang Feng.

Xiao Hu Chi, Xiao Shi Rang, and Pi Shui Han worked together and succeeded in their plunder, but because of the problem of distribution, they fought against each other.

Central Continent was full of conflict and fighting, it was utter chaos.

Fairy Zi Wei stayed in Heavenly Court, she felt that days were passing like years.

Eventually, Old Man Zheng Yuan spoke: "We have gathered enough human will now, we can use the first human path killer move."

Fairy Zi Wei was overjoyed, quickly asking him to make a move.

Old Man Zheng Yuan nodded, he stood up shakily as a grand and vast aura surged out of his body!

Immortal killer move — People's United Hearts!

The accumulated human will was expended rapidly, almost none was left.

At the same time, Central Continent's Gu Immortals, Gu Masters and even mortals became enveloped in a halo of light.

The halo flashed for a moment, it was like an illusion.

But Central Continent's people soon found something special.

Their hearts were connected, they could sense each other's thoughts and emotions.

The fear of being attacked, the sadness and hatred of having friends and family die, the worry towards one's own life, and the aspirations towards one's future...

Never had Central Continent's people been so tightly connected before in history.

Unfettered Scholar, who was hiding in the Gu refinement location, was discovered, he managed to exact revenge and kill the Central Continent Gu Immortal who was guarding the place.

Southern Border secluded immortal Zheng Qing was exposed too, but he had no animosity towards Central Continent or Heavenly Court, he was asked to leave politely.

"This human path killer move, people's united hearts, is truly amazing." Shen Shang communicated with Fang Yuan using treasure yellow heaven. His current location was unknown, Fang Yuan only knew that he had left Eastern Sea and could possibly even be in Central Continent now.

"What did you comprehend? Can we restrict these human path killer moves?" Fang Yuan asked, he had already given all of the information regarding these human path killer moves in his memory to Shen Shang.

Shen Shang sighed: "To negate these killer moves, the easiest way is to destroy the human will. Without human will as the foundation, these human path killer moves cannot be used. But I deduced that these human wills are kept in Heavenly Court."

"Then what about other ways?" Fang Yuan asked.

Shen Shang sighed again: "Then we can only unravel the killer move directly, this is very difficult, I will need a lot of time. Don't worry, since I promised you, I will do my best. I do not want to see a complete fate Gu either."

Fang Yuan continued to wait patiently.

Wu Yong led the Southern Alliance immortals as they appeared on Hairy Foot Mountain.

"Follow me, let us destroy Infallible blessed land, let's take all the success dao marks and make Heavenly Court taste failure!" Wu Yong announced.

"We will follow Lord Alliance Leader!!" The Southern Alliance immortals said together, they had high morale as they followed him.

Heavenly Court immediately received news about this.

Fairy Zi Wei's face was grim as cold light shined in her eyes: "This Wu Yong."

"Wu Yong has moved out. Longevity Heaven is also about to take action, it is time for me to make my move." After receiving the news, Fang Yuan smiled as he appeared near Yi Tian Mountain.

Chapter 1922: Southern Alliance Destroys Formation

Myriad Year Flying Warship floated in the sky, Fang Yuan looked at the formation in front of him with a smile.

He arrived at Yi Tian Mountain again, this time, he would definitely take all of the dream realms away.

This timing was truly impeccable.

Firstly, Wu Yong had led the Southern Alliance experts to infiltrate Central Continent, Southern Border was at its weakest now. Secondly, the huge battle had just started, this was likely the final period of free time for Fang Yuan.

"Different from the previous life, I had all the initiative this time, I defeated Heavenly Court repeatedly. The secret of my rebirth is known to all, Heavenly Court must have ways to counter it. Their arrangements will be different from the previous life, I should let the four regions' Gu Immortals strike first while I observe their new methods."

Fang Yuan had a firm grasp of the situation.

At this point, Fang Yuan's rebirth advantage was mostly depleted. His previous life's memories were not reliable against a colossal force like Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court would not be so stupid as to not make changes.

If Fang Yuan took the lead as the vanguard, he would be stuck in endless battles, unable to get away from fighting. He might even die in the process.

After all, Heavenly Court's foundation was unfathomable, Fang Yuan could not be sure that the venerable methods in his memories were all the methods left behind.

Immortal killer move — Refinement Formation Rain.

Rain started to fall from the sky, gradually infiltrating the formation.

There were naturally defending Gu Immortals in the formation.

The Gu Immortals were in panic.

The formation could not block him, the periphery had already been refined by Fang Yuan.

Even though this formation was set up by Chi Qu You, Fang Yuan had secretly undergone dream realm transactions with him, he gained a lot of information about this formation.

Fang Yuan's formation path and wisdom path attainment, along with refinement formation rain, completely countered this formation.

"This demon Fang Yuan did not attack Central Continent, he came back to Southern Border!"

"What do I do?"

"Seek help?"

"Our rank eight Gu Immortals have all gone to Central Continent under the lead of Lord Wu Yong!"

"We still need to inform them about this!"

The Southern Border Gu Immortals conversed for a while, nobody dared to go out to fight Fang Yuan, but they had no reinforcements either. They had to use the immortal formation and add changes to it.

The immortal formation continued to change, Fang Yuan's speed of refining the formation became slower instantly.

But Fang Yuan became happy internally.

The more this formation changed, the more he could comprehend the profundity within it. With the help of the light of wisdom, he could easily understand all of these secrets.

Within Central Continent, the Southern Alliance's immortals had already entered the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Wu Yong and the rest received this news.

"What? The dream realm was attacked?"

"That scoundrel Fang Yuan!"

"Can he see the big picture at all? He is actually attacking us at this time?!"

The Southern Alliance's immortals were furious.

Wu Yong was silent for a while before speaking: "Of course he can."

"What does Lord Wu Yong mean?" Ba De had a livid expression. Fang Yuan's actions were harming the benefits of all the Southern Border righteous path forces!

Everyone knew about the value of these dream realms, furthermore, they would get more important when the great era arrives.

Wu Yong smiled instead: "If Fang Yuan does not see the big picture, he would have attacked the dream realm long ago. He would not wait for us to go to Central Continent. Or maybe, he wants to make use of us as cannon fodder."

"Then aren't we sacrificing ourselves for him?" Someone asked in an indignant tone.

"No." Wu Yong shook his head: "If fate Gu is repaired, its threat will be far greater than the otherworldly demon Fang Yuan. He has been reborn, it seems we took the initiative to attack like now in the previous life. But there is no choice, we need to attack. This is for the sake of the five regions."

"Everyone, before we left, I already told you that our region would likely get attacked. Be they your family, friends, or our territory, all of the destruction and slaughter pale in comparison to the big picture! If Heavenly Court gains a complete fate Gu, we will all be helpless, there will be no future for anyone!"

Wu clan said this as his eyes shined like lightning, he looked around as he declared: "This is my order, let all of the defending Gu Immortals retreat from the formation, do not make unnecessary sacrifices. I know this is a risky move, but even if my Wu clan headquarters get destroyed, I will not retract my words!"

Wu Yong's determination shook the hearts of all the immortals.

They were all united now, the Southern Alliance immortals were tightly connected, they fought their way into the depths of the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

After Southern Border received Wu Yong's orders, the defending Gu Immortals sighed in relief, they brought as many Immortal Gu as they could with them as they started to teleport away.

A moment later, Fang Yuan refined the formation, not a single Southern Border Gu Immortal was in sight.

After he dismantled the formation, he received an information path Gu worm, it was a letter that Wu Yong had specially written to him.

Fang Yuan's divine sense swept through it, looking at the content.

The letter only had one sentence, it spoke of one viewpoint — The threat of Heavenly Court and Fate, Central Continent is strong, while the four regions are weak.

He did not say anything about asking Fang Yuan to stop.

"This Wu Yong…" Fang Yuan sighed to himself.

Earlier, he was a problem for Fang Yuan, using his political skills to restrict Fang Yuan's extortion and causing him great loss. But now, Wu Yong asked the Southern Border Gu Immortals to stop defending, he made them retreat and saved Fang Yuan a lot of effort.

If these Southern Border Gu Immortals continued to defend, it would waste a lot of time.

After Fang Yuan takes the dream realm, he would save a lot of time, that meant he could find trouble with the righteous path of Southern Border. Wu Yong's orders carried lots of risk, it was a bold move.

But Wu Yong was sure that Fang Yuan knew the big picture, he would not continue causing trouble in Southern Border.

It was like how Fang Yuan knew Wu Yong would not come back from Central Continent to defend these territories if he attacked.

And the truth was, Fang Yuan had no intention to find trouble with Southern Border's righteous path at this moment.

After some effort, Fang Yuan took away all of the dream realms here.

Yi Tian Mountain saw the light of day again, the huge Gu Immortal battles engraved here could be seen all around the mountain, there was no sign of life here, everything had changed.

Fang Yuan started to head to Central Continent.

As he traveled, he transformed these dream realms into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

In the following battle, these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies would be a huge force of his. In the previous life, Feng Jin Huang was able to resist the detonation of his Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, in this life, it was likely that she could do the same.

But Feng Jin Huang was just one single mortal Gu Master. Fang Yuan had the initiative, he had several battlefields to approach.

Heavenly Court, Central Great Hall.

Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, and Qin Ding Ling watched over the situation.

Old Man Zheng Yuan was also invited here.

"The latest news, Southern Border's Gu Immortals broke the first formation, they are going to the second formation. Fang Yuan appeared in Yi Tian Mountain and destroyed the formation, taking all the dream realms." Fairy Zi Wei suddenly said.

Duke Long said grimly: "Fang Yuan will not continue causing chaos in Southern Border, he will definitely go fight in Central Continent. It seems that we need to deal with these dream realms."

Fairy Zi Wei nodded: "We are very lucky that Feng Jin Huang created the perfect Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, she can resist Fang Yuan's dream path methods."

Duke Long chuckled: "You think this is luck? No, this is the power of fate! Heavenly Court will not lose this battle, we cannot lose."

At this moment, Fairy Zi Wei gasped as she showed a surprised expression: "Southern Border's immortals have broken the second formation, they are going to the third one now."

"So fast?" Even Qin Ding Ling was shocked.

Within nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, the immortals had high morale.

"Chi Qu You, good job."

"As expected of the sole formation path great grandmaster in Southern Border!"

"With Lord Chi Qu You around, how can any formation stop us? Hahaha."

Just earlier, when the immortals went into the second sub-formation, Chi Qu You spoke: "Stop."

Next, he observed the area and led the immortals to quickly and delicately destroy the formation.

The immortals praised him but Chi Qu You shook his head: "The truth is, I did not see through this formation, I had received information from Fang Yuan."

The expressions of the Southern Border immortals froze.

Chi Qu You continued: "Using my method, I can break this formation rapidly. But that is a forbidden method that will expend my lifespan. It seems that Fang Yuan had been reborn. In the previous life, he must have broken this formation too, he knows about it clearly."

The immortals nodded, agreeing with him.

What they did not know was, Chi Qu You was the one who explained the profundity of this formation to Fang Yuan.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan rushed to Hairy Foot Mountain from Emperor City battlefield, in order to destroy the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, the immortals wanted to use the five regional limit formation. But without the complete formation chart, and having to create it within the enemy's formation, it was too difficult.

Fang Yuan used his wisdom path and formation path attainment to cooperate with Chi Qu You and Black Extremity, working together to deduce the complete formation chart.

During this process, Chi Qu You gave Fang Yuan and Black Extremity an explanation on their experiences of breaking the earlier formations so that they could understand the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Since Wu Yong asked the Southern Border immortals to retreat, displaying greater sincerity and determination, Fang Yuan was returning the favor by guiding them now.

After learning of this situation, Wu Yong had a slightly complex expression as he sighed: "It seems that Fang Yuan has already arrived in Central Continent."

Fang Yuan understood Wu Yong, but Wu Yong also understood Fang Yuan.

The two of them had an indescribable understanding.

Even though they wanted each other to die during normal times!

The truth was, in the previous life, in order to break the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, Fang Yuan also asked the Southern Alliance for dream realms.

Wu Yong did not hesitate but agreed instantly.

Fang Yuan was transported back to Southern Border, the defensive formation was opened and he managed to take the dream realms away.

But later, when Fang Yuan converted them into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, Feng Jin Huang resisted them and he failed to destroy the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Using Fang Yuan's guidance, the Southern Alliance's immortals broke through another two formations, their efficiency was out of this world.

Heavenly Court finally reacted in time, Fairy Zi Wei frowned and thought about the countermeasure when suddenly, rainbow light appeared above Heavenly Court.

Bright lights spread everywhere, rank eight Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar shot out from within!

"Heavenly Court, we're here." Bing Sai Chuan called out with great morale.

"We have been waiting." Qin Ding Ling slowly stood up.

Chapter 1923: Stars During Daytime

Heavenly Court.

Colorful lights filled the sky, a huge rank eight Immortal Gu House flew out from within.

It had three floors of altars, grand and magnificent. There were multiple pillars holding each floor up, having white jade railings and shining aurora, it was eye-catching.

"Calamity Luck Altar!" Qin Ding Ling watched with shrunken pupils, her expression was complex.

She was looking at the Immortal Gu House that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable built personally, but the latter had passed away. Even if you were an Immortal Venerable, lifespan was limited.

"Heavenly Court." On the other hand, Bing Sai Chuan in Calamity Luck Altar was trembling with excitement.

At long last, he had finally attacked this place, commencing the great plan that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had entrusted to him — to seize fate Gu and refine destiny Gu!

"We really got in." The accompanying Five Elements Grandmaster was very shocked and surprised: "Is Heavenly Court's defense really this weak?"

"Of course not." Bull Demon explained in a deep voice: "This is the arrangement of our Ancestor Giant Sun. Back then, Golden Hoop Great Immortal invited our ancestor to come to the Heavenly Court for a visit, ostensibly proclaiming that he wanted to invite Ancestor Giant Sun into Heavenly Court. At that time, Ancestor Giant Sun secretly set up this arrangement, leaving it for the future."

Five Elements Grandmaster could not help but inwardly be astounded at the words, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's strategy was planned so long ago but he actually managed to use it so far in the future!

"Go! We'll use the route that Limitless Demon Venerable made when he previously attacked, we will attack Central Great Hall, ascend to Heaven Overseeing Tower, and seize fate Gu!" As soon as Bing Sai Chuan gave the order, the surrounding colored lights moved sharply.

Calamity Luck Altar was actually carried by the colored lights and moved to a distant place.

The qi wall left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had already activated, it sealed Calamity Luck Altar within the qi wall.

On the other side, Qin Ding Ling had a pale face as she fell to the ground.

She had already done her best to make some minor modifications to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangements. The so-called trap against Northern Plains would naturally be most effective with the help of a venerable method.

Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable left behind the killer move qi wall in Heavenly Court, it was everywhere. When the three Demon Venerables attacked Heavenly Court, they created three paths that had no qi wall along them. But all other areas were filled by the qi wall.

Qin Ding Ling worked her hardest to relocate Calamity Luck Altar into the qi wall.

At once, Calamity Luck Altar became immobilized, it faced a huge pressure from all directions.

Fairy Zi Wei quickly helped Qin Ding Ling to stand up as she said in admiration: "Senior, it was all thanks to you!"

Qin Ding Ling sighed and said with a solemn tone: "To think that even after I worked my hardest after waking up, I merely managed to move his method to a slight extent. Sigh..."

Duke Long walked slowly with a calm expression: "Let's go, it is time to welcome our guests."

"Damn it! Heavenly Court knew that we were going to attack, they made use of that to set up an ambush!" Bing Sai Chuan's expression changed, turning ashen.

The surprise attack that he had anticipated for so long had just started, but he already lost control of the situation.

He manipulated Calamity Luck Altar with all his strength but the killer move qi wall was too strong.

Even though this rank eight Immortal Gu House could barely move now with a snail-like speed, the most despairing thing was that the qi wall had a strong self-recovery ability. As Calamity Luck Altar moved, the qi wall behind it healed and mended together.

Just as Longevity Heaven's people suffered a setback, Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals arrived in Hidden Dragon Cave.

"To think that Hidden Dragon Cave is here." Song Qi Yuan sighed deeply to himself.

Granny Rong snickered: "This place is quite secluded indeed, but there is no such thing as absolutely hidden in this world."

Yang Zi He added: "Back then, Di Zang Sheng wreaked havoc in Central Continent, Duke Long suppressed and sealed it here, it was a huge event. But because that was long ago in history, and because Heavenly Court wanted to exterminate the dragonman race, they were ruthless in eliminating the traces."

"Hehehe. Speaking of which, Duke Long is very vicious, for the sake of Heavenly Court, he sacrificed all of his children and descendants." Shen Cong Sheng criticized with a tone of disdain.

Eastern Sea's eight Gu Immortals arrived here.

It was the same situation as the previous life.

To achieve this goal, Fang Yuan had put in a lot of effort secretly. On one hand, he used his status as Qi Sea Ancestor to hint to Song Qi Yuan and Hua Cai Yun, on another hand, he contacted Shen Cong Sheng using his own identity, and finally, the four rank eight lone cultivators in Eastern Sea were all Dragon Palace Dragon Generals, they obeyed Fang Yuan's arrangements.

Fang Yuan was not sure about Hidden Dragon Cave's location originally, but after getting Dragon Palace, he saw related records in it.

Back then, when Duke Long suppressed Di Zang Sheng, the dragonman race had put in effort too.

After getting this secret information, Fang Yuan spread it using the mouths of the Four Dragon Generals, influencing the decisions of all the different Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

These rank eight Gu Immortals from Eastern Sea were different from Southern Alliance and Longevity Heaven, they did not have any courageous spirit to take risks, in this life, they had no strong intention to gain Dragon Palace. Fang Yuan thus motivated them to release Di Zang Sheng from Hidden Dragon Cave and cause problems for Heavenly Court.

Once Di Zang Sheng gets released, the entire world would shake, blood would flow into rivers, living beings would die. There would be no need for these Eastern Sea Gu Immortals to fight.

Once Central Continent's attention was drawn and they sent Gu Immortals to deal with Di Zang Sheng, they would be weaker elsewhere, Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals would have a great opportunity.

There was another advantage, Di Zang Sheng would target and attack Central Continent's mortals.

The more people it killed, the more foundation Central Continent would lose.

Eastern Sea's righteous path rank eights would not attack mortals with their status, it would ruin their reputation. Having Di Zang Sheng do the dirty work was best.

At the fringe of Western Desert.

The thin regional wall was in front them.

"The five regions are indeed fusing. The regional walls that once restricted our movement are already so thin and weak." Fang Gong looked at the scene in front of him as he sighed.

Fang Yuan's clone, Fang Di Chang, had a high status in Fang clan, he managed to convince Fang clan's first supreme elder and many Western Desert super forces to take action together.

This was a much stronger group than in the previous life.

But gathering so many Gu Immortals used a lot of time, they only managed to assemble now.

"Oh no, that blood path demonic immortal is causing chaos in my clan." Right at this time, Sun clan reported bad news.

"There is a brand new immemorial desolate beast attacking my clan's oasis." Mo clan's Gu Immortal also received bad news.

"Everyone! This is likely Heavenly Court's scheme. They want to restrain us so that we cannot stop them from repairing fate Gu." Fang Di Chang analyzed.

Even though he had no proof, in order to stabilize these Gu Immortals, lying was fine.

"No, I need to get back."

"I objected earlier when you asked us to move out. Our base is too weak now, I was right after all."

"In my opinion, we should play safe. Western Desert's resources are all in the oases, if they are destroyed, our clans will lose our foundation without the support of resources."

The Western Desert Gu Immortals discussed, they wanted to retreat.

"Damn it, Fang clan took too long to develop, we do not have enough influence and authority." Fang Di Chang gritted his teeth, he watched as a portion of Sun clan and Mo clan left.

"The nature of these two clan's Gu Immortals is not so tough normally, I'm afraid Heavenly Court is involved with these two clans!" Fang Di Chang reacted at this time.

With the departure of a portion of Sun clan and Mo clan, the other clans also wanted to leave, otherwise, their balance would be disrupted.

Western Desert's Gu Immortal world had gone into chaos earlier because of the rise of Fang clan, their relationship was tense now and nobody trusted each other.

There was another fundamental problem, in history, Western Desert had never experienced any large scale cooperation between super forces.

Western Desert's Gu Immortal world did not have any domineering overlord in history, unlike Southern Border's Wu clan or Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven.

After some discussion, a portion of Western Desert's Gu Immortals returned to their base. The rest of them still exceeded the numbers in the previous life, they passed the regional walls and arrived in Central Continent.

Heavenly Court.

Reports of battles were sent over rapidly.

"Hidden Dragon Cave is attacked by Eastern Sea's rank eight Gu Immortals."

"Gu Immortal elites have appeared at Western Desert's fringe, they are heading towards Emperor City."

Fairy Zi Wei spoke.

At this time, Duke Long slowly retreated from the front of the battlefield.

Calamity Luck Altar was surrounded by the qi wall, there was a sizable area of movable space around it now, Heavenly Court's countless experts were attacking it from all directions.

If Calamity Luck Altar retaliated, these Gu Immortals would retreat into the qi wall and hide themselves, staying safe.

After several attempts, Bing Sai Chuan had to activate Calamity Luck Altar's defense as they pressed forward.

Because of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals' obstruction, Calamity Luck Altar could barely move forward slowly and with great difficulty.

Duke Long had nothing much to do, the battlefield in Heavenly Court was already secured, Longevity Heaven was trapped and they would eventually fall.

Duke Long heard Fairy Zi Wei's reports as he said calmly: "Qi Sea Ancestor and Fang Yuan, have they not made a move?"

"Nothing at the moment." Fairy Zi Wei shook her head.

The two people Duke Long was most wary of were these two. Qi Sea Ancestor had unparalleled strength, he rivaled Duke Long and was someone that Duke Long had to focus and keep his attention on.

Meanwhile, even though Fang Yuan had rank seven cultivation level, he inherited Red Lotus Demon Venerable's true inheritance, he might have some powerful method, he needed to be guarded against.

"Qi Sea Ancestor's attitude is unclear, meanwhile, ever since Fang Yuan snatched Southern Border's dream realms, he vanished. He has a lot of dream realms on his hands now." Fairy Zi Wei said slowly, she was going to analyze this further.

"What plan do you have?" Duke Long interrupted her.

Fairy Zi Wei said: "I plan to activate the formation and resist our external foes to force out Fang Yuan. There is also Qi Sea Ancestor who might possibly fight us, we need to force them to take action!"

Duke Long pondered before nodding: "Alright, we need to take the initiative. If we can establish our dominance in this battle, the five regions chaotic war will be much easier to deal with."

Fairy Zi Wei quickly left and sat down at the central area of a formation.

She activated the formation and released Star Constellation Chessboard. The chessboard floated in the air and rotated on its own, innumerable starlight specks that resembled fireflies flew in the sky, entering the formation.

Central Continent's people soon noticed a strange phenomenon.

Many pointed at the sky and screamed: "Quickly look! There is starlight, there are actually stars in bright daylight."

"What is going on?" Fang Di Chang had just crossed the regional wall when he saw such a scene.

"Heavenly Court took action. This did not happen in my previous life." Fang Yuan also arrived in Central Continent, he looked at the sky silently while frowning.

Heavenly Court had indeed prepared something new.

At this moment, in the sky of Central Continent, bright lights shined, stars appeared during daytime, radiating heaven and earth!

Chapter 1924: Flesh Whip Immortal

Central Continent, Hidden Dragon Cave.

"What is going on?" Eastern Sea's eight Gu Immortals saw the change in the sky.

In broad daylight, Central Continent's sky was covered in stars that shined brightly.

"This is likely Heavenly Court's method, but we do not know what effect it has." Qing Yue An frowned as he spoke.

"What is there to fear? We will deal with it when it comes, with our force, who can stop us? Unless Heavenly Court sends their main forces to face us." Yang Zi He laughed loudly.

"Indeed." Qing Yue An's frown eased a little.

In this situation, Heavenly Court focused on repairing fate Gu, Hidden Dragon Cave was just a small area at the corner of the big picture, if Heavenly Court sent their main forces here to resist Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals, they would be disregarding the bigger problems, it would be a terrible decision!

"Enter the formation, destroy this formation and release Di Zang Sheng, he will cause chaos in the world, we will then gain our opportunity." Yang Zi He encouraged them without acting suspicious.

"Hmm... let's wait for a while. Since we are going to take action, why the need to rush now?" Song Qi Yuan had a composed mentality: "Since Heavenly Court has already used their method, we need to at least find out what it does, right?"

Song Qi Yuan's words made the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals hesitant again.

Yang Zi He and the other Dragon Generals cursed in their hearts, these Eastern Sea righteous path rank eights were truly indecisive. They had already shown hostility to Heavenly Court but still did not want to destroy the formation immediately!

They were concerned about this ridiculous starry sky because they were too worried about their own safety. If they were Northern Plains' Gu Immortals, they would have entered the formation already. No wonder Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world had the most wealth but still stayed suppressed and unable to resist Gu Immortals of other regions.

Fang Yuan did not want these Gu Immortals to wait outside.

The Four Dragon Generals were enslaved by Dragon Palace, they were undoubtedly loyal.

Among them, Granny Rong smiled as she said: "If this method has just materialized and needs three days to take effect, are we going to wait three days here?"

"This..." Song Qi Yuan and the rest were uncertain.

But at this moment, from the sky, grand starlight pillars shot down rapidly.

The light pillars were shining in a bluish light, it was a grand sight.

More than ten pillars of light shot down together, encircling all eight Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

Next, the pillars faded away as a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal appeared in the location of each pillar.

The Eastern Sea immortals' expressions changed.

In an instant, they were surrounded by Heavenly Court, the situation took a turn for the worse!

"You crawling worms dare to offend Heavenly Court!" Zhang Fei Xiong said in a cold and domineering tone.

"You will die today." Wan Zi Hong licked her scarlet lips, oozing with killing intent.

"Those who offend Central Continent will be killed." Qin Song had a solemn expression.

"Enough talk, I'm going to attack now, yayaya!" A female Heavenly Court immortal could not wait anymore, she charged forward.

Her body was plump to its limit, she was like a meat cannonball that shot towards the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals fearlessly.

Eastern Sea's immortals were not united, they quickly split up.

The fat female immortal missed her target, she screamed in anger: "You cowards, why are you dodging, come, fight your mommy for three hundred rounds!"

"Flesh Whip Immortal is still so impatient." A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal who knew about this female immortal sighed helplessly.

"Flesh Whip Immortal is gentle and kind normally, but once she enters battle, she acts like what the rumors say." Many Heavenly Court Gu Immortals watched with surprise.

At once, the female immortal called Flesh Whip Immortal chased after Eastern Sea's eight Gu Immortals while shouting vulgarities non-stop, she was extremely noisy.

"Vile woman, don't be too arrogant." Qing Yue An could not take it, he turned around to battle.

Flesh Whip Immortal was overjoyed: "Someone finally stopped running!"

Boom!

The two used their killer moves that collided, causing a thunderous explosion.

A huge shock wave burst out and caused the surrounding clouds to disperse and change form.

"Quickly go and reinforce Little Whip." Qin Song ordered, among these Gu Immortals, he was the most senior, even Flesh Whip Immortal was his junior.

Central Continent's immortals all charged forward at once.

Among them, there was Zhu Que Er who cultivated fire path and transformation path. There was Vortex Space Boy who cultivated space path and had terrifying killer moves. There was Ye Qiao Zi, Z, Wu Shuang, Yu Zhu Zi, and others, they were all famous Heavenly Court experts in history.

Not only did Heavenly Court's side have more people, they even had excellent coordination, they created their battle tactic long ago, they erupted with great power.

Eastern Sea's eight Gu Immortals were forced back time and again, they could not hold their own.

"This is a trap, let's retreat!" Song Qi Yuan shouted with all his might.

His words immediately received the acceptance of the other three righteous path members, with the enemies being this strong now, they could not fight forcefully.

The Four Dragon Generals remained silent.

Without Fang Yuan's orders, they would not abruptly retreat.

Amidst the chaotic battle, Zhu Que Er suddenly pushed with her palm as a flame light was shot out.

The flame light resembled a beautiful blade light as it slashed towards Granny Rong.

Granny Rong and Zhao Shan He were currently fighting, seeing the approaching blade, she did not dodge it.

At the crucial moment, Zhang Yin suddenly moved, a shadow appeared and blocked the flame light.

"Oh? There's something weird going on with these two Gu Immortals." Zhu Que Er's expression changed, she felt something amiss.

Compared to the previous life, she had woken up much earlier, she made many preparations. She had already obtained information regarding Granny Rong and Zhang Yin.

These two were lone immortals but they actually trusted each other this much, it was really rare!

But soon, Zhu Que Er found out that it was not only Zhang Yin and Granny Rong, Yang Zi He and Shi Miao were also weird, these four rank eights trusted each other completely, they were willing to let themselves be defended by one another in dangerous situations!

Because of their coordination, they were able to resist the attacks of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals without losing.

Fairy Zi Wei was currently looking at the situation from her formation core in Central Hall.

Starlight flashed in front of her, displaying the scene in Hidden Dragon Cave.

Even though she was in Heavenly Court, she obtained firsthand information of the battlefield.

"What's wrong with these four Eastern Sea lone immortals? Their relationship should not be this close. Unless they set some sort of strict alliance agreement that allowed them to work together with complete trust?"

Fairy Zi Wei could not think more, it was not the time to deduce this now.

She considered it for a while before giving her orders.

After getting her orders, Old Man Bei Feng who was inside Hidden Dragon Cave became revitalized, he quickly activated the formation.

Intense lights appeared around the formation, its power spread out across the battlefield.

"Oh no!"

"Quickly leave!!"

"Once we enter the formation, they will take us out one by one."

Eastern Sea's immortals were flustered, they quickly shouted.

But how could Heavenly Court's rank eight Gu Immortals allow them to leave? Immediately, killer moves were used to obstruct the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, they could not get out, they were swept into the formation along with the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Both parties entered Hidden Dragon Cave's formation.

Old Man Bei Feng, who was controlling the formation, grunted as his face turned pale, blood flowed out of his nostrils.

Even though Hidden Dragon Cave's formation was powerful, taking in so many rank eight Gu Immortals at once was beyond Old Man Bei Feng's limits.

"Grandfather, are you okay?" Feng Chan Zi who was at the side asked with concern.

He was Old Man Bei Feng's beloved grandson, if he did not make a mistake and was forced to guard Hidden Dragon Cave along with his grandfather, Old Man Bei Feng would have become a member of Heavenly Court already.

"But if I can make some contributions in this battle, Heavenly Court might recruit me!" Old Man Bei Feng's eyes shined with bright light, he was filled with morale.

Eastern Sea's rank eights were trapped in the formation, they were split up.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were also split up into different areas.

"This formation is mainly used to suppress and seal Di Zang Sheng, it does not have any power to cooperate with Gu Immortals in battle. Every Gu Immortal that enters the formation will be sent to a different area. Unless the formation is destroyed, there will not be two Gu Immortals in the same area."

Fairy Zi Wei knew about Hidden Dragon Cave's formation, she ordered Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals to retreat.

While Eastern Sea's immortals were trapped inside.

"I will leave this place to you." Qin Song said before leaving.

"Don't worry, I will guard this place with my life. If anything happens, I will report it and seek reinforcements." Old Man Bei Feng said with a polite and serious attitude.

"Very good." Qin Song felt assured as he brought the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to leave.

At this time, more than ten pillars of light shot down again, the blue starlight pillars enveloped all the Heavenly Court rank eights.

The pillars vanished, along with the rank eight Gu Immortals within.

Fang Di Chang and the rest traveled in their Immortal Gu House as they rushed towards Emperor City.

Even though the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was disrupted by Fang Yuan in advance in this life and had slower progress than the previous life, it was not even at the final round of the competition yet.

But evidently, Emperor City was the only place that could protect them while not interfering with the Gu refinement and the restoration of fate Gu. That place was already heavily guarded by Heavenly Court, Fang Di Chang thus asked the Western Desert immortals to head to Emperor City.

Western Desert's immortals had surging morale.

But at the next moment, starlight pillars appeared again, as more than ten Heavenly Court Gu Immortals appeared.

"Kill!" Flesh Whip Immortal charged forward again.

But this time, Western Desert's Gu Immortals were not flustered.

They were within their Immortal Gu Houses, they felt very safe.

Watching as Flesh Whip Immortal attacked, even though she was a rank eight Gu Immortal, she could not destroy an Immortal Gu House instantly.

"What method is Heavenly Court using? They could transport so many rank eights at the same time!" Fang Di Chang did not think anymore, he mobilized several Immortal Gu Houses to resist the enemies.

As a wisdom path Gu Immortal who controlled the strongest Immortal Gu House Divine Bean Palace, he was selected as the leader of the group, he had the highest authority.

Immortal Gu Houses charged without care, it was Heavenly Court's time to dodge them.

But two Gu Immortals did not retreat.

One was Zhang Fei Xiong, he turned into a giant with a bear head and human body, he resisted Immortal Gu Houses with his body.

The other was Flesh Whip Immortal, she was a transformation path Gu Immortal, she transformed into a walking meat tree as her roots moved like legs, running rapidly, while her branches turned into countless whips that attacked in a frenzy.

Crack crack crack!

She was also resisting Immortal Gu Houses, several rank seven Immortal Gu Houses were forced to turn around and escape.

Within Divine Bean Palace, Fang Di Chang's expression was dark.

"Heavenly Court made changes, but this change is simply too huge."

"Zhang Fei Xiong, Wan Zi Hong, and Zhu Que Er woke up in advance, even experts like Flesh Whip Immortal appeared."

"And most importantly, what killer move is this? It can transport more than ten rank eight Gu Immortals at once! This is simply unheard of!"

With this move, Heavenly Court had the initiative to mobilize their main forces to attack anywhere they wanted.

This was a very significant trump card in battle.

As long as this move was not destroyed, Heavenly Court could fight in several battlefields at the same time, they could deal with anything that came at them.

Chapter 1925: Heavenly Court's Initiative

Crack crack crack!

The tower-like walking meat tree was charging at the forefront, thousands of octopus tentacle-like branches waved and created a sound of fierce wind whistling, they had awe inspiring might, the Western Desert Gu Immortal's Immortal Gu Houses were forced to retreat.

Flesh Whip Immortal was able to resist Immortal Gu Houses singlehandedly, she was truly a rank eight expert slumbering in the Heavenly Court immortal graveyard, her strength was unquestionable!

Of course, this was also the advantage of transformation path.

"Let us!" At the crucial moment, Dong clan's Gu Immortals spoke up.

Similar to the previous life, Dong clan still mobilized the rank seven Immortal Gu House Red River Wheel.

This Immortal Gu House looked like a water wheel or a giant tire, rotating while blazing with red flames, it crashed towards the walking meat tree.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals saw this and their gazes focused.

Immortal Gu Houses charged head on because it was the fastest method, it was usually not their strongest ability.

According to the different types of Immortal Gu used to construct them, Immortal Gu Houses had different immortal killer moves.

Right now, Red River Wheel had used its own killer move with overwhelming might to attack Flesh Whip Immortal.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were nervous, similarly, Western Desert's Gu Immortals were also nervous.

Red River Wheel was only a rank seven Immortal Gu House, it could resist rank eight, if it crashed into Flesh Whip Immortal, they would be evenly matched, it would be damaged too.

However, this result was still slightly favorable to Western Desert.

Even if both of them were harmed, Red River Wheel would be able to recover by replacing the dead Gu. Flesh Whip Immortal, however, would be physically injured, and subsequent healing and recovery would be quite troubling.

"Come!" At the crucial moment, Flesh Whip Immortal, instead of retreating, yelled in excitement and charged straight up.

"This person..."

"Defend her!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals reached a consensus in an instant.

Zhang Fei Xiong growled again, he turned into a giant with a bear head and human body, charging towards Red River Wheel.

"Red River Wheel is strongest at the front and back, but the sides are the weakest. Let's help out Dong clan!" Immortal Gu House Jade Toad Castle was like a green meteor that crashed into Zhang Fei Xiong.

Wan Zi Hong smiled delicately as countless petals drifted over the battlefield and landed on Red River Wheel, its momentum continued to decline.

Fang clan's Chicken Dog Coop came over to support, releasing chickens and dogs and other ancient desolate beasts to attack Wan Zi Hong.

Wan Zi Hong was still maintaining her killer moves and had no time to dodge, so Yu Zhu Zi and Ye Qiao Zi appeared around her. One of them sprinkled countless jade beads and made a tinkling sound, while the other emitted a mass of yellow light, sometimes slow, sometimes fast.

Chickens, dogs, and many other ancient desolate beasts were either smashed to death by the jade beads, or were temporarily trapped by the yellow light, hovering high in the air, unable to move.

"Damn it, this Wan Zi Hong is the demoness who scourged Western Desert in history and was recruited by Heavenly Court!" Dong clan's Gu Immortals were inside Red River Wheel, looking at Wan Zi Hong and gnashing their teeth.

Dong clan was a Western Desert righteous path force and hated Western Desert's demons the most, while this Wan Zi Hong was one of the most infamous demonesses in history.

Seeing the Dong clan's Red River Wheel's power was weakening, at this rate, it would be crushed by the walking meat tree. At the critical moment, a forest flower house-like Immortal Gu House was exerting its power behind the battlefield.

Wan Zi Hong gave a soft cry as she suddenly felt her killer move go out of control, countless petals rolled towards Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals instead.

Wan Zi Hong muffled a grunt as her killer move failed and the backlash caused her to suffer considerable damage.

Her eyes were like lightning as she stared at the culprit, it was Fang clan's rank seven Immortal Gu House — Fallen Flower Hall.

Boom!

At the next moment, the walking meat tree and Red River Wheel finally collided together.

Both sides immediately flew backwards.

The walking meat tree had hundreds of severed fleshy tentacles, while the surface of the Red River Wheel's wheel was battered beyond recognition, losing over three thousand Gu, Dong clan's Gu Immortals quickly started to repair it.

"This... is really satisfying!" Flesh Whip Immortal gritted her teeth and struggled to maintain the form of the walking meat tree, although her injuries were not light, her fighting spirit was instead more vigorous.

She was about to charge up again, but was stopped by Zhang Fei Xiong.

"Let me fight, you should go back and heal your injuries." Zhang Fei Xiong had been knocked away by the Immortal Gu House earlier, he returned and immediately took the place of Flesh Whip Immortal.

Flesh Whip Immortal, however, was stubborn and would not retreat in a deadly battle: "I won't! Let me charge, no one can stop me."

As soon as the words were said, a giant pillar of starlight shot down violently overhead, covering Flesh Whip Immortal.

Flesh Whip Immortal: "..."

In the next instant, she disappeared together with the giant pillar of starlight and returned to Heavenly Court.

In Heavenly Court's battlefield, Calamity Luck Altar was still struggling to move forward, trying to break free from the qi wall, but Duke Long was firmly blocking in front of it.

Duke Long's tall body was like cast steel, and even if it was just one man, Calamity Luck Altar could not deal with him.

Boom boom boom!

Every time Duke Long attacked, it was accompanied by a fierce explosion, and just by using transformation path killer moves, Calamity Luck Altar could not move forward.

After advancing ten steps, it would often be knocked back nine steps by Duke Long.

Flesh Whip Immortal swallowed a mouthful of saliva, gazing up at the heroic fighting stance of Duke Long, feeling envious in her heart, when would she have such powerful strength!

Light flickered around her, pale blue strands of flowing water wrapped around her, washing the dao marks away to heal her wounds.

This was a healing formation specially set up by Heavenly Court to greatly improve the efficiency of healing injuries.

"Heavenly Court's teleportation method can move groups as well as a single person to and fro! This is really troublesome." Fang Yuan's clone, Fang Di Chang, frowned deeply.

Although he could not see the healing formation in Heavenly Court, he could deduce it easily with his brain.

The key was that with such a method, Heavenly Court could quickly retreat. It was almost an extravagant hope for Western Desert's side to kill or injure the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals. They had to kill with a single blow, denying Heavenly Court any chance to teleport and heal their members.

But how difficult was it to kill such experts among rank eight!

It was not just Fang Di Chang, the vast majority of the Gu Immortals recognized this, the morale of the Western Desert immortals began to plummet.

Fang Di Chang secretly gritted his teeth: "This is not good."

Immediately, he activated Divine Bean Palace to move to the front line: "Everyone, let me do it!"

The Western Desert Immortals were energized greatly, they hurriedly made way for Divine Bean Palace, casting expectant glances at it.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals saw an Immortal Gu House lofty as a mountain, majestic and imposing, rumbling and rushing as it attacked, all their hearts jumped.

The same name flashed in the hearts of the immortals — Divine Bean Palace!

Immortal killer move — Myriad Life Spring Lightning!

Divine Bean Palace shook intensely, countless sparks that resembled dragons or snakes coiled around the palace. Lightning gathered into beads of jade green lightning balls as they exploded around the palace.

Rumble...

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals dodged wildly, not daring to face the attack. Even transformation path Zhang Fei Xiong had reverted to his human body, flying around in a very sad state.

Myriad life spring lightning, life and death was interlinked, destruction and creation were gathered into one move. After exploding, dao marks would be left in the battlefield, creating an environment that was advantageous to the user.

"How can we fight this?" This time, it was the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals' turn to feel helpless.

"It is, after all, an Immortal Gu House created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable himself."

"Sigh, how did it end up in the hands of Western Desert's Gu Immortals!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were resentful and without options, all of them were thinking of retreating.

One of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals was pale and chubby, he was Zhao Shan He, who was now looking at Yu Zhu Zi.

Yu Zhu Zi nodded at him as they suddenly gathered together.

At the same time, the other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were surrounding the two of them, planning and defending around them.

Zhao Shan He was a food path Gu Immortal and Yu Zhu Zi was earth path, they both unleashed a move together — Sitting and Eating the Mountain Empty!

The killer move enveloped the entire battlefield, Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses could not dodge it.

After it was used, starlight pillars flashed in the sky for an instant.

At the next moment, all of the Heavenly Court rank eights left the battlefield, the intense and chaotic battle was left with only Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses.

Even though Western Desert's Gu Immortals forced back Heavenly Court, their expressions turned ugly.

Because they found out that many of the Gu worms in the Immortal Gu Houses were weakening, soon, their aura fell to rock bottom as Gu worms died one by one.

Not only that, the Gu Immortals in the houses were also getting hit, many of their immortal essence beads started to disintegrate and disappear.

"This was all caused by that move."

"What kind of killer move was it, not only did the Immortal Gu Houses get affected, but even the Gu Immortals inside the houses were not spared?"

"This should be the profundity of food path. Because of that, it's hard to defend against using our Immortal Gu Houses."

The Western Desert Gu Immortals discussed and exchanged ideas, they soon guessed correctly.

Food path had been too limited in circulation, Western Desert's righteous path did not have a lot of food path inheritances, their defense against it was too low, it was a weakness.

And most importantly, Zhao Shan He was a food path expert on Heavenly Court's side.

"This will not do!"

"Heavenly Court fights and retreats when they want to, as long as they give Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi the chance to use this move each time, we will lose all our strength and resources over time."

"Everyone! We must hurry up and rush to Emperor City as soon as possible to force Heavenly Court to fight us to the death. There, they won't retreat so easily."

Fang Di Chang analyzed the situation and advocated.

The Western Desert Gu Immortals agreed.

In a short period of time, they had no way to counter Heavenly Court's teleportation killer move and could only use this method to restrain Heavenly Court.

Zhao Shan He and the others returned to Heavenly Court once again.

The injured ones all went to the healing formation to recover, while the rest were focusing on their recuperation while communicating with each other on how they should work better together.

After a fierce battle with Western Desert's various Immortal Gu Houses, these Gu Immortals suffered no losses, and the most seriously injured person, Flesh Whip Immortal, was almost healed completely, alive and well once again.

Unlike the previous life, these Gu Immortals, because of their early awakening, not only possessed a full range of Immortal Gu, but they also had a certain level of mutual cooperation.

"Immortal Gu Houses are just hard to fight. Divine Bean Palace is the most troublesome of them all."

"What are you worried about? A few more rounds and Western Desert's side will collapse. They won't be able to reach Emperor City!"

"Have Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor not done anything? Quickly do something, we can't wait anymore."

Gu Immortals were all experts that had huge reputation at some point in time, they were overflowing with confidence and morale.

The truth was, Fang Yuan was the one who caused this situation.

Since rebirth, Fang Yuan had been gaining victories over Heavenly Court multiple times, Star Constellation's will felt a huge threat from this and awakened many Gu Immortals in advance.

It was unlike the previous life when Longevity Heaven attacked, in which Heavenly Court had fallen into a crisis and had to awaken many Gu Immortals in a hurry, they were unable to display their true battle strength.

Chapter 1926: Northern Plains' Retaliation

"Quickly stop them!" Fang Di Chang shouted.

Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses tried their best to stop Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi.

But in front of them, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were putting up a tight defense.

Roar!

Zhang Fei Xiong turned into a giant, obstructing an Immortal Gu House relentlessly.

Crack crack crack!

Flesh Whip Immortal turned into an immemorial walking meat tree, she waved her branches and whipped at the Immortal Gu Houses, they were knocked about and spinning around all over the place.

Bam bam bam...

All kinds of immortal killer moves erupted, as if they were large bursts of fireworks, incomparably splendid and powerful.

These were all rank eight killer moves of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, the Immortal Gu Houses of Western Desert suffered a serious obstruction, inevitably hesitating.

Taking advantage of this time, Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi finished their preparation and unleashed their immortal killer move, sitting and eating the mountain empty.

Western Desert's Gu Immortals were hit again, they then helplessly watched as a giant pillar of starlight shot down, teleporting away the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

At the next moment, they returned to Heavenly Court.

As the Gu Immortals healed their wounds, they exchanged conversations.

"It's really getting harder and harder to use the killer move, sitting and eating the mountain empty."

"After all, the other side has elites of an entire region, so they cannot be underestimated. As the saying goes, if a fool suffers sufficient losses, he will become wiser."

"But their strength has also been weakened quite badly, so they probably won't be able to hold out after two more times."

The Gu Immortals were full of morale, and the more they fought, the higher their spirits became.

Guh.

At this moment, Qin Song's face turned pale and he coughed out a small mouthful of blood.

His blood was yellowish brown, and there were countless small insects jumping around in the blood foam.

"Senior Qin, are you injured?" Zhou Xiong Xin, who was standing right next to Qin Song, asked with concern.

Zhou Xiong Xin was dressed in a white robe, he had a strong physique and a squarish face with thick eyebrows. In his last battle with Fang Yuan, he activated the fastest battlefield killer move in the world, rumor cage, and once caused Fang Yuan to fall into a dangerous battle. In the end, Fang Yuan was even more calculating and used the arrangements left by the organization Defy to plot and kill Zhou Xiong Xin.

But this time, Fang Yuan was reborn, Zhou Xiong Xin was thus alive and one of the many Gu Immortals that fought along with Heavenly Court.

Qin Song weakly shook his head: "This is an old injury, it is not from the fight earlier."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals all gathered around to check on Qin Song's state, even Fairy Zi Wei came here.

Qin Song was the key person now.

The reason why Heavenly Court was able to display such a powerful star cast killer move was not only with the help of the related formation and Star Constellation Chessboard, but also relying on Qin Song's strength.

Qin Song was most skilled at teleportation.

In the previous life, he was the one who brought the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals on a long journey to quickly make their way to Di Zang Sheng. At that time, he did not have his complete set of Immortal Gu, he used killer moves without caring about his own condition, causing him to die prematurely.

This life, however, he had awakened earlier, the situation was much better. Not only were his Immortal Gu comprehensive, he also got to use an advanced lifespan extension method.

Qin Song's seniority was very high, he had gone into hibernation long ago. During his hibernation, Heavenly Court had many new findings and improvement in their research on lifespan extension methods.

As time passed, there were bound to be improvements.

As a result, Qin Song's lifespan was extended to a certain extent, but the repeated battles made him repeatedly exert himself, and his health declined rapidly. His lifespan was greatly reduced.

"Based on your current physical state, I'm afraid you can only use four movement killer moves at most. Beyond that number, your flesh and soul will all collapse." Fairy Zi Wei calculated for a moment and spoke.

"Four times?" Qin Song smiled and coughed out another mouthful of yellow blood with a calm demeanor: "It is enough to defeat Western Desert, and there's still room to spare, so maybe we can deal a blow to Southern Border as well! Or maybe Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals. As for after my death, it will be up to all of you."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were silent.

Only Flesh Whip Immortal grinned: "Don't worry, Old Man Qin, I'm here."

There was nothing they could do about Qin Song's state. The cause behind all of this was his old injury, an injury that he had brought with him from exploring Reckless Savage's grave, it could not be treated in the past, and now it was still fatal.

Fairy Zi Wei, however, did not order a further attack, she was pondering in her head.

Without Qin Song, Heavenly Court would not have the ability to teleport in groups. Relying on Star Constellation Chessboard alone would be too inefficient and it would seriously reduce her own ability to deduce and calculate.

Fairy Zi Wei had experience in using star cast, this killer move consumed too many thoughts. If she had to use this killer move, she would no longer have the extra energy to look over the big picture.

This was clearly not worth it for Heavenly Court.

It would be fine if it was just one battlefield, but Heavenly Court was fighting in at least three battlefields, they were facing not only the powerful elites of the four regions, there was still Fang Yuan, the demon who had yet to do anything.

As the leader and strategist of Heavenly Court in both the previous life and this life, Fairy Zi Wei had to oversee the whole situation.

"What a pity, there is no wisdom path Gu Immortal awakening in the immortal graveyard this time."

"Fang Yuan has yet to make a move, and Qi Sea Ancestor has made no movements either. If we waste Qin Song early at this time, it will be bad if there is a sudden change in the battle in the future."

Fairy Zi Wei pondered deeply, unwilling to expend a key force like Qin Song in advance.

She always considered one thing: Fang Yuan possessed a killer move using Fixed Immortal Travel, as well as the ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel, he could quickly appear in any place in Central Continent.

If Heavenly Court preserved the remaining uses of their star cast method, when they deal with Fang Yuan in the future, it would be much easier.

"Right now, we have four battlefields, they are in Heavenly Court, Hairy Foot Mountain, Emperor City, and Hidden Dragon Cave." Fairy Zi Wei looked around, analyzing as she spoke.

"Of these four battlefields, Heavenly Court's battlefield is the most important. Once we are breached and fate Gu gets destroyed by Longevity Heaven, all hope is lost."

"The second most important is Hairy Foot Mountain. If Infallible blessed land is destroyed and we don't refine enough success dao marks, it will have a huge impact on our ability to repair Fate. However, this is not irrevocable. Even if the Infallible blessed land is destroyed and we don't have enough success dao marks, fate Gu would still be alive. In the future, with new developments in refinement path, we might be able to find other ways to repair fate Gu."

"After that is Emperor City. The Western Desert immortals are moving with their forces aimed straight at Emperor City. But after our repeated strikes, their vigor has been lost. Emperor City itself is already heavily guarded and defended by human path methods left by venerables. Even if it is destroyed and the elites are all dead, it is not very important. In a hundred years, more elites will emerge."

"Finally, there is Hidden Dragon Cave. Although there are many Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals, they are not looking to kill and only want to seek gains. The formation and Old Man Bei Feng alone won't be able to defend against them, but delaying them for a while is more than enough. During this period of time, we only needed to support them once to stabilize the situation over there."

A Gu Immortal asked: "So, what is your decision?"

Fairy Zi Wei cast her gaze towards Calamity Luck Altar in the qi wall: "Let's take care of Longevity Heaven first! With Heavenly Court secure and fate Gu safe, even if the situation outside is completely lost, we will always be in an impregnable position."

After a pause, she continued: "In addition to that, it will also allow Senior Qin Song to preserve his health, preventing Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor from suddenly making a move ."

"Great!"

"These are truly the words of a great strategist."

"I'm also feeling uneasy about trapping Calamity Luck Altar in our headquarters. After all, they are the descendants of Giant Sun, so they might unleash a surprising attack anytime."

"We will listen to you!"

After listening carefully, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals all approved of this plan.

As a result, the immortals stopped attacking at a long range, they entered the qi wall and fought Longevity Heaven fiercely.

The qi wall in Heavenly Court was left behind by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable. After so many years, except for the three paths that were opened by the three venerables, the rest of the qi wall was still strong and enduring.

And even worse was that the qi wall still retained its autonomous abilities.

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were allowed to move freely in it, while Longevity Heaven's Gu Immortals were restricted by a strong force.

There was a hemispherical battlefield in the qi wall, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals bombarded Calamity Luck Altar with a barrage of attacks with their backs against the wall.

Once Calamity Luck Altar retaliates, these Gu Immortals would rapidly retreat, entering the qi wall and using it to block Calamity Luck Altar's attack.

Because of this, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were able to attack with their full strength, Calamity Luck Altar's surface was filled with cracks.

As an rank eight Immortal Gu House, Calamity Luck Altar itself was extremely sturdy, and it was created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable himself, so it had a clear advantage in charging. It was simply unreasonable.

But all along, it was always obstructed by a Gu Immortal.

This person was Duke Long!

His body was slowly growing minute by minute, his face was like iron, his body was robust, and the defense of violet-gold dragon scales all over his body was extremely amazing.

Transformation path killer moves were being unleashed as he desired. The moves were domineering and fierce, blocking Calamity Luck Altar firmly.

Be they Calamity Luck Altar or killer moves of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals that he was in range of, he held firm, as if he was a pillar of heaven, all of the rank eight killer moves felt like just a light breeze.

In the previous life, Duke Long and the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals fought for Dragon Palace, and although he succeeded, he was seriously injured. By the time the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was held, Duke Long was still injured, so his performance in battle was not so shocking at the start.

In this life, because Fang Yuan had obtained Dragon Palace in advance, Duke Long was in a fully intact state and could attack Calamity Luck Altar to the point where it could not inch forward.

"Duke Long... is actually so strong!" Bing Sai Chuan was livid.

The accompanying Bull Demon, Flower Lady, and Five Elements Grandmaster were all desperately trying their best to repair Calamity Luck Altar.

"This won't work. Without breaking through the barrier in front of us, we won't be able to get close to Heaven Overseeing Tower." In Calamity Luck Altar, Mao Li Qiu lay down on the ground, yelling out in dissatisfaction.

Bing Sai Chuan struggled for a while internally before he sighed: "There is no other way, activate the killer move call of the ancient."

Calamity Luck Altar suddenly stood still and abruptly exploded with a round of golden light.

The light was so dazzling that it caused Duke Long to squint his eyes.

Swish swish swish...

The sound of river waves surging through the battlefield resounded.

The phantom image of a segment of the grand River of Time appeared above Calamity Luck Altar.

"This is?!" Duke Long's heart was slightly shaken.

Then, following the astonished eyes of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, Northern Plains' Gu Immortals walked out of the phantom River of Time one by one.

"Come on, eat one of my explosive lightning bolts!" The tall-bodied Nu Er Bao Xiong laughed wildly.

"To think that I can use this move to come to the future and participate in a huge battle, I am truly fortunate." Hei Fan had a slight smile.

"Wow! What a huge battle, oh heavens, I better hide somewhere." Liu Liu Liu had a delicate white face, he had a crafty look as his body vanished on the spot.

Chapter 1927: Asking Fang Yuan for Reinforcements

"What happened?"

"These are all historically famous experts from Northern Plains, they've actually been summoned here!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were all surprised.

Duke Long said in a deep voice: "Attention everyone, this is Red Lotus Demon Venerable's time path killer move, call of the ancient. It can summon closely related Gu Immortals from the upstream of the River of Time to the present to fight for the user!"

"That's interesting." Flesh Whip Immortal licked her lips, her fighting spirit surging as she rushed up.

"Let me do it." Zhang Fei Xiong transformed into a giant, together with Flesh Whip Immortal, they crashed into Calamity Luck Altar from the left and right.

But at this time, Calamity Luck Altar was already guarded.

Nu Er Bao Xiong roared wildly and used his immortal killer move, lightning balls flew everywhere, exploding fiercely.

For a moment, Flesh Whip Immortal and Zhang Fei Xiong were both blocked by the lightning balls, their attacks were thwarted.

Zhu Que Er squealed and used her movement killer move, drawing a bright and stunning red trail of light through the air and circling behind Calamity Luck Altar.

"Don't even think about it." A male immortal stepped out of the phantom River of Time to block Zhu Que Er.

He had a handsome face like jade, graceful and dashing, his gaze carried a faint smile, it was Dong Fang Yu.

Boom boom boom!

Zhu Que Er and Dong Fang Yu fought a fierce battle.

Immortal killer move — Sitting and Eating the Mountain Empty!

In the distance, Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi joined forces once again and successfully activated the killer move.

The killer move worked on Calamity Luck Altar with very little effect. Calamity Luck Altar was worthy of being created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, its defense against food path was quite strong.

Ye Qiao Zi's killer moves followed one after another. Wooden stakes were created out of thin air, forming a circle to trap Calamity Luck Altar.

Ye Qiao Zi grunted in a low tone again, and countless bright green vines grew from the wooden stakes, wrapping around Calamity Luck Altar and spreading upwards in an attempt to stain the phantom River of Time.

"It's useless. This phantom River of Time cannot be attacked, only by defeating Calamity Luck Altar which is sustaining it can we put an end to this move." Duke Long was about to make a move.

But another Heavenly Court Gu Immortal suddenly teleported towards the phantom River of Time.

This Gu Immortal resembled a child with black hair, he had a small cowlick on the top of his head, his face was round and cute. It was none other than Vortex Space Boy.

His aura surged as a huge vortex appeared above it had, it had an immense suction force that destroyed anything that got drawn into it.

But the phantom River of Time remained unmoved, completely unaffected.

Another newly appeared Northern Plains Gu Immortal had just walked out, he could not react in time before the vortex sucked him in.

"Hahaha, at least I had some gains." Vortex Space Boy laughed as he exerted even more force.

Nian Er tribe's expert was trapped inside — Nian Er Nong Fu.

He looked like an old farmer, his pants were rolled up, his legs were covered in mud, his back was hunched, wrinkles covered his face.

Trapped at this moment, he sighed: "Oh my, I'm going to die in battle as soon as I get out. Seriously? Of all the Northern Plains Gu Immortals, I'm the least proficient at fighting."

The small face of Vortex Space Boy puffed up as he did his best to grind and crush Nian Er Nong Fu.

Nian Er Nong Fu was guarded by a pale yellow halo of light, it was thin but very strong, firmly resisting the crazy force of the spinning vortex.

Another Gu Immortal came out from the illusory River of Time, seeing that Nian Er Nong Fu was trapped, he was about to rescue him.

However, Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Zhou Xiong Xin also arrived in time to stop the man.

Ye Lui Kou also came out, his skin was dark and his eyes were like a falcon, scanning the battlefield, he suddenly found the weakest Gu Immortal in Heavenly Court, Qin Song.

Qin Song's weakened state was hard to conceal.

Ye Lui Kou sneered and attacked Qin Song straight away.

"Your opponent is me." A beautiful female immortal intercepted Ye Lui Kou while he was on his way.

Ye Lui Kou gazed at the female immortal, feeling a certain threat to his life: "Who are you?"

The female immortal smiled fawningly, but her words were murderous: "Your killer — Wan Zi Hong!"

As the two fought, golden light flashed and petals flew.

Figures flew in the sky or fought on the ground.

Intense explosions continued to resound, sparks were flying, bright lights were flashing.

Northern Plains' Gu Immortal experts fought against Heavenly Court's members.

Rumble!

Zhang Fei Xiong's flesh was torn by Nu Er Bao Xiong's explosions.

Crack crack crack!

Flesh Whip Immortal smacked Yuan Ben so hard that the white bone armor Yuan Ben was wearing got smashed to pieces, he was forced to retreat.

Nian Er Nong Fu was still resisting, while Vortex Space Boy was gritting his teeth, refusing to give up.

Surrounding the two who were deadlocked in battle, several Gu Immortals were also engaged in a fight.

The Gu Immortals were all beginning to suffer injuries, the air was filled with the thick smell of blood.

"Even though I used the killer move, call of the ancient, I am actually being pressured!" Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth, his heart growing heavier.

The trump card he had pinned his hopes on did not turn the tables around, it only saved him from defeat and deadlocked the situation.

In the previous life, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had awakened hastily from the immortal graveyard, and despite the emergency deployment of the Immortal Gu by Fairy Zi Wei, their battle strength was still crippled.

But this life was different, these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had great battle strength and were in good condition, enough to fight with the strong Northern Plains and even suppress them. After all, there had been a lot of cooperation between the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, while Northern Plains' historically powerful experts had just been summoned, they had heard of each other at most, in their own lives, how could they have worked together?

"This can't continue. The longer call of the ancient lasts, the more experts it will continue to summon into battle." Fairy Zi Wei frowned, feeling both worried and glad.

Thankfully, she had placed priority on dealing with Longevity Heaven, this killer move was really troublesome. If they had used star cast earlier, the loss of Qin Song and the scattering of Heavenly Court's experts would likely allow Longevity Heaven to succeed and rush out of the qi wall.

After all, there were few Gu Immortals left in Heavenly Court, and Yuan Qiong Du and the others had to preside over the refinement path Gu formation, the only main force that could block Calamity Luck Altar was Duke Long.

Duke Long gazed at the phantom River of Time for a while, before slowly withdrawing his gaze.

He sighed in his heart, he could not unravel this killer move, it was like how he could not deal with the 'support of the future' killer move that Red Lotus Demon Venerable used back then.

"If it can't be broken directly, then all we need to do is to demolish Calamity Luck Altar." Thinking of this, Duke Long slowly clenched his fists and stepped into the battlefield.

Ye Qiao Zi suddenly coughed blood, the killer move backlash caused him to suffer heavy injuries.

He had been cooperating with Duke Long to investigate and restrain Calamity Luck Altar. But how could the rank eight Immortal Gu House be so easily restrained?

Ye Qiao Zi had to retreat into the qi wall, while Calamity Luck Altar stirred, trying to break through the qi wall.

Duke Long silently approached Calamity Luck Altar.

"Block him!" Bing Sai Chuan ordered coldly.

He was someone from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's generation, while most of the experts of Northern Plains were descendants of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, so they naturally listened to him.

Nu Er Bao Xiong was the first to strike, hundreds of lightning balls smashed towards Duke Long.

Boom boom boom!

With a series of deafening explosions, smoke and dust rose, Nu Er Bao Xiong laughed wildly: "Have you tasted my power yet? Hahaha... uh."

A figure gradually walked out of the smoke and dust.

Duke Long's face was indifferent, his body as straight as a spear, his violet-gold dragon scales still gleaming, leaving only a trace of ash at most.

Nu Er Bao Xiong was furious, he stared with glaring eyes, his aura soaring wildly: "Take this move from me again!"

He held his hands above his head and countless thunderbolts gathered into a huge deep blue lightning ball.

The surface of the lightning ball was lingering with electricity, but inside it was dark and deep, Nu Er Bao Xiong threw it like a meteor shooting towards Duke Long.

Duke Long was finally willing to avert his gaze, but only gave a glance at the lightning ball.

He waved his hand.

Rumble!

The air currents soared, forming a big hand, and with a slap on the back of his hand, the lightning ball was sent flying far away with ease.

Nu Er Bao Xiong's powerful killer move was thus dealt with by Duke Long.

At the next moment, Yu Yang Zi, Liu Hui, and Liu Liu Liu attacked one after another, while Duke Long went straight to Calamity Luck Altar without looking at them.

Only by destroying Calamity Luck Altar would call of the ancient be stopped!

Boom!

Calamity Luck Altar was punched by Duke Long and sunk into the ground.

A fist crater appeared on the surface of the Immortal Gu House, a large number of Gu worms died in battle, even the Immortal Gu were damaged.

The killer moves of the Northern Plains experts seemed like a downpour of rain, drowning Duke Long.

But after the continuous bombardment, Duke Long was still standing, only a light layer of soot was added on his face.

"How is this possible?"

"How can this person be so strong!"

"He is Duke Long, the master of Red Lotus Demon Venerable!"

Someone identified Duke Long as the Gu Immortals of Northern Plains drew a sharp breath of cold air.

He was an old monster!

But at the next moment, the morale of the people of Northern Plains soared again. They had a brave nature, the stronger Duke Long was, the more excited they became.

"Kill! Kill! Kill!"

"Decapitate this old fellow!"

"Protect Calamity Luck Altar and break out of the qi wall."

The Northern Plains Gu Immortals roared wildly, fighting to break out and setting off a flurry of attacks.

"These Northern Plains lunatics!"

"Hmph, brutish cavemen."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had to retreat and back off for a while.

Faced with the relentless spirit of Northern Plains' Gu Immortals to fight to the death, Duke Long could not continue to ignore it this time.

He snorted lightly: "Annoying pests."

As soon as his words fell, the aura around him changed.

Qi currents rushed and spread everywhere, while Duke Long's body became firm like a mountain, his aura soared rapidly.

The killer move was prepared as Duke Long waved his hand.

Whoosh—!

Air was forcefully pushed aside, five grand qi waves flew forward overbearingly.

Everywhere they went, the killer moves of Northern Plains' experts broke apart like paper, they could not stop the qi waves.

It was immortal killer move — Qi Current Scissors!

Duke Long extended his hand to the sky and pointed.

Immortal killer move — Qi Breath Mountain.

Rumble!

A huge translucent mountain created from qi currents descended and pressed down immediately.

The Northern Plains Gu Immortals wanted to escape, but several of them could not dodge, they were pushed down by the qi breath mountain as it crashed towards Calamity Luck Altar, turning into meat paste on the spot.

The entire mountain of qi currents pressed down on Calamity Luck Altar so hard that the ground was shaking violently.

Calamity Luck Altar was originally ready to attack, but now, it was immobilized.

Duke Long unleashed two moves in a row, the effect was immediate, he suppressed the entire battle.

Bing Sai Chuan's expression was livid, his heart sank to rock bottom. He now realized that they could not break through the qi wall with their own strength alone! Ignoring the other Gu Immortals, just Duke Long alone was a mountain they could not pass.

It was not that Bing Sai Chuan had no other trump cards.

In the previous life, he asked Limitless to turn around, restraining Duke Long for a long time, he was unable to move entirely.

But in this life, Calamity Luck Altar was too far away from Imperfection Regret Pavilion, this method could not be used. In the previous life, Calamity Luck Altar reached Central Great Hall before asking for Limitless' help.

"We can only ask Fang Yuan for help!" Bing Sai Chuan had a thought in his mind.

Chapter 1928: Fang Yuan Takes Action

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had once told Bing Sai Chuan: If the plan to attack Heavenly Court fails, and Longevity Heaven loses all hope of getting fate Gu, they would need to ask the crucial person for reinforcement.

"Who is the crucial person?" Back then, Bing Sai Chuan asked this question.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable then answered him: "Whoever destroys Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is the crucial person. When the time comes, you will definitely know."

Longevity Heaven's plan was to refine destiny Gu, they needed to snatch fate Gu first.

But unlike the previous life, Bing Sai Chuan had suffered a serious setback this time. He had no choice but to ask for help from Fang Yuan.

By the time he received the letter from Bing Sai Chuan, Fang Yuan was already in Central Continent, hiding inside a formation of the organization Defy.

This large formation was set up by Shadow Sect and left for Defy to use as a base camp. However, after the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Shadow Sect perished, Defy was uprooted by Fairy Zi Wei, resulting in this formation turning vacant.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan used this formation to successfully kill Zhou Xiong Xin. In this life, the situation had changed and Fang Yuan retreated early, not tangling with Zhou Xiong Xin too much in order to guard against the killer move people's accusation. As a result, Zhou Xiong Xin survived and became a fierce member of the main force of Heavenly Court, while this formation in Defy was preserved.

"To think that Longevity Heaven would encounter such trouble." Fang Yuan's eyes flickered as he rapidly pondered.

He had been unaware of the situation in Heavenly Court now, this letter containing Bing Sai Chuan's request for help described their precarious predicament in detail.

Compared to the previous life, Fang Yuan soon found the key to Longevity Heaven's problem, they were relocated into the qi wall the moment they arrived.

"It should be because of Qin Ding Ling. With a luck path Gu Immortal like her, Heavenly Court could find out Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement in advance, they even managed to use this to ambush Longevity Heaven instead." Fang Yuan understood.

"This is yet another change."

"There is also call of the ancient... so it turns out that once Calamity Luck Altar activates it, it can teleport immediately. In the previous life, Bing Sai Chuan used this against Duke Long."

Before getting this information, Fang Yuan had been wondering about Heavenly Court's method to use star cast on a large scale, trying to find a way to break it.

How greatly Fairy Zi Wei valued it and did everything possible to preserve the method was how greatly Fang Yuan wanted to destroy it!

By now, Fang Yuan had deduced that this formation was in Heavenly Court, with the core being Star Constellation Chessboard and the countless stars scattered in the sky. The power of the formation was projected onto these stars, using them as the springboard to create a large scale star cast effect.

Fang Yuan did not deduce that Qin Song was the key figure.

In his previous life, Qin Song made a very brief appearance and died after escorting the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals to Hidden Dragon Cave.

Later, the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals did not inform Fang Yuan of this information.

Lacking this crucial clue, Fang Yuan's deduction had hit an impasse.

But now he had become somewhat aware of it.

"According to the information conveyed by Bing Sai Chuan, although Fairy Zi Wei did not participate in the siege, she also appeared outside the qi wall to observe the battle. That's a bit strange, this massive use of star cast should exert all her effort, yet she's still able to distract herself."

"Someone is helping her!"

"Who is that? Is there another wisdom path great expert? Or did others cooperate to create a successful large scale use of star cast?"

Fang Yuan quickly threw away this train of thought.

Now was not the time to contemplate this question, he had to make a decision as soon as possible!

As a wisdom path Gu Immortal, Fang Yuan was now like a chess player who was playing against Fairy Zi Wei.

Both sides had their own chess pieces.

Fairy Zi Wei was clearly a number of pieces ahead, not only in her own wisdom path attainment, but also Heavenly Court's unity, and in the current situation, she had a distinct advantage.

Fang Yuan had a seemingly huge force at his disposal, but in reality, they were fighting on their own, he could only exert influence and push his agenda on the people of the four regions subtly.

Although his subordinates were numerous and far surpassed the previous life, few were qualified to participate in a battle of such a level.

Fang Yuan fully considered the entire Central Continent battlefield once again.

In Infallible blessed land, the Southern Border Gu Immortals entered the battlefield and fought, breaking formations one after another, but this was not a concern for the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, there were endless sub-formations.

In the battlefield of Hidden Dragon Cave, the Eastern Sea immortals were trapped in a large formation and were struggling to break it. However, it was clear that Old Man Bei Feng could still hold on for a while longer.

As for Emperor City's battlefield, the Western Desert Gu Immortals were still on their way, their morale was low too.

In Heavenly Court's battlefield, Longevity Heaven was completely at a disadvantage, and since they were ambushed by Heavenly Court, they had completely lost the initiative.

"Of the four main battlefields, the most important is still Heavenly Court's battlefield. Fate Gu is in Heavenly Court, if we want to win this battle, we must destroy fate Gu." Fang Yuan thought, just like Fairy Zi Wei's analysis, both sides knew where the most important place was.

"That being the case, we cannot lose in Heavenly Court! Longevity Heaven's performance is so disappointing, I was hoping that they would cause problems for Heavenly Court and trigger Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's painting path methods first."

Fang Yuan knew that he had to support Bing Sai Chuan even though he had deceived Fang Yuan for his own interests in the previous life, and also in this current life. For the sake of the entire situation, Fang Yuan had to provide support.

Heavenly Court battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Chaotic Dragon Fist!

Steel fists shook Calamity Luck Altar, the force of the punch caused tremors as countless Gu worms perished instantly.

Within Calamity Luck Altar, Mao Li Qiu shouted: "Let me out! Let me hold him back."

Bing Sai Chuan had a cold expression and shook his head: "No, you are no match for him. You'll be courting death if you go. You're not like the others, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals will target you."

Duke Long ignored Northern Plains' generations of experts, he let the other Heavenly Court members deal with them.

Heavenly Court knew clearly that they could only stop call of the ancient by destroying Calamity Luck Altar.

But once Mao Li Qiu entered battle, it would be different. It was a fierce general of Longevity Heaven, it had great strength and killing Mao Li Qiu would greatly weaken Longevity Heaven, he would definitely take action.

Immortal killer move — World Shaking Dragon Hammer!

Duke Long shouted, he raised his fists above his head and smashed down like a giant hammer.

The surface of Calamity Luck Altar shattered, a huge amount of Gu worms died, their carcasses flying everywhere. A large hole was smashed open on the surface of Calamity Luck Altar, it was only the size of a finger but the inside could be seen!

Duke Long roared: "Longevity Heaven, only defeat awaits you. This outcome was already predetermined from the moment you tried to attack Heavenly Court."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals cheered, their morale climbing to its peak.

"The might of Duke Long is overwhelming!" Bing Sai Chuan sighed long and hard, feeling a sense of powerlessness.

"Why hasn't Fang Yuan come to support us?" Five Elements Grandmaster called out, inevitably revealing a sense of trepidation.

"As far as I know, Fang Yuan is only rank seven, even if he repeatedly defeated Heavenly Court, he was only taking advantage of the River of Time. If he comes to support us, will he really be able to change the battle situation? Even if he brings out Myriad Year Flying Warship, the other side has Duke Long." Bull Demon spoke, expressing doubt.

Indeed, as of now, it would be difficult to resist Duke Long with just two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses.

Duke Long's battle strength was too astounding!

What was even more unbelievable to them was that with every passing moment, Duke Long grew stronger endlessly.

This was unreasonable!

Mao Li Qiu snorted: "That lad took Reverse Flow River in front of my very eyes, at least with that killer move alone, even if he's only rank seven, he can resist Duke Long and take the pressure off us."

"Fang Yuan will definitely support us." Bing Sai Chuan smiled: "I don't know much about him, but I believe in Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable!"

Just as this was said, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals actually began to retreat.

They had the qi wall to rely on, thus retreating quite smoothly.

Soon, only Duke Long was left on the scene.

In the meantime, Zi Wei Fairy dispatched urgently: "Quick, we must send support quickly. The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation in Infallible blessed land is about to collapse! Hidden Dragon Cave's formation is also facing destruction!"

Zhou Xiong Xin and the others were shocked as someone asked: "How could the situation change for the worse so quickly?"

Fairy Zi Wei said: "Fang Yuan is making a move."

"Oh? Even so, the unceasing formation won't collapse so swiftly!"

"He showed up in person?"

"Let's take him out! We will kill this source of chaos for the sake of the world!"

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were all excited.

Previously, Fang Yuan had repeatedly defeated Heavenly Court, causing many of the Gu Immortals to become angry. After Fang Yuan relied on his knowledge to extend his advantage in the River of Time, Heavenly Court lost the lead and failed miserably during the battle of the stone lotus island, suffering huge losses.

Now that the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was held, Fang Yuan had to attack. The battlefield was placed in Central Continent, the Gu Immortals were eager to see how much territorial advantage Fang Yuan could exploit this time!

But Fairy Zi Wei shook her head slightly: "Fang Yuan has not shown himself, I'm afraid the ones outside are only his subordinates."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were stunned.

Mere subordinates could cause the two immortal formations to break apart?

Fairy Zi Wei explained: "In Hidden Dragon Cave, Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace appeared, they used a large number of dream realms to erode the formation."

The truth dawned on the immortals, they had an understanding of Fang Yuan's dream realm methods.

They had already expected this, dream path was an era ahead, it was only natural that the formation would be broken.

"But we have Feng Jin Huang guarding the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation. Although she's only a rank five Gu Master, she can use the power of the immortal formation to unleash the dream path killer move shatter dream, and transform dream realms into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies." Zhou Xiong Xin expressed his confusion.

Fairy Zi Wei said in a complex tone: "That's because he did not use dream path methods against the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, but rule path instead."

"Rule path?!" Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals gasped in amazement once again.

"Rule path?" Within the Infallible blessed land battlefield, the Southern Alliance immortals looked at the formation in front of them with great surprise.

They had broken several formations in a row, but they had learned from Fang Yuan that this was the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, while they were feeling annoyed and troubled, this nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation broke apart on its own.

When they exited the formation, the Southern Alliance immortals saw a large formation suspended high in the sky, constantly emitting a five-colored smoke miasma.

The smoke miasma infiltrated the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, forcing Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals to dismantle the sub-formations on their own.

"These are reinforcements of Fang Yuan, this formation was created by Southern Border Gu Immortal Tao Zhu, it is called the five regional limit formation, it can emit a smoke miasma and create a formation similar to the environment of the five regions' regional walls." Wu Yong received a letter from Fang Yuan at this time and explained with a rather complicated expression.

Chapter 1929: Evil Dragon Escapes

"To think that there would be such an amazing formation that can counter the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation!"

"To think that our Southern Border's Gu Immortal, Tao Zhu, created it..."

"It seems that we had greatly underestimated this person."

"Fang Yuan actually possesses this method, when did he get it?"

The Southern Border Gu Immortals conversed as they sighed in amazement.

Fang Yuan had extorted and blackmailed them, but now it was Fang Yuan who had stepped in to support them, which made the Southern Border Gu Immortals all feel quite complicated.

At this moment, the voice of Zhan Bu Du came from within the five regional limit formation: "Southern Border, please do not lower your guard yet. Heavenly Court will not sit around as they lose control of this battlefield, they will surely send reinforcements."

"In that case, please also open the immortal formation and let us defend within it." A Southern Border Gu Immortal replied.

Zhan Bu Du smiled lightly, not hiding his contempt in the slightest: "There is no need to say such naive words. Whether you all fight or retreat, it depends on your willingness. If you don't want to fight, just scram."

"You..." The Southern Border Gu Immortal who answered had a change of expression from anger.

At this moment, more than ten giant pillars of starlight shone down, the main force of the Heavenly Court really did come to help out!

"This is the formation! Tear it down!" Zhang Fei Xiong took the lead.

Zhan Bu Du was silent and began to activate the formation with his concentration, the five-colored smoke miasma not only defended itself but also spread incessantly to the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation.

Even though the latter formation was created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it had to dismantle the sub-formations at the moment, it was stalling for as much time as possible.

"Let's take action and do our best to protect the five regional limit formation." Wu Yong did not hesitate and immediately ordered.

"Lord, but this is Fang Yuan. Haven't you been opposing..." Someone was unwilling.

Wu Yong gave this person a fierce stare and spoke in a stern tone, "Everything is for the big picture!"

His prestige was high, Wu clan was also the number one force in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, their leadership had become a tradition.

The Southern Alliance Gu Immortals immediately engaged in a fierce battle with the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

With their help, Zhan Bu Du was relieved internally, the pressure on his shoulders dissipated mostly, and the five-colored smoke miasma spread even more menacingly.

With the cry of a phoenix, flames dazzled and the figure of Prince Feng Xian appeared.

He had sharp eyes and a golden cloak on his back, he opened his mouth to breathe out a monstrous flame.

The flames burned in the five-colored smoke miasma, sweeping towards the immortals of Southern Border.

A rank eight Gu Immortal of Southern Border, Yi Hao Fang, immediately transformed into a sea beast and rode the water waves to stop the flames from spreading.

Jun Shen Guang transformed into a white light, moving through the battlefield, avoiding the four rank eights of Southern Border and attacking the remaining rank seven Gu Immortals.

Moving along with him were Zhou Xiong Xin, Zhu Que Er and others.

Unfixed Manor, Flying Sand Pavilion, and Bay Pavilion were all taken out as Southern Border's rank seven Gu Immortals quickly entered them.

"Ahhh!"

A scream was heard as Vortex Space Boy carried the head of a Southern Border Gu Immortal in his hand.

Taking advantage of this moment, the rest of the Southern Border rank seven immortals entered the Immortal Gu Houses.

"You guys are moving too slowly." Vortex Space Boy looked at Zhou Xiong Xin and the others as he chuckled.

"Where are you going?!" Wu Yong snorted coldly and chased after him.

Vortex Space Boy retaliated with an immortal killer move, obviously prepared in advance.

Wu Yong raised his hand similarly, setting off a roaring tornado of wind blades, the two killer moves collided with a loud bang, air currents surged, the five-colored smoke miasma rumbled like a dragon.

Vortex Space Boy and Wu Yong grunted at the same time and their faces turned pale.

Immortal killer move — Sitting and Eating the Mountain Empty!

Taking advantage of this time, Zhao Shan He teamed up with Yu Zhu Zi once again to display this powerful killer move.

"Even if you have Immortal Gu Houses, so what?" Yu Zhu Zi snorted coldly.

All the Immortals in the Southern Border Immortal Gu Houses were hit by this move and their faces changed color, their Gu worms and immortal essence were all rapidly depleting out of thin air.

Wu Yong's pupils shrunk, he advanced instead of retreating: "Defend me!"

Ba De and Chi Qu You immediately moved to his side.

The Immortal Gu Houses stayed at the periphery.

"Stop him!" Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were all experienced in battle, Wu Yong immediately drew all their firepower as he looked like he was about to launch a powerful killer move.

Chi Qu You and Ba De struggled to resist them but soon lost the ability to continue holding them off.

One of them was a formation path Gu Immortal while the other had just advanced to rank eight, how could they be a match for the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals?

In terms of strength alone, Heavenly Court was clearly superior to the immortals of Southern Border. Fortunately, Southern Border had Immortal Gu Houses as well as the five-colored smoke miasma created by Zhan Bu Du, they were huge obstacles for both sides to fight with their full strength, the difference in strength between the two sides was somehow balanced.

However, even though the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals knew well that the stronger the attacks they used in this miasma, the deeper the backlash they would suffer, they were still brave enough to fight to the death, having a relentless stance as they approached the five regional limit formation without any fear of their lives.

After some time, the Southern Border immortals' battle formation started to show signs of crumbling.

Wan Zi Hong suddenly gave a delicate cry as flower petals flew, attacking the Southern Border Immortal Gu Houses in front of her and forcing them to move aside, forcefully creating a path to move on.

Zhang Fei Xiong followed, transforming into a bear-headed giant and slamming into the five regional limit formation.

Boom!

There was a loud bang and the formation trembled viciously.

Massive amounts of Gu worms perished, even Zhan Bu Du suffered backlash, spitting out a large mouthful of blood.

"Ah, that hurts!" The Formation Spirit was in the main formation, it howled miserably as its body suddenly became much more illusory, no longer as solid as before.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were no better.

They also suffered enormous backlash, but one by one, they gritted their teeth and tried their best to destroy the five regional limit formation.

"Oh no, the Southern Alliance won't be able to defend against such a fierce attack from Heavenly Court." Zhan Bu Du secretly gritted his teeth.

The main power of the five regional limit formation lay in the five-colored smoke miasma, although its defense was also strong, it would never last long under the fierce attack of these Gu Immortals.

"But even if that's the case, I'll fight to the death and try to stall for as long as possible." Zhan Bu Du was already prepared to die.

Everything was for the big picture, even if it meant sacrificing this clone, he would have no regret.

Sacrifices should be made when necessary, clones were also merely chess pieces. It was just easier to fully utilize them.

Even if the five regional limit formation was broken and destroyed, it was still valuable.

On one hand, it temporarily maintained the Heavenly Court battlefield and protected Longevity Heaven's members. On the other hand, it gave a crucial amount of time for the battlefield in Hidden Dragon Cave.

Hidden Dragon Cave.

A large amount of dream realms were eroding the battlefield, Old Man Bei Feng was livid but unable to do anything about it.

"Call for help, call for help, grandfather!" Feng Chan Zi shouted in a hurry, his face was pale and covered in cold sweat.

Old Man Bei Feng did not speak.

He had already requested for support, but Heavenly Court's reinforcements were delayed, that did not make sense.

After all, Heavenly Court had a way to use a large scale star cast method, it would only take an instant for support to come over. If they did not appear at this time, they must have been held back by something.

A bad feeling filled Old Man Bei Feng's heart.

Roar!

Already sensing the weakening of its bindings, the suppressed Di Zang Sheng within the formation was also struggling at this time, adding onto the burden of the formation.

Immortal killer move — Mountain Suppression!

Immortal killer move — Broken Mirror Shard Light!

Qing Yue An and Song Qi Yuan were the first to break through the restraints, and because of their efforts, the power of the formation was greatly weakened once again. The other Gu Immortals were able to successfully break through one after another.

The eight Immortals converged, and although they were still inside the formation, they had noticed the change.

"How could there be so many dream realms!" Zhang Yin pretended not to know and looked surprised.

"Perhaps Fang Yuan is helping us." Shen Cong Sheng deliberately said, he had actually gotten a message from Fang Yuan: "Who else can control the dream realms besides him?"

"Why is Fang Yuan here!?" Hua Cai Yun frowned.

"As the saying goes, great people see eye to eye, he may also try to target Di Zang Sheng." Qing Yue An guessed as he healed his wounds.

"Then let Fang Yuan go release Di Zang Sheng, should we withdraw now?" Hua Cai Yun hesitated.

Right at this moment, there was a loud rumble as an Immortal Gu House broke the formation, charging towards the formation core.

This Immortal Gu House was a majestic palace, emitting an orange-golden glow, it was overbearingly magnificent, and the surface of the palace was filled with dragon-shaped carvings.

Hua Cai Yun, Qing Yue An and the others were stunned, although they were seeing it for the first time, they all guessed the name of this Immortal Gu House at the same time — Dragon Palace!

There was a loud rumble as Dragon Palace crashed through the core area.

Old Man Bei Feng howled and fell to the ground, he suffered a strong backlash, he was currently in a terrible state, having less than ten percent of his battle strength left.

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Dreamy light smoke, with a gentle movement, moved Old Man Bei Feng into the palace and sealed him with ease.

Feng Chan Zi who was beside Old Man Bei Feng also got swept into this smoke.

Seeing a rank eight Gu Immortal being suppressed so easily, the Eastern Sea rank eight Gu Immortals could not help but show changes of expressions. Only half of them were genuine, while the other half were disguising their emotions as they knew about the truth.

Wu Shuai controlled Dragon Palace, and after capturing Old Man Bei Feng, he plunged down into the depths of the Earth Trench, ignoring the eight Eastern Sea immortals.

Qing Yue An and the others looked very pale, realizing that they were being used as cannon fodder and bait by Fang Yuan.

A moment later, they heard another deafening dragon roar, the earth shook as heaven and earth changed color, a huge Evil Dragon slowly rose up.

The Eastern Sea Gu Immortals panicked and retreated, looking up.

The Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng was so huge that it was like a mountain range, flying high in the sky, enveloping heaven and earth, it could shroud the brilliance of the sun and moon!

Thankfully, Di Zang Sheng did not find trouble with the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals and flew directly to the west.

"Central Continent is in for a world of trouble, haha."

"Strange, where did Dragon Palace go?"

"What? You want to fight against Fang Yuan? Let's leave now."

"You all saw the move that Dragon Palace just used to capture Old Man Bei Feng, right? It's a dream path killer move!"

The Eastern Sea immortals stopped their conversation, they did not dare to stay longer.

Fang Yuan's demonic might had shocked rank eights, after all, Heavenly Court had been defeated by Fang Yuan several times. Now that he used the methods of Dragon Palace, he shocked these unsuspecting Gu Immortals even more.

"Di Zang Sheng has been released, it will definitely create chaos in Central Continent, creating a good opportunity for us."

"No, don't forget how the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals appeared before the war started. I don't want a dozen or so Heavenly Court rank eights suddenly appearing around me when I'm on the move."

The Eastern Sea Gu Immortals were also communicating while flying away, they frowned when this was brought up.

They had originally planned to release Di Zang Sheng to deplete Central Continent's foundation and attract firepower to facilitate their actions. But Heavenly Court possessed the method to use a large scale star cast, nullifying the effectiveness of this plan.

Chapter 1930: Qi Ci Lang

To continue with their previous plan, Eastern Sea's immortals would have to first unravel Heavenly Court's method, otherwise, it would be too dangerous.

Shen Cong Sheng looked at the sky, thinking of the information that Fang Yuan gave him, he spoke: "It is not impossible to unravel Heavenly Court's method. Heavenly Court purposely arranged a large number of stars in white heaven and used them to relocate Gu Immortals to anywhere in Central Continent."

The other Gu Immortals' eyes brightened at the news.

"Then we should destroy these stars."

"But if we attack white heaven, wouldn't we be provoking Heavenly Court, what if the main force of Heavenly Court besieges us again?"

Some Gu Immortals were hesitant.

Granny Rong spoke slowly and logically: "There is indeed such a risk."

Zhang Yin sneered: "What are you afraid of? If you can't beat them, can't you escape? Just pay some attention to prevent Heavenly Court from making use of a battlefield killer move, if we engage in a hit and run situation, can Heavenly Court waste their time chasing us?"

"Haha, Zhang Yin's words are reasonable." Yang Zi He's eyebrows raised, he caressed his palm and smiled: "Currently, the situation in Central Continent is chaotic with battles everywhere, Di Zang Sheng has even been released. We have already provoked Heavenly Court at this point, what is there to hesitate?"

Shi Miao acted like he was contemplating: "It seems that Heavenly Court cannot cope with so many battlefields at the moment. If not, why wouldn't they come over to fight us? Why would they let us free Di Zang Sheng?"

Song Qi Yuan nodded: "Heavenly Court is already overwhelmed, it seems that the Southern Border Gu Immortals have found the location of Infallible blessed land and are storming the battlefield, attacking Heavenly Court's formation. The Western Desert immortals are heading to Emperor City. The Northern Plains Gu Immortals are still nowhere to be seen, but these barbarians are bound to join in the chaotic battle. And with Di Zang Sheng rampaging as well... In my opinion, I'm afraid Heavenly Court won't be able to care about us yet."

With that, the Eastern Sea eight immortals reached a unified opinion once again and acted in unison, heading for white heaven.

They were still unaware that Longevity Heaven had already engaged with Heavenly Court in a huge battle.

In their case, Emperor City did not have anything valuable to loot. Infallible blessed land was attractive but Southern Border and Heavenly Court were already fighting there, it was better to avoid it.

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei stayed in Central Great Hall to oversee the situation, all sorts of new information reached her continuously.

Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals entered white heaven, their motive was very clear, they wanted to destroy the stars that Heavenly Court had arranged.

But it was not a problem.

When they set up the stars as an arrangement, Heavenly Court made considerations. Fairy Zi Wei decided to ignore them.

These stars were placed in a scattered manner, they were far from each other, if Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals wanted to destroy them, they would need to spend a lot of time.

In other words, Heavenly Court was using these star immortal materials to stall eight rank eight Gu Immortals, this was extremely worth it, Fairy Zi Wei was happy to see them take action.

After all, with Qin Song's condition, they could only use a large scale star cast method four more times. Before Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals destroy all the stars, these four uses would likely be expended.

What worried Fairy Zi Wei was Di Zang Sheng.

In truth, Di Zang Sheng escaping was not too worrying to Fairy Zi Wei.

But the problem was, after escaping, Di Zang Sheng acted very strangely, it did not create chaos and destruction wantonly, it flew away calmly and was not in a maniacal state.

This was different from historical records.

"Was it subdued by Dragon Palace?" Fairy Zi Wei could not help but think of this.

It was easy to deduce it.

Firstly, Heavenly Court had records that Dragon Palace was an enslavement path Immortal Gu House, everyone knew that. Secondly, Fang Yuan sent Dragon Palace to attack Hidden Dragon Cave, he must have had some intention. Dragon Palace displayed powerful dream path methods, with its battle strength, Fang Yuan would not use it in a non-crucial battlefield!

"If Fang Yuan's previous idea was to use Dragon Palace to subdue Di Zang Sheng, then him dispatching his subordinates to set up a large formation to restrain the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation and attract the main force of our Heavenly Court to attack furiously is just bait. At the same time, the attack of the eight Eastern Sea immortals is also a smokescreen that he threw." Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with cold light.

"Fang Yuan was actually able to influence the eight immortals of Eastern Sea? How did he do it? Among the eight immortals of Eastern Sea, it seems there are members of Fang Yuan's group, or those who secretly work with him. I'm afraid that there are quite a few of these members, there are at least two of them."

Fairy Zi Wei speculated: "But what if Fang Yuan coincidentally happened to be there? The eight immortals of Eastern Sea unexpectedly had the same goal as him, allowing him to benefit by chance. This is also quite possible. After all, Fang Yuan has Giant Sun's true inheritance, his luck has constantly been good. Qin Ding Ling is on our side, but she is still healing. Altering Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement had a much larger price than we expected."

Even if he was an opponent, Fairy Zi Wei could not help but admire Fang Yuan.

She also had to admit, Fang Yuan had done a beautiful job in the Hidden Dragon Cave battlefield!

The bad feeling in her heart was still deepening, Fairy Zi Wei's attention was mostly focusing on Di Zang Sheng.

"Most likely, it is being controlled by Fang Yuan. Then where exactly is it going to reinforce the enemy?"

"Emperor City is the nearest battlefield, the elite Gu Masters have just arrived, they have yet to officially begin the final round of the Refinement Path Convention. Destroying Emperor City will greatly delay the restoration of fate Gu."

"It is also likely to go to the Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield. Wiping out the main force of Heavenly Court at once is also Fang Yuan's style. Even if the main force of Heavenly Court is teleported back by me, he will still find a way to destroy Infallible blessed land. Once he destroys the blessed land, then at least this time, our restoration of fate Gu will have to be suspended."

"Of course, Heavenly Court's battlefield is also a possibility. Since Longevity Heaven can come in unannounced, it is also possible that Fang Yuan can come. After all, he has obtained Red Lotus Demon Venerable's true inheritance, so he might have access to such a backdoor secretly."

For the first time since the start of the war, Fairy Zi Wei felt passive.

If the large scale star cast method could teleport Duke Long as well, it would be great. However, unfortunately, Duke Long's might became an obstacle to the teleportation. To make a comparison, the Heavenly Court rank eights were like a dozen rabbits, while Duke Long was a full-grown elephant, the difference between the two was considerably big, the star cast method could not move Duke Long.

Immortal killer move — Decomposition!

Northern Plains Gu Immortal Yu Yang Zi used his signature method, this killer move was largely the reason why he was famous in history.

Decomposition hit Duke Long directly, his body paused for a moment, as he looked at Yu Yang Zi, he had a plain expression: "Oh, that's decomposition. You are Yu Yang Zi?"

When Duke Long said that, he was hundreds of steps away from Yu Yang Zi.

After he said that, purple-gold dragon-shaped qi flickered as he was teleported right in front of Yu Yang Zi.

At this moment, Yu Yang Zi's pupils shrank to pin size as his heart pounded wildly with alarms and warnings.

He tried to retreat but it was clearly just an extravagant hope — his neck was steadily choked by a large hand.

It was Duke Long's hand, covered in purple-gold dragon scales, with fingers as sharp as blades.

Yu Yang Zi had already activated his defensive killer move, but the killer move's light was like glass, it shattered under the force of the monstrous dragon claws.

Before dying, Yu Yang Zi roared and self-detonated, an intense explosion resounded, the terrifying shock wave spread out intensely, shaking all the surroundings.

The smoke and dust dissipated, the figure of Duke Long remained standing like a pillar of heaven.

"Immortals of Northern Plains, what else do you have other than a lack of fear for death?" Duke Long's tone was plain, but it spread throughout the battlefield.

The Northern Plains immortals gnashed their teeth, but could not refute it.

Although the main force of Heavenly Court had all withdrawn with only Duke Long left, even with only Duke Long alone, Calamity Luck Altar still could not make an inch of progress. They could only rely on call of the ancient to constantly summon powerful experts of Northern Plains in history to maintain the battle situation.

"And this!" Suddenly, Liu Liu Liu's figure appeared behind Duke Long's back.

Duke Long's body shook.

The grey light dagger in Liu Liu Liu's hand was thrust into his back, even the purple-gold dragon scales could not block this method.

This was Liu Liu Liu's signature killer move — Despicable Penetrating Blade!

In the previous life, Liu Liu Liu had killed many members of Heavenly Court with this move, and even severely injured Fairy Zi Wei. At that time, if not for Wu Shuang blocking most of the power, Fairy Zi Wei would have died tragically in his hands.

"Good!" Seeing this scene, the Northern Plains immortals were suddenly energized.

Since the start of the war, no matter how furiously the Northern Plains immortals attacked, this was the first time that Duke Long was wounded like this.

However, Liu Liu Liu's face changed abruptly, he could not hide his shock.

Although his killer move dagger had pierced into Duke Long's body, it was like the blade got stuck in a block of iron, unable to move a single inch!

"A human path killer move? Not bad, it fits your temperament." Duke Long slowly turned around and stretched out his hand, steadily grasping Liu Liu Liu's head.

At this moment, Liu Liu Liu suddenly realized: "Duke Long purposely got hit by my move, he used his body as bait to trap me!"

It was not that he did not want to escape, but he could not.

Like the dagger in his hand, he could not move.

Slap.

With a cracking sound, Liu Liu Liu's skull was like a watermelon easily crushed by Duke Long, his headless corpse immediately fell down, the grey dagger in his hand dissipated instantly.

"Who else?!" Duke Long raised his arms and shouted, his body was like iron, having grown to twice the size of a normal man, his long purple hair dancing wildly in a monstrous wave of sounds.

The Northern Plains immortals responded to him with countless killer moves.

Rumble...

There were dazzling light shadows, countless killer moves were stacked on top of each other, Duke Long rushed out brutally, displaying world shaking dragon hammer and ruthlessly slamming into Calamity Luck Altar.

With a loud bang, Calamity Luck Altar flew back dozens of steps, creating a long trench on the ground.

The front that was hit by Duke Long was completely caved in, forming a shockingly deep pit.

"There is no time to repair damage of such a level!" Bing Sai Chuan thudded, his heart sinking violently.

Bull Demon, Flower Lady, and Five Elements Grandmaster were trying to repair Calamity Luck Altar, they froze at this moment.

If Calamity Luck Altar broke, Longevity Heaven's members would immediately lose this battle, they would die without a proper burial!

But at the moment when Duke Long was about to attack again, a black light flew out from the River of Time.

The black light followed the hole in the front of Calamity Luck Altar and shot into its interior, transforming into a young and handsome looking Gu Immortal with curly black hair hanging down his waist.

With a wave of his palm, the young Gu Immortal's dark light surged, quickly repairing the damage of Calamity Luck Altar and saving Longevity Heaven from the brink of defeat!

Bing Sai Chuan's body shook intensely: "Seventh Prince!"

Duke Long snorted coldly: "So it's Giant Sun's child."

The young looking Gu Immortal was the seventh child of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he was known as Seventh Prince, he nodded: "Duke Long, with me, Qi Ci Lang, here, it will be much harder for you to destroy Calamity Luck Altar now."

Chapter 1931: Shen Shang's Solution

"This is Central Continent's Emperor City?" Ye Fan followed the main group as they walked into Emperor City, he looked around and assessed the place.

He was a Southern Border Gu Master, but he had heard of Emperor City's famous name long ago.

This was the largest mortal city in Central Continent, or rather, the entire five regions world. Here, rank three Gu Masters were very commonly seen, but in Southern Border, rank three Gu Masters were normally authoritative elders in their clans.

This was the first time Ye Fan visited Emperor City.

Emperor City lived up to its name, it was well guarded and had a grand structure, Ye Fan was not disappointed.

"However, compared to an Immortal Gu House, Emperor City is far inferior." Thinking of this, Ye Fan looked at the sky.

In the sky, there were several Immortal Gu Houses floating silently.

There was a pavilion, exquisite and small, there were countless bird cages hanging on it, birds chirped continuously. This was Heavenly Lotus Sect's Canary Pavilion.

There was a garden that was exquisitely built, it was grand with white jade tiles and oozing with cold air, there were faint dragon roars heard occasionally, this was Ancient Soul Sect's Immortal Gu House, Frost Dragon Manor.

There was also a seven-story tower, curtains were fluttering in the building, it was Wind Cloud Manor's rank seven Immortal Gu House, Wind Sweeping Building.

There was also Combat Immortal Sect's Edge Link Camp which had grand flags fluttering with the wind.

Other than those, Illusion Garden, Yue Yang Palace, and Sun and Moon Temple were there.

Ye Fan's master was Lu Wei Yin, he learned a lot of information regarding Gu Immortals from him, he could discern most of the famous Immortal Gu Houses.

These Immortal Gu Houses were not as large as Emperor City, but they were much more dazzling, they were the center of attention that all of the city people were talking about.

At this time, a youngster beside him sighed: "It seems that the rumors are correct. The world is going to change, immortals are going to battle. A chaotic great era is coming, the difference between mortal and immortal will shrink! This is our plan too, isn't that right, Brother Ye?"

Ye Fan looked at the youngster as he nodded: "You are correct, Brother Hong."

Similar to the previous life, Ye Fan and Hong Yi met in the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention and became sworn brothers after they interacted.

Hong Yi smiled: "This Refinement Path Convention is unprecedented, let those Gu Immortals fight in the sky, it is not something we can interfere in."

"Haha, that makes sense, let us have a true competition this time!" Ye Fan patted Hong Yi's shoulders.

The two brothers were filled with fighting spirit.

Hong Yi said: "I have a feeling that the eventual winner of this Refinement Path Convention will be one of us."

Shen Shang's ears twitched, he heard the entire conversation between Hong Yi and Ye Fan without missing a word.

These two were mortals, but Shen Shang kept a trace of his concentration on them at all times.

"In the future five regions chaotic war, these two youngsters likely have an opportunity to become immortal." Shen Shang was a human path quasi-supreme, he had a strong premonition when it came to humans.

Over at Heavenly Court, people's united hearts and other human path killer moves were all used already, Unfettered Scholar and Zheng Qing had been expelled.

But Shen Shang still managed to disguise himself and enter the final competition ground, he was not suspected at all.

He was after all a rank eight Gu Immortal and also a human path quasi-supreme grandmaster!

Shen Shang observed his surroundings, he became gradually excited.

"My estimations earlier were not wrong, this Emperor City is one of the main human veins of Central Continent!"

Mountains had mountain veins, the earth had earth veins, and humans had human veins.

"Emperor City was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, after so many years of relocation and movement, it still remained as the largest gathering spot of humans, it stayed on the trail of Central Continent's human vein all along."

"This place produces human talents, it is because of Central Continent's main human vein. Heavenly Court's generations of Immortal Venerables have left their human path methods here, hmm... I can vaguely sense their existence."

Fang Yuan used his rebirth as the reason to urge Shen Shang to take action and try to unravel the various venerable human path methods.

This was a challenging mission, it spurred on Shen Shang's morale and ambition.

Fang Yuan and the rest could not sense any of the traces of these human path killer moves. But for Shen Shang, he could trace and locate them.

Thus, he disguised himself and entered Emperor City, he finally found a chance to destroy the venerable killer moves.

"Heavenly Court is collecting human will and storing it inside Heavenly Court for use."

"That place is too tightly defended, if we cannot enter Heavenly Court, we will not be able to destroy the human will. If we cannot destroy the human will, we cannot drain them of this resource."

"However... taking action here will also have superb effects."

"Heavenly Court is collecting human will, Emperor City plays a crucial role in this process, it is the largest shipment area they have to transport the human will."

"If I destroy this place, Heavenly Court's efficiency in gathering human will would fall greatly."

But Shen Shang did not plan to cause destruction.

He had a greater objective.

He wanted to follow the traces with Emperor City as the anchor to find the venerable human path killer moves and reverse-deduce the profundities of their human path methods, to try to steal their knowledge!

Shen Shang was confident and daring.

He was not satisfied with just the reputation of unraveling a venerable killer move, he wanted to master the venerable human path methods and gain much more strength in the process.

"If my human path methods improve, it might be possible to get rid of the problem of the black fire, I will not go berserk anymore."

Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield.

Five colored smoke miasma rumbled, Southern Border's Gu Immortals and Heavenly Court's main forces had already fought for a long time.

Bay Pavilion, Flying Sand Pavilion, and Unfixed Manor were heavily damaged, they went to the second defensive line to get repaired.

At the front lines, there were four rank eights from Southern Border, as well as two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and Great Space Temple.

Heavenly Court's main forces had no deaths, their morale was high.

Zhao Shan He prepared his killer move again, his aura was surging.

Zhan Bu Du quickly shouted: "Stop him! He is going to use that move again!"

Wu Yong and Yi Hao Fang gritted their teeth, they wanted to charge in but Ye Qiao Zi and Vortex Space Boy stopped them.

Zhou Xiong Xin and Flesh Whip Immortal joined hands to obstruct Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

Meanwhile, Zhu Que Er and Wan Zi Hong went from the right and left, bypassing the battlefield to attack the five regional limit formation directly.

Wu Yong and the rest were left with no choice, they had to return to being defensive.

They had too few people, it was hard enough to defend, they were not as agile and flexible as Heavenly Court's group.

Zhao Shan He successfully used his killer move, he opened his mouth, he sucked in all of the surrounding five colored smoke.

A large amount of smoke was sucked into his stomach, which expanded at an observable rate. At the same time, his face and muscles turned multicolored.

Zhao Shan He actually swallowed the five colored smoke, creating a temporary cleared out area.

Without the restraints of the five colored smoke, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were able to use their full power, they unleashed all sorts of killer moves with terrifying power.

Wu Yong and the rest resisted, but their defensive line was not tight, killer moves were directed to get through the cracks, after a rough filter by their defenses, the rest landed on the five regional limit formation.

The five regional limit formation shook intensely, a large number of Gu worms died, a weakened Formation Spirit quickly tried to repair it.

Zhan Bu Du's expression was ugly.

Relying on Zhao Shan He's food path method, Heavenly Court managed to make a breakthrough, each time they used this method, the five regional limit formation suffered immense damage.

Even though they were repairing it at full speed, it could not keep up with the waves of attacks that kept on coming.

As damage accumulated, the five regional limit formation started to get into a dangerous spot.

What to do?

Emperor City.

The final round of the competition was racing against the clock to start.

Shen Shang was secretly happy.

He started to refine Gu, using this as a cover, he secretly prepared his killer move.

"We finally arrived!" Fang Di Chang drove Divine Bean Palace as he charged at the front.

Behind him was Western Desert's main troops.

"To battle!"

"Force them back!"

"Defend Emperor City to the death."

Central Continent's troops cheered and shouted, they faced off against Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses as battle erupted.

"Wonderful!" Shen Shang, who was paying attention to the outside world, cheered, with Central Continent's forces being restrained, he had no worries left.

Right at this moment!

Bam.

He erupted with a strong Gu Immortal aura, he shouted as profound white light pierced through the hall, radiating in the entire Emperor City.

"The venerables have passed away, all of your human path methods should go as well!" Shen Shang's eyes shined with piercing and blinding light.

Puff!

At the next moment, he spat out a mouthful of blood, his body cracked as his lungs burst, his intestines blew into tiny pieces that shot out of the wounds all over his body.

Failure!

"How can this be?!" Shen Shang could not believe this, he stared with wide eyes: "I had already..."

Not only did he fail to resolve the venerable methods, he even triggered them in advance.

This was human path killer move — Hope of the People!

White light flew around in the sky like a snowstorm, it gathered on the bodies of the Central Continent Gu Immortals, creating a pure white halo.

Human path killer move — Heroes Among People!

The white lights surrounding the Central Continent Gu Immortals started to shrink, while the Gu Immortals' auras started to grow.

Howl!

Central Continent's army roared, their morale soared as they charged towards Western Desert's troops.

"Oh no!" Fang Di Chang's expression changed.

Chapter 1932: Heavenly Court's Grand Might

The white light that spread across the sky was like drifting snow, filling the heaven and earth of Central Continent.

The first to benefit was Emperor City's battlefield.

"So strong, such strong power!" Central Continent's Gu Immortals had an incredible feeling, their bodies were surging with new strength. This strength was so grand and vast, it felt like an endless tide, sweeping through their bodies and minds constantly.

All their fatigue was gone.

Their minds were clear, their fighting spirit also rose sharply.

Be it rank six, seven, or even rank eight, they felt the same.

"This is the foundation of my Central Continent's Heavenly Court!"

"My strength has at least doubled, and with such an increase, what enemies will I be afraid of?"

"Charge, kill them, we will defeat all the invaders! Let them know the might of Heavenly Court, the might of Central Continent!!"

The morale on Central Continent's side soared like a rainbow, setting off a ferocious frenzy of attacks.

Western Desert's side was retreating steadily.

"Retreat!"

"Quickly retreat!"

"Such an amplification is truly terrifying, what kind of killer move is this?"

"Let's avoid battle for now, such a powerful killer move cannot last long."

The Gu Immortals on Western Desert's side communicated in panic.

"It's useless. This is the method of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the two human path killer moves are heroes among people and hope of the people respectively, they have no problem sustaining it throughout the entire battle." Fang Di Chang said.

The Western Desert side kept retreating, but Divine Bean Palace under Fang Di Chang's control always remained in place, as if it was their support pillar, with no intention of retreating.

Fang Di Chang had a cold look on his face.

He did not expect that Shen Shang's unraveling would actually cause the killer moves to activate in advance.

In the previous life, these two human path methods were a rather important trump card that changed the battle situation.

In this life, Fang Yuan had painstakingly plotted to ally with Shen Shang in order to resolve these two methods. But despite all of his efforts, the results were still unsatisfactory. As far as the current results were concerned, Shen Shang not only failed to restrain and get rid of the two killer moves, he even made the situation more troublesome.

Heroes among people targeted Gu Immortals themselves, causing their comprehensive battle strength to be amplified to at least double of the original!

The killer move had terrifying might, after gaining the amplification, the Gu Immortal's killer moves, including Immortal Gu Houses and immortal formations, would be powered up as well. In a certain aspect, it was even more useful than Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's perfect pair killer move.

The waves of attacks were like stormy waves, bombarding Divine Bean Palace incessantly.

Divine Bean Palace was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, but it could not resist such impacts. The surface was cracked and damaged, a large number of Gu worms died quickly and miserably, facing destruction.

But the power of Divine Bean Palace was in recovery, it followed the cultivation style of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable.

Although a lot of the Gu worms perished, they would be replenished quickly. Injured Gu worms that did not die would even recover quickly!

Divine Bean Palace was like a golden reef, steadily supporting itself on the front lines, silently enduring the endless bombardment of Central Continent's forces.

"As expected of Divine Bean Palace!"

"Fang clan's Fang Di Chang is really a worthy leader."

"Let's fight, since we've come this far, are we going to constantly run away?"

The morale of the Western Desert army was finally stabilized, their Gu Immortals no longer retreated and faced the Immortal Gu Houses of Central Continent.

At once, battle started between Immortal Gu Houses.

Canary Pavilion opened several bird cages, groups of birds flew freely, when they flew out of the bird cages, they swiftly grew and formed a flock of birds, like an overwhelming patch of moving dark clouds.

Western Desert's Chicken Dog Coop was not falling behind, releasing a flock of desolate beast chickens and dogs to fight against it.

After a few moments of contact between the two sides, it became clear that the chicken and dog desolate beasts could not resist, many were killed.

"I'll help you!" Dong clan's Gu Immortals steered Red River Wheel to go and support them.

Red River Wheel was like a waterwheel, it rolled forward as a huge red light shot out of the wheel, it seemed to resemble a ribbon that tangled the bird group.

The molten flame birds were immediately suppressed, they were captured by the red light and were all subdued within Red River Wheel.

"Thanks for the molten flame birds!" Dong clan's Gu Immortals laughed loudly, the power of Red River Wheel rose by twenty percent because of this!

Although Western Desert's side gained a small profit, Chicken Dog Coop still had to cooperate with Red River Wheel to resist Canary Pavilion.

This was common sense.

In the battlefield, Western Desert's Immortal Gu Houses often had to team up against one enemy.

The Immortal Gu Houses on Central Continent's side all had great power. Yue Yang Palace shot out grand profound light, piercing the skies, Frost Dragon Manor emitted dragon soul and frost energy, Wind Sweeping Building rampaged with tornadoes, sweeping the battlefield.

From the first contact, Western Desert's group was pressured and could barely resist.

"This cannot go on." Fang Di Chang observed the battlefield, he was a little worried.

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

Fang Di Chang knew about Central Continent's strength but he was even clearer regarding the strength of his forces. Western Desert's Gu Immortals would not fight to the death, this group that he brought was already the result of Fang Di Chang's maximum effort.

With such intense battles, once any deaths occurred on Western Desert's side, they would want to retreat.

Once someone retreats, others would follow.

In other words, this was not a real army, it was a gathering of dispersed forces, their morale could not be sustained.

Fang Di Chang led these people at such a crucial time, he had to be at the front lines, to ensure that they would remain in formation.

"I wanted to save this for the end... there is no choice." Fang Di Chang sighed, he sent out the divine bean soldiers that he had saved within Divine Bean Palace.

The quantity of yellow bean soldiers was the highest, they were the basic troops that were treated as cannon fodder.

Next were green bean soldiers that could shoot flying arrows, red bean soldiers could self-detonate, while black bean soldiers had the greatest defense.

As for blue and white bean soldiers, they had the lowest quantity, the former could reflect killer moves to an extent while the latter could heal bean soldiers.

Once the bean army was sent out, they stabilized the situation, causing a deadlock to occur. But the price to pay was that these soldiers were rapidly being expended.

Once the casualties hit a certain level, Western Desert's side would be pressured once again. By then, Fang Di Chang would be out of trump cards, he would need to wait for reinforcements.

Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Rumors Become Tigers!

Zhou Xiong Xin used his information path killer move as tigers formed into groups, roaring and attacking Wu Yong.

Wu Yong waved his hands repeatedly, and used countless wind blades to stop the tigers from pouncing at him.

To the side, Zhu Que Er and Ye Qiao Zi joined forces to attack him.

Wu Yong sighed and wisely retreated.

If now was earlier, he might have been able to fight them head on, but now after the amplification from human path killer moves, Wu Yong could only retreat.

Speaking of which, he had repeatedly tried to use the killer move unlimited wind, but he was always obstructed by Heavenly Court, unable to gain the precious time he needed to unleash this killer move.

"Fortunately, our side has Immortal Gu Houses which can act as fortresses for us to rest and recover. Oh no!" Wu Yong had just returned to rest in Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building when his expression suddenly changed dramatically.

His departure had made Chi Qu Yu's position slightly more eye-catching.

Gu Immortals of other regions might not be able to make use of this, but Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were all experienced experts.

"Chi Qu You, quickly retreat!" Wu Yong transmitted.

Even without his warning, Chi Qu You already sensed something amiss, he quickly retreated.

"Where are you going?" Wan Zi Hong restrained Chi Qu You.

Wu Yong had to stop resting as he flew out.

Zhou Xiong Xin suddenly appeared above Chi Qu You, his five fingers spread out as he grasped.

Immortal battlefield killer move — Rumor Cage!

This was the fastest battlefield killer move in the world, the speed of setting it up was number one in the five regions.

Chi Qu You could not dodge in time, he was trapped in the battlefield.

Zhou Xiong Xin, Zhang Fei Xiong, and Zhu Que Er entered the battlefield, the other Gu Immortals stayed outside, blocking the reinforcement of Wu Yong, Yi Hao Fang, and Ba De.

"Chi Qu You is in danger!"

"Quick, we need to destroy this battlefield."

Wu Yong and the rest were anxious.

However, the rumor cage battlefield had already shrunk to a dot, it vanished. To find it, a lot of effort would be needed, and there were Heavenly Court Gu Immortals around obstructing them.

Immortal killer move — Sitting and Eating the Mountain Empty!

While the Southern Border immortals were trying to save him, Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi worked together again, using their killer move to heavily damage the Southern Border Immortal Gu Houses.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals suffered a great loss while their attention was diverted away.

And within rumor cage, Chi Qu You was in danger, at the brink of life and death.

This was an information path battlefield, Zhou Xiong Xin was the main attacker, while Zhang Fei Xiong and Zhu Que Er had transformation path attainment, they turned into information path immemorial desolate beasts to help with the battle.

Suddenly, Wu Shuang also entered the battlefield.

Human path killer move — Peerless!

This killer move was once used on Duke Long, it was very helpful. This time, it was used on Zhou Xiong Xin who was already amplified by a human path killer move, with this additional boost, his killer moves became even stronger.

Chi Qu You stared with furious eyes but he could not resist them, he was devoured by the information path tigers.

Rumor cage battlefield dissipated, Zhou Xiong Xin and the rest returned to the outside battlefield. Wu Yong and the rest could only see the torn and dismembered remains of Chi Qu You.

A formation path great grandmaster and first supreme elder of Chi clan had died!

Southern Border's Gu Immortals were shaken, such a terrifying sacrifice had happened before their eyes.

"First supreme elder Chi Qu You!"

"He died in battle."

"Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals killed him..."

The morale of Southern Border was rapidly declining.

"Oh no!" Wu Yong had an ugly expression, Chi Qu You's reputation was very high, his death was worse than if they lost Yi Hao Fang or Ba De, it was a huge blow to the Southern Border Gu Immortals' morale.

However, Wu Yong could not do anything.

Even though he had the killer move unlimited wind, Heavenly Court did not let him use it. His special move farewell friend wind could also not be used, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had all been sleeping in the immortal graveyard, he had no opportunity to become 'friends' with them.

"Our situation was tough to begin with, now that Chi Qu You is dead, it is even worse now!"

"What do I do?"

Wu Yong had already tried his best but the situation still left his control gradually.

"Persevere!" The light of determination flashed in his eyes.

"Heavenly Court must not be allowed to repair fate Gu, this is the consensus of all four regions. Western Desert has attacked Emperor City now, Eastern Sea and Northern Plains' Gu Immortals will definitely also take action."

"And Fang Yuan..."

"I'll wait for reinforcements!"

"That's the only way now."

The Emperor City battlefield and Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield were completely suppressed and in a dangerous position, so was the battlefield in Heavenly Court.

Even though Duke Long was unaffected by the human path killer moves' amplification, he was still overwhelming, his strength alone suppressed all of Longevity Heaven's members.

And worse was that he had reinforcements.

"Qin Ding Ling!" Within Calamity Luck Altar, Qi Ci Lang looked at Qin Ding Ling while gritting his teeth.

Qin Ding Ling had recovered with the help of the human path killer moves, she joined the battlefield to assist Duke Long.

She had incredibly strong luck path attainment, she could target Calamity Luck Altar well, Qi Ci Lang and the rest were getting into a tight spot.

With a loud crash, Duke Long's fist defeated another Northern Plains' expert.

He looked at the phantom River of Time as he laughed loudly: "So what if you summon more people?"

"Longevity Heaven!"

"This time, none of you shall escape, you will all die!"

"No matter how many reinforcements you have, it will not change the situation."

Qin Ding Ling raised her head high as she snickered: "Exactly, how can the grand Heavenly Court be defiled by the likes of you!"

Chapter 1933: Arrival of Reinforcements!

"Get him!"

"Don't let him get away!!!"

There was already chaos in the venue of the final competition of the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

Several rank eight Gu Immortals charged down.

Shen Shang's face was pale, he suffered a serious injury instead of unraveling the venerable methods. However, looking at the Central Continent rank eights that pounced down, he still sneered: "Just the few of you want to catch me?"

Next, his body flickered as he vanished.

Central Continent's rank eight Gu Immortals lost sight of their target, they used all sorts of investigative killer moves but could not find any traces.

"Where did he go?"

"Who is he, he is actually able to move freely in Emperor City!"

"This place is under the effect of people's united hearts, he could actually sneak in."

"The five regions are huge, hidden experts are everywhere."

The rank eight Gu Immortals exchanged words and after discussing, they each dispersed to continue their search.

Even if they searched Emperor City completely, even if they demolished it, they still wanted to find Shen Shang.

Shen Shang was currently hiding in a corner of Emperor City, far away from the venue of the final competition.

He was panting, but the fighting spirit in his eyes was not extinguished, instead, like adding fuel to a fire, it was growing stronger and stronger!

"Worthy of venerables, their methods exceeded my expectations." He exclaimed in his head and immediately sent another message to Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan, hold on! Give me some more time and I will definitely be able to unravel this move!" Shen Shang spoke with certainty.

Fang Yuan sneered: "How can I believe you?"

Shen Shang then explained: "I've already found out that the various human path killer moves of Heavenly Court's venerables are based on a massive amount of human will. Without this foundation, no matter how powerful the human path killer moves are, they are useless without enough fuel."

Fang Yuan retorted: "But the human will is stored in Heavenly Court, it is too far from our reach."

Shen Shang smiled lightly: "Precisely so, I deduced another method, instead of eliminating the human will, we should help to develop it instead."

Fang Yuan gained some interest: "Tell me."

Shen Shang then said: "Heavenly Court collected the human will of Central Continent, so their people's united hearts killer move can distinguish between friend and enemy. But if I add the human will of the other four regions, how can they possibly still have united hearts? The Heavenly Court and Central Continent Gu Immortals are also amplified by the killer move heroes among people because of Central Continent's human will. If it contains the human will of the five regions, then heroes among people's effect would also work on the rest of us."

Fang Yuan asked again: "Then how do you do this, how will we channel the human will of the other four regions into it?"

Shen Shang replied calmly: "On one hand, I have already made arrangements in Emperor City. On the other hand, the five regional walls are close to disappearing, not only will the five regions be unified by the earth veins, but the human veins will also be linked. In a way, we have to thank Heavenly Court for their propaganda. Now that the five regions all know that the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention is being held, the will of all five regions is concentrated here, except that Heavenly Court only collected the central part of it."

Fang Yuan was silent for a moment and suddenly said: "Then do it, I can't maintain all of the battlefield, I can only try my best to stall for you. You have to fight for every second!"

"Of course." Shen Shang said without any hesitation.

Emperor City battlefield.

"Kill!" Combat Immortal Sect's Gu Immortals shouted in unison.

Under their maneuvering, the Immortal Gu House Edge Link Camp suddenly surged in speed and rushed towards Western Desert Fang clan's Inquiry Dock.

Inquiry Dock retreated sharply.

Edge Link Camp suddenly shined with a dazzling light, the light condensed into a giant horn that rushed into the sky.

It was Edge Link Camp's killer move — Giant Horn Rush.

Normally speaking, Inquiry Dock would not be afraid of this method, but after the amplification of human path killer move heroes among people, giant horn rush's power doubled!

Inquiry Dock was only an information path Immortal Gu House, it could not resist this fierce attack alone.

Fallen Flower Hall quickly tried to help it and moved closer to Inquiry Dock, but Wind Sweeping Building restrained it.

"We cannot lose Inquiry Dock, our Fang clan's three Immortal Gu Houses can use the battlefield killer move peach blossom maze!" Fang Di Chang quickly gave orders to save it.

Peach blossom maze was able to trap rank eight Gu Immortals, and back then it was even able to trap Divine Bean Palace.

This killer move was famous and all the Western Desert Gu Immortals knew about it. It was just that since the battle started, Central Continent's side had taken the initiative and did not allow Western Desert to set it up, so there was no time to activate peach blossom maze.

Several Western Desert Immortal Gu Houses supported Inquiry Dock at the same time, but at the next moment, Central Continent's lineup changed and formed a large encirclement, separating Inquiry Dock from the reinforcements.

"Damn it!" Fang Di Chang's expression sank, he had to move Divine Bean Palace to help it.

Divine Bean Palace was the support pillar of Western Desert's troops, it should not be moved lightly. Once it was moved, it would cause Western Desert's entire arrangement to change, which would result in a gap to form and allow Central Continent's side to seize the opportunity.

But at this moment, there was nothing that Fang Di Chang could do.

At the sight of Divine Bean Palace moving, the Central Continent Gu Immortals were excited.

"Fang Di Chang fell for it!"

"He is a wisdom path Gu Immortal but the situation is forcing his hand after all."

"Attack, Western Desert's battle arrangement has gone chaotic, if we grab onto this opportunity, we will claim victory!"

Rumble...

Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses erupted with a frenzy of attacks, it was like a tsunami that crashed towards Western Desert's forces.

"Oh no." This scene was so devastating that even Fang Di Chang's expression changed.

Western Desert's defeat was right before his eyes!

Boom!

With a loud explosion, a grand Immortal Gu House entered the battlefield.

It was larger than Divine Bean Palace, with giant red-gold bricks and black-gold tiles around its walls, countless statues were embedded on the surface of the palace, each one of them was lifelike and full of brilliance.

"This is?!"

"Rank eight Immortal Gu House — Myriad Statue Palace!"

Central Continent's attacks froze for a moment.

At the next moment, from within Myriad Statue Palace came the voice of Thousand Transformations Ancestor: "Central Continent's Heavenly Court is simply going overboard! This time, I, Thousand Transformations Ancestor, will make you pay with your blood!!!"

At the crucial moment, Thousand Transformations came to the rescue and finally salvaged the battle at Emperor City.

Fang Di Chang let out a long breath and muttered softly: "There's still some hope left in this fight."

Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield.

Rumble!

With a loud bang, a corner of the five regional limit formation broke again, it was like a pavilion that was see-through on all sides, the inside was visible to all.

The Formation Spirit was so weak that it was nearly transparent, Zhan Bu Du was heavily injured, he only manipulated the formation while kneeling, his seven orifices were bleeding, blood had gathered into a pool below him.

"Once we destroy this formation, there will be no obstacles left."

"Hmph, if you want to find trouble with Heavenly Court, you're all not qualified enough!"

"Mere rats, all of you will become prisoners of our Heavenly Court."

As always, the main forces of Heavenly Court fought fiercely and furiously, their attacks were unceasing and increasingly coordinated, while Southern Border lost the rank eight pillar Chi Qu You, they could barely sustain the fight, they could not protect the five regional limit formation.

"It seems that my life ends here. But I am not going to let you guys have it easy either!" Zhan Bu Du gritted his teeth and decided to use one final move to self-detonate the entire formation.

Roar—!

Just before Zhan Bu Du was about to self-detonate, the loud roar of a dragon could suddenly be heard.

The sound of the dragon resounded throughout heaven and earth, shaking the entire battlefield.

Next, the five-colored smoke swirled violently and was brutally pushed apart by a huge object!

At this moment, Heavenly Court and the Southern Border immortals stared at the newcomer in shock.

It was a giant dragon, unimaginably huge, the dragon head alone was like a chain of hills, and the dragon's body stretched endlessly!

A Gu Immortal's body could not even compare to a piece of the dragon's scales.

"Evil Dragon!"

"It is Di Zang Sheng!"

"Why is it here?"

Di Zang Sheng's dragon eyes swept over the five regional limit formation and the Southern Border immortals, quickly fixing on the main Heavenly Court forces.

Heavenly Court's immortals suddenly felt an extremely strong sense of danger that threatened their lives!

Roar—!

Di Zang Sheng roared again and rushed towards the Heavenly Court immortals.

"It's our reinforcements!" The morale of the Southern Border immortals was boosted.

Wu Yong's eyes narrowed, "Doesn't Di Zang Sheng hate all humans? How can it be manipulated and be an enemy of Heavenly Court? Who's controlling it? Who can manipulate it?"

For some reason, the image of Fang Yuan surfaced in Wu Yong's heart.

"We're finally saved." Zhan Bu Du sprawled on the ground in exhaustion. With the help of Di Zang Sheng, he was saved from the brink of self-detonating.

Heavenly Court battlefield.

Calamity Luck Altar was at its wits' end.

Duke Long's constant bombardment caused a huge accumulation of damage, Calamity Luck Altar was in tatters, Bing Sai Chuan who was controlling it suffered heavy injuries, Qi Ci Lang had already fainted long ago.

What caused this was just not Duke Long's divine might, but also the help of Qin Ding Ling and Fairy Zi Wei.

Qin Ding Ling was able to use luck path to effectively disintegrate the defenses of Calamity Luck Altar. Fairy Zi Wei collected information from the battle and made deductions on the spot, telling Duke Long the best spots to attack.

With these three Gu Immortals working together, Longevity Heaven was in a precarious position. The destruction of Calamity Luck Altar was close at hand.

Once it completely breaks apart, Longevity Heaven will suffer a devastating blow, and the result of the battle in Heavenly Court will be decided!

Far away from Central Great Hall, at the peak of Star Zone Mountain, the two chess players' figures playing against each other emerged at some point in the Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

No matter from any angle, one could only see a side of the faces of these two figures at most.

The woman had peerless beauty, while the man looked as cold as ice.

It was a contest between two venerables!

"It seems that our side has won this game by a little again." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable smiled slightly.

Limitless Demon Venerable nodded: "Heavenly Court awakened so many Gu Immortals in advance this time, aren't you afraid of getting completely assimilated by heaven's will?"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable grasped a chess piece: "I still have some time. It seems that the person you are waiting for will not appear. Even if he arrives, it is too late."

Limitless Demon Venerable was silent but suddenly, his eyes shined with mysterious light, he seemed to have sensed something as he stood up and turned around to look at the Heavenly Court battlefield far away.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was stunned, she followed Limitless Demon Venerable's direction and saw that white profound light started to appear in the battlefield, with a shrill sound, a tunnel was opened.

Myriad Year Flying Warship flew in through the tunnel, a Gu Immortal was standing on it.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had a deep gaze as she analyzed, this Gu Immortal was dressed in a white robe, his sleeves were fluttering and his black hair was hanging down to his waist like a waterfall. His face was extremely handsome, almost delicate like a beauty, and what attracted people's attention most were his eyes, which were pitch-black as if they were connected to the ninth layer of the deepest abyss, devouring all light that approached it.

Fairy Zi Wei's body shook as she said uncontrollably: "Fang Yuan!"

"So this is Fang Yuan." Qin Ding Ling coldly smiled.

"Regardless of who comes here, you cannot do anything!" Duke Long did not raise his head, he still stared at Calamity Luck Altar as he tried to deal the fatal blow.

"Is that so?" On Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan smiled lightly as he observed the battlefield.

He raised his hand slowly, his fingers outstretched as he aimed at the battlefield.

At the next moment, the killer move that he prepared for a long time burst out, grand qi surged as heaven and earth shook intensely.

Rumble!

The colossal qi wall that enveloped Heavenly Court lasted for a few breaths of time before shattering into countless qi currents, they were all drawn by a formless force into Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

At once, the entire place went silent!

Fairy Zi Wei and Qin Ding Ling stared in a daze as they shouted in disbelief:

"Rank eight?!"

"Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's qi wall was actually..."

Duke Long slowly raised his head, he ignored Calamity Luck Altar as his gaze became fixed on Fang Yuan, his expression was completely different from before.

Next, they heard Fang Yuan's plain voice reverberate in their ears: "This unlimited qi sea killer move was modified by me, how is the power? Please do give me your honest opinion."

"Hahaha." Loud laughter was heard from within Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

Limitless Demon Venerable raised his head as he laughed in joy and satisfaction.

"Look." He pointed at Fang Yuan, turning around to face Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: "The person I am waiting for is here!"

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sighed deeply, she had a complex expression: "Indeed, he... has arrived."

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan appeared in the battlefield personally, charging into Heavenly Court!

Chapter 1934: Fang Yuan Fights Duke Long

Heavenly Court battlefield.

"This is the crucial person — Fang Yuan?" Bing Sai Chuan muttered, looking at Fang Yuan who was high in the sky.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady stared with their mouths wide open: "Didn't they say Fang Yuan was rank seven? When did he reach rank eight?"

"This lad!" Mao Li Qiu gritted its teeth, feeling deep emotions inside.

The last time it met Fang Yuan was in Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan had used the river to escape. Other than that, he was weaker than Mao Li Qiu.

But in their next encounter, he was able to destroy the primordial qi wall!

Without the primordial qi wall, Calamity Luck Altar was like a fish in water, it regained freedom.

The restraint holding them back was gone, they could see ways to attack and advance now.

"Oh no!" Fairy Zi Wei's face turned pale, she could not think of a countermeasure immediately.

"Attack—!" At the next moment, Bing Sai Chuan's voice resounded from Calamity Luck Altar.

The Northern Plains immortals summoned using call of the ancient all became energized, their eyes shined with bright light as they split up and attacked the surroundings.

These Northern Plains brutes had been suppressed for too long!

Only Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, and Qin Ding Ling were here, the three of them could not deal with so many Gu Immortals at once.

At the crucial moment, there was a tiger roar as a Shabi emerged. There was the cry of a crane as a green jade crane flew out.

These were two legendary immemorial beasts of Heavenly Court, one was Shabi Ninety-five, the other was Ruan Dan.

The two legendary immemorial beasts joined the battle, desperately blocking the Northern Plains immortals.

Fairy Zi Wei quickly returned to Central Great Hall, she needed to protect Old Man Zheng Yuan who was there.

Meanwhile, Qin Ding Ling charged towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stood on Myriad Year Flying Warship as he observed the battlefield, seeing the scattered Northern Plains immortals, he nodded in satisfaction.

In order to destroy the qi wall, he had prepared this move for a long time.

Unlimited qi sea was the move that made Qi Xiang famous throughout the world back then. It was grand and vast, complex and everchanging, it could attack and defend, it was a comprehensive method.

It had potential for growth on its own, capable of growing stronger by gathering all the different qi in the world. After Qi Xiang created this move, he collected all sorts of qi and stored them inside the immortal aperture, including life qi, death qi, sword qi, blade qi, dusk qi, dawn qi...

The more types of qi gathered on large scales, the stronger unlimited qi sea was.

Not only would this move expend immortal essence, it also used up the stored qi. Even if they were not used, as time passed, these qi would naturally dissipate slowly.

Back then, Qi Sea grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit used this move to survive many calamities and tribulations that the grotto-heaven faced, among which were myriad tribulations! When Fang Yuan was attacked by this move, unlimited qi sea was already weakened to its limit, even the heavenly spirit had to hibernate due to injuries.

Thus, the actual power of unlimited qi sea was not truly at the level when Fang Yuan saw it.

Since rebirth, Fang Yuan had been thinking of the method to destroy primordial qi wall.

After getting unlimited qi sea, he acutely sensed that this move was a counter to the qi wall.

However, the primordial qi wall was a venerable method, even if Fang Yuan had unlimited qi sea and great grandmaster qi path attainment level, he would need more than a decade to unravel the qi wall method while fully focused on making deductions.

The solution to this problem was Duke Long.

In order to recruit Qi Sea Ancestor, Duke Long used Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's qi path killer moves as bait. Even though Fang Yuan only obtained half of it, because of his insistence, the content included the primordial qi wall as well.

With it, Fang Yuan used the light of wisdom from wisdom Gu to barely deduce and modify unlimited qi sea before the great battle.

As for how Fang Yuan invaded Heavenly Court, he used heaven form. He added the time path killer move shrink time into heaven form, allowing him to rapidly invade the target area. After all, he had deep attainment in theft path and time path. As the Fang Di Chang clone was also comprehending the theft path Immortal Gu House, he gained a lot of inspiration and insight.

The qi wall was too crucial of an element!

With this qi wall, Heavenly Court's enemies only had three routes to choose from, those were the paths carved out by past Demon Venerables.

But once the qi wall vanishes, they could roam freely in Heavenly Court, with their current defense, they could not guard against everyone.

The situation of the battle in Heavenly Court immediately was overturned.

Once Fang Yuan took action, he gave Longevity Heaven and himself the initiative, they now had control over the battle.

"Fang Yuan, let me, Qin Ding Ling, see your skills." Qin Ding Ling turned into a golden ray of light as she flew in the sky, towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan took a glance at her, this was their first encounter.

She was taller than normal people, her shoulders were broad, she stood straight and had a heroic aura. She had an outstanding air, especially her long legs, she was like innate royalty that ruled above the common man. Her nose bridge was tall and a little sharp, her lips were thin and her eyes were narrow and long, her gaze was emitting a cold light now. She was not a traditional beauty, she had an authoritative aura that was bred naturally within her, people would lower their heads and not dare to look at her directly, it was as if they could only look at her feet in order to not offend her.

"No wonder Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose you as his concubine back then." Fang Yuan replied plainly, Qin Ding Ling's attacks became even fiercer instantly.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he manipulated Myriad Year Flying Warship to move quickly, evading Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling's heart jumped, she cried out in dismay internally.

She had great strength, having converted from metal path to luck path, her battle strength was second to Duke Long and nobody else in Heavenly Court, she had no clear weaknesses. However, her speed was inferior to Myriad Year Flying Warship.

At this moment, rapids surged below Myriad Year Flying Warship, pushing this rank eight Immortal Gu House to move through the battlefield, heading directly to the immortal battlefield.

Fang Yuan was passive earlier, but once he attacked, he aimed at Heavenly Court's weakness! The greatest weakness!

At this moment, even Duke Long could not let him pass.

The immortal graveyard was the most important place in Heavenly Court.

Even Duke Long did not know how many Gu Immortals were slumbering inside.

This was Heavenly Court's greatest wealth, it was their immense accumulation over millions of years since creation.

In the previous life, even though Longevity Heaven reached Heaven Overseeing Tower, they could not threaten the immortal graveyard. But now that the qi wall was broken, there were countless paths to take, they could approach the immortal graveyard.

Duke Long gave up on Calamity Luck Altar, he flew rapidly and blocked the path of Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Behind Myriad Year Flying Warship, Qin Ding Ling was chasing relentlessly.

At once, Fang Yuan was encircled by Duke Long and Qin Ding Ling.

"Don't worry, I'll help you!"

"Protect this person, he is the crucial person that Ancestor Giant Sun mentioned!"

"That's right, even if we die, we need to protect him."

The surrounding Northern Plains immortals gathered towards Fang Yuan.

Bing Sai Chuan did not hesitate, he immediately mobilized Calamity Luck Altar to reinforce Fang Yuan. Right now, they had the common enemy Heavenly Court, they needed to work together.

Since Fang Yuan came to help them, Bing Sai Chuan had to return the favor, they had to resist Heavenly Court's two strongest experts.

Bing Sai Chuan had no better option now.

If he let Duke Long kill Fang Yuan now, not only would they lose this source of battle strength, the rank eight Immortal Gu House Myriad Year Flying Warship would also become unmanned.

Facing this unprecedented attack, Fang Yuan had a calm expression. However, when he was about to use his method against the enemies, he suddenly felt a sense of fire qi emerging in his heart, causing him to burn with fury.

Next, a sense of sorrow qi pervaded his body, causing his defenses to fall rapidly.

Next, a lump of old qi entered his body and mind, causing his lifespan to decrease continuously.

There was also poison qi that spread around him, causing a lethal threat.

Unlucky qi crowded above his head, causing his luck to fall.

Silly qi filled his mind, the results of the collision of thoughts in his mind were all stupid ideas...

Frost qi entered his body, causing his movements to slow down...

All sorts of qi tangled around him, Fang Yuan's battle strength fell to rock bottom, in just a few breaths of time, he fell to the level of a rank seven Gu Immortal, after some more time, he was even weaker than an ordinary rank six Gu Immortal.

Duke Long saw Fang Yuan's aura weakening rapidly as he was surrounded by all sorts of qi, he felt overjoyed: "This is Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's method! Fang Yuan destroyed the qi wall, causing this move to attack him."

He had cultivated Primordial Origin's true inheritance after all, he could tell what had happened.

But at the next moment, Duke Long saw a mild light shoot out behind him, it resembled a chess piece, rapidly entering Fang Yuan's body.

Instantly, all of the qi around his body vanished, as if the former scene was an illusion.

Duke Long's body and mind shook, he turned around at lightning speed, seeing that Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette had stood up from his seat for the first time in Imperfection Regret Pavilion, looking over at this battlefield from afar, Duke Long's pupils shrunk slightly.

At the crucial moment, Limitless Demon Venerable made a move, cleansing all of the qi currents around Fang Yuan's body.

The Northern Plains immortals saw this and their hearts eased.

Bing Sai Chuan was a little puzzled: "So Fang Yuan had a method to make Limitless Demon Venerable turn around. How did he do it? I did not see him make any actions earlier."

Immortal killer move — Dragon Roaring Wave.

Duke Long opened his mouth and roared loudly.

The sound waves of the dragon roar spread out rapidly, all over the place.

Immortal killer move — Body Flicker.

At the next moment, Duke Long teleported along with the dragon sound waves, directly appearing in front of Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan was still standing on the bow, the two were less than an arm's length away.

One was the master of Red Lotus, the dragonman ancestor, Duke Long. The other was the inheritor of Red Lotus, the new dragonman ancestor, Fang Yuan!

"Oh no!"

"Fang Yuan is overconfident."

"Quickly return to the Immortal Gu House!"

The Northern Plains immortals felt like they were falling into despair, they screamed. Duke Long's divine might was engraved in their minds, nobody could face him head on. Even Calamity Luck Altar, the legendary Immortal Gu House that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable personally created, could not resist Duke Long's offensive methods. Longevity Heaven's members were suppressed by Duke Long's power, they had to hide inside Calamity Luck Altar, not daring to fight outside.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Claw Strike!

Duke Long snorted coldly, his right hand turned into a dragon claw as he slashed at Fang Yuan's skull.

Slap.

At the next moment, there was a soft sound as Fang Yuan raised his furry left arm, blocking Duke Long's dragon claw.

"He... he blocked it?!"

Be it Northern Plains' immortals, Qin Ding Ling, or Fairy Zi Wei, they were all stunned.

Nobody had ever been able to resist Duke Long in a frontal assault, but he had managed to block it with such ease.

Fang Yuan's appearance was completely changed, he turned into a bandit monkey.

Bandit monkeys were of strength path, their fur was golden and black tiger stripes covered their body. Fur grew out from their waist naturally to cover the crotch and the butt area, just like a kilt made of skin.

Bandit monkeys respected strength and arm wrestling was their main social activity. Young monkeys could arm wrestle immediately after being born. Arm wrestling was not only a game for bandit monkeys, it was also a commonly used method to resolve disputes.

There were Gu Immortals who recognized the bandit monkey, feeling surprised: "Since when did bandit monkeys become so strong?"

Ordinary immemorial bandit monkeys could not resist Duke Long's attack, if they acted like Fang Yuan, their left arm would have been cut off on the spot.

Fang Yuan's transformation was not so simple of course.

Before this, he had already used the killer move myriad beings assimilation transformation.

This was the ultimate method of Beast Calamity Immortal, it contained the highest profundity of transformation path, able to turn dao marks of all other paths into transformation path dao marks.

How many dao marks did Fang Yuan have now?

Qi path had over a million, refinement path had three hundred thousand, transformation path had two hundred thousand, and that was not all, they were just the three highest paths.

Just these alone, after using myriad beings assimilation transformation, gave him one million and five hundred thousand transformation path dao marks.

After Fang Yuan transformed into the bandit monkey, all of these transformation path dao marks turned into strength path dao marks.

One million and five hundred thousand strength path dao marks!

With just the dao mark amplification alone, Fang Yuan could resist Duke Long's killer move.

Duke Long's dragon claw strike landed on Fang Yuan's left arm, it felt like he was punching a mountain.

A sense of danger appeared in Duke Long's mind, but Fang Yuan's right fist had already been launched.

Boom!

With a loud sound, Duke Long felt like he was a paper boat riding a ferocious wave, he felt like a mountain had slammed into him. An unimaginable force caused him to fly away at a speed that could not be observed with the naked eye.

Duke Long flew like a comet, crashing into the ground at lightning speed, with a loud crash, the surroundings shook, a huge dust cloud spread out.

Everyone was silent!

This time, fear and disbelief appeared on the faces of the Northern Plains and Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Everyone's attention was on Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stood at the bow of his ship while transformed into the bandit monkey, he looked down plainly at the pit he created.

It was the pit created by Duke Long who had been sent flying, it was thirty feet deep!

Chapter 1935: Star Constellation Versus Limitless

Ever since the start of the battle, this was the first time anyone had seen Duke Long be sent flying far away from an attack.

Not only did Fang Yuan defend against Duke Long's attack, he even retaliated and sent him flying!

This was far out of anyone's expectations.

"He actually became so strong! What sort of growth speed is this!!" Mao Li Qiu opened its mouth, it stood up subconsciously, no longer lying on the ground.

"The crucial person that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is waiting for... indeed, he lives up to Ancestor's expectations!" Bing Sai Chuan sighed with a complex expression.

Unknowingly, Qin Ding Ling's speed had fallen as she chased after Fang Yuan.

What a joke!

Fang Yuan sent Duke Long flying, what did that mean?

Even though Qin Ding Ling was strong, she knew her limits, she knew the difference between Duke Long and her. Back then, in order to perceive Duke Long's luck, she paid a huge price and had to rest for many days to recover. Right now, the result of this collision eliminated any thought she had of observing Fang Yuan's luck.

Qin Ding Ling was in quite an awkward predicament now.

She wanted to fight and kill Fang Yuan earlier, but now, after seeing this, oh heavens! What a fierce person!

Qin Ding Ling directly stopped moving, she did not dare to approach Fang Yuan anymore.

The transformation path cultivation level that Fang Yuan displayed earlier showed that close combat was not his weakness, it was his strength instead.

Qin Ding Ling changed her mind instantly, she decided to assist Duke Long instead, she did not want to fight Fang Yuan directly anymore.

"This is a monster!"

"To think that in the future after I died, such a demonic immortal would appear, this is so interesting."

"Let's go, he does not need our help."

Northern Plains' immortals quickly turned around, they left, spreading out to the surroundings.

Fairy Zi Wei frowned tightly, she had a heavy heart. Northern Plains' immortals were moving around all over the place, all of them had their own chosen routes to advance, if they destroyed everything along their path, how could Heavenly Court stop them all?

Even if a large number of Gu Immortals woke up in the immortal graveyard now, they would need time to gather their Immortal Gu, it was too late now.

"I can only defend the most important areas now!" Fairy Zi Wei gritted her teeth, she made a painful decision, deciding to abandon the deadweight.

Dust clouds dissipated, within the huge pit, Duke Long stood up slowly.

"You really surprise me time and time again, Fang Yuan." Duke Long raised his head to look at Fang Yuan, he had a calm expression but his tone was eerie.

He was hit by Fang Yuan's fist directly, his chest only caved in slightly. While he spoke, his wound healed completely as his chest returned to normal.

He was the dragonman ancestor after all, his recovery speed was shockingly fast.

Fang Yuan looked at Duke Long as well, upon seeing this, his expression did not change.

Everything was within his expectations.

Duke Long was not heavily injured, the attack earlier had a huge commotion but the effect on the enemy was small. He had only caught Duke Long off guard.

After all, Fang Yuan did not use any immortal killer moves then. He only raised his fist and attacked with the amplification of strength path dao marks.

With the support of over a million strength path dao marks, Fang Yuan's bandit monkey form had immense strength, Duke Long could not compare to it. But he had many immortal killer moves defending him, he was tough as steel, even if he was sent flying, he was still intact.

Below Myriad Year Flying Warship, the water of the River of Time surged as this time path Immortal Gu House moved suddenly, it was like a huge flying sword, tearing through space and creating a dazzling rainbow behind it, it pierced towards the immortal graveyard.

Duke Long snorted coldly, a frenzied light flashed in his eyes as his deep killing intent surged without concealment, it was as if a fierce tide was raging.

He was now in a passive spot, with Fang Yuan's attack, he had no choice but to defend, this was a terrible feeling.

Once the primordial qi wall was broken, Fang Yuan's side gained the initiative, their target was the immortal graveyard.

Duke Long was sent flying by Fang Yuan's fist earlier, his air of intimidation took a beating, he decided to focus on the enemy ahead now. The truth was in front of him, trying to engage in close combat with Fang Yuan in order to kill him was an impossible dream.

Immortal killer move — Qi Breath Mountain!

Rumble!

A grand qi current gathered and formed into a translucent mountain.

The mountain was hundreds of li large as it slammed down.

Fang Yuan was at the bottom of the mountain now, raising his head to look at it, the mountain pressed down like the entire world, he could not evade it.

Fang Yuan did not intend to evade it either.

He stopped his bandit monkey transformation as he turned into a majestic astral wind flying heavenly boar!

Astral wind flying heavenly boar lived in the sky, they were qi path beasts that could fly freely. They were agile like flying fish, they had agility incomparable with their boar bodies, they could charge into the heavenly wind qi wall with ease. With a leap, they could enter the heavenly wind qi wall and swim inside like fish in water.

Fang Yuan's four legs stepped on Myriad Year Flying Warship, he did not raise his head, he only growled slightly.

Immortal killer move — Rampaging Qi Roar!

This was a qi path killer move but it originated from Lang Ya Sect's treasury.

In the past, when Lang Ya land spirit controlled Heavenly Giant Solor, he used this move against the sharp tusk boar, killing this ancient desolate beast with one move on the spot.

Now that Fang Yuan used it, with his one million and five hundred thousand qi path dao marks, the power had risen by one thousand five hundred times!

Boom!!

The qi breath mountain exploded from Fang Yuan's roar, countless currents spread out and formed tornadoes that swept the battlefield.

His killer move was broken, Duke Long suffered a backlash.

But this Dao Guardian of Red Lotus Demon Venerable still had great morale after suffering a setback, he used another move.

Immortal killer move — Qi Current Scissors!

He raised both fists, spreading out his ten fingers.

Countless pale qi currents moved out from his palms, they slashed towards Fang Yuan like thin threads.

In a few breaths of time, tens of thousands of pale white thread qi currents moved like a torrent or swarm of moths, approaching from all over the place.

Every qi current was like a blade, even if an immemorial desolate beast faced this move, they would be covered in cuts and injuries, until all of their flesh was removed and only a skeleton was left.

Against this move, Fang Yuan's astral wind flying heavenly boar form was not useful, he changed his form again.

This time, he turned into a crane.

It was a qi path immortal beast as well, single qi crane.

The flying crane was as large as a horse, it was beautiful and had a long proud neck, its wings were huge like two capes, spreading out on the bow of Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Fang Yuan spread his wings and waved them, at once, thousands of feathers gave off shining light.

At the next moment, immortal killer move divine flick[1] was ready to strike, Fang Yuan unleashed it.

Cling cling cling...

Countless shrill sounds could be heard as qi currents shot out of his feathers, crashing into Duke Long's qi current scissors.

As the two offensive methods collided, most of them were dispersed by each other, only a small amount got past and hit Duke Long and Myriad Year Flying Warship respectively.

No matter which side, against such trivial lingering attacks, they did not even blink.

Immortal killer move — Moving Qi Ring!

Fang Yuan used another move as his beak opened, he blew as white qi came out.

The white qi spread out rapidly, entangling with the back of Myriad Year Flying Warship, causing its speed to rise sharply, shooting forward.

Duke Long's expression changed, he realized the problem and quickly chased.

According to conventional wisdom, moving qi ring was a qi path killer move, it would not be useful when it supported a time path Immortal Gu House. But Fang Yuan had modified this move himself, it was rank eight. With the support of a vast number of qi path dao marks, its power rose by a thousand times, it pushed Myriad Year Flying Warship forward while defying common logic!

Fang Yuan quickly got past the several Northern Plains immortals in front, he reached the immortal graveyard before anyone else.

Looking at the immortal graveyard, it was wide and large, there were countless gravestones on the lush grassland, each of these gravestones were different, some were golden, some were short, some did not even have gravestones but were half exposed coffins instead that were buried under the soil.

The sacred atmosphere of dignity and solemnity, filled with history, enveloped the immortal graveyard.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he turned into the bandit monkey again, ready to attack the immortal graveyard again.

At this moment, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette sighed in Imperfection Regret Pavilion, grabbing three chess pieces and tossing them out.

The pieces did not attack Fang Yuan, they fused into the formation here.

Fairy Zi Wei was inside the formation core now, she controlled Star Constellation Chessboard to observe the situation.

After these pieces fell into Star Constellation Chessboard, Fairy Zi Wei felt the power of this formation rise as it broke its limit, reaching an unimaginable level!

Fairy Zi Wei was overjoyed, she quickly activated the formation and aimed it at Fang Yuan.

A huge starlight pillar shined down as Fang Yuan and Myriad Year Flying Warship vanished within the starlight.

At the next moment, another starlight pillar appeared behind Duke Long as Fang Yuan and Myriad Year Flying Warship appeared.

With the help of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette, Heavenly Court's formation gained the ability to teleport people of Fang Yuan and Duke Long's level.

"This is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's method?" Fang Yuan noticed the situation and let out a breath of air, this did not happen in the previous life.

"I have so many dao marks but the starlight pillar can still teleport me forcefully. Impressive! However, I'm afraid this distance is its limit?" Cold light shined in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Next, he saw that several Northern Plains immortals were also forcefully teleported away from the immortal graveyard.

But these people vanished from Heavenly Court directly, they were likely sent outside.

Fang Yuan looked at other places.

A few Northern Plains immortals had already succeeded, they either destroyed resource points or Immortal Gu Houses.

He immediately realized something else: "It seems that the formation's power is limited even after receiving the help of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. It can only allow Heavenly Court to defend some important areas."

Even so, it was enough for now.

Heavenly Court finally stabilized the situation, their losses were not severe.

Within Imperfection Regret Pavilion, Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette turned around and looked at Star Constellation Immortal Venerable: "You are quite generous, using three pieces like that."

"But now, you have the disadvantage in this game." Saying so, Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette smiled, he returned to his seat and sat down calmly.

"Back then, I threatened to destroy Heavenly Court and forced you to accept this game. A million years passed, our powers weave and influence this chessboard, we have been stuck at a deadlock. Now, I only used one piece but you used three, if I attack now, you will be in trouble." Limitless Demon Venerable smiled as he placed his finger at one spot on the chessboard, a brand new chess piece appeared on the board when he retracted his finger.

This chess piece contained the power of Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette, the spot it occupied was where one of the three pieces that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable used earlier was situated.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette smiled indifferently: "Back then, your main body wanted to gain the heaven path foundation of Heavenly Court, so you set up this game. This chess game secretly connects to the Dao field that you created in your later years, Crazed Demon Cave, the more you win, the more heaven path foundation you gain, and the more helpful it will be for the derivation over in Crazed Demon Cave."

"That's right, you're absolutely right." Limitless Demon Venerable admitted to his greed, this was an open scheme, there was nothing to hide.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette smiled again: "There was no helping it in that situation, so what if you gained some heaven path foundation? Times are different now, your main body's lifespan ran out long ago, you are already dead."

Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette was slightly stunned before his eyes shined with bright light, he realized: "Heavenly Court made arrangements in my Crazed Demon Cave as well."

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette praised truthfully: "Crazed Demon Cave is uniquely blessed, the venerables that came after you were unwilling to destroy it, a few of them even left behind their Dao fields. Over there, the few of us will definitely have a huge contest, but that is something for the future."

[1] Originally Qi Zai's mortal killer move from chapter 1040. Back

Chapter 1936: Heavenly Court's Three Elites Against Fang Yuan

"It seems that to destroy Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard, I will need to destroy this transportation formation first!" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed like lightning, he started at the formation far away.

The Myriad Year Flying Warship below his feet moved according to his will, the ship shot out like a large flying sword towards the formation.

Fairy Zi Wei was guarding the formation in the Central Hall.

Seeing Fang Yuan's assault, she took a deep cold breath, she felt immense pressure towering over her!

"Fang Yuan, with me here, you will not move freely!" Duke Long roared as he stepped forward to block Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Seeing this, Fairy Zi Wei let out a sigh of relief: "Thankfully, we have Lord Duke Long guarding us!"

Boom!

Fang Yuan and Duke Long clashed, Duke Long was sent flying while Fang Yuan and Myriad Year Flying Warship only flew back by a thousand steps.

The aftermath of the combat stirred up thousands of storm clouds and set off monstrous air currents, the aftermath of which was so vast that it resembled a hurricane. The rank eight Gu Immortals were swept and blown away by the aftershocks. Even Calamity Luck Altar halted, Bing Sai Chuan and the others inside were unable to stand on their feet firmly, their bodies were shaking violently.

Subconsciously, everyone started to avoid Fang Yuan and Duke Long.

"Fang Yuan was blocked."

"As expected, only a monster can block a monster!"

"Let the two of them fight."

Only Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth and forced herself to fly over, intending to reinforce Duke Long as his support.

Fang Yuan and Duke Long clashed again, tornadoes formed, lightning flashed and thunder roared.

Because of heavenly dragon's last stand, Duke Long was getting stronger by the minute! Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had a large number of dao marks and Myriad Year Flying Warship, he had the upper hand for now.

Duke Long continued to move back as the two of them fought closer and closer to the teleportation formation.

Immortal killer move — Self-Moving Dragon Qi Wall!

Left without a choice, Duke Long roared as he spread his arms, a huge invisible qi wall appeared before Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan pushed Myriad Year Flying Warship to charge forward, after moving for a few dozen steps, he was stopped by the qi wall, unable to move further.

Duke Long started to cultivate Primordial Origin's true inheritance long ago, he naturally knew about the killer move qi wall. This move was modified by him, Fang Yuan could vaguely see countless qi currents inside the wall. These currents were all dragon-shaped, the dragon heads spun around while chasing the tail, creating countless whirlpools.

These dragon-shaped qi currents were very profound, they could reduce the force of external impacts and greatly increase the qi wall's durability.

Duke Long's self-moving dragon qi wall could not be as firm as the primordial qi wall but it was very durable, it successfully obstructed Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan used unlimited qi sea to destroy the primordial qi wall, he had modified it according to his understanding of the qi wall in the first place.

Currently, Fang Yuan knew little about this dragon qi wall, it was impossible to replicate his former success now.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with brilliance, since he could not unravel this move, he had to use force instead.

He turned into a bandit monkey again, stretching his arms as he pushed forward.

Immortal killer move — Strength Path Giant Hand!

Rumble!

The surrounding thousand feet of air was pushed side, two translucent hands that were the size of mountains crashed towards Duke Long's qi wall with immeasurable might.

Within the qi wall, Duke Long raised his head and spread out his arms, sustaining his qi wall killer move.

The two strength path giant hands moved for several hundred steps before becoming slower, unable to advance further.

Fang Yuan and Duke Long had solemn expressions as they exerted strength, falling into a deadlock.

"Good chance!" Seeing this, Qin Ding Ling realized that her chance to attack had arrived.

In the earlier battle, she could not find a chance to attack, she could only prepare her killer moves.

Once the chance arrived, she immediately threw out a small golden dagger.

The dagger was only the size of a thumb, it flew into the air and grew larger as it moved, by the time it reached the top of Fang Yuan's head, it was already the size of a horse carriage.

Swish swish swish.

The golden blade swung down, attempting to slice off Fang Yuan's luck advantage.

But Cooking Luck Pot suddenly appeared above Fang Yuan, it flew up and resisted the attack of the golden blade.

Clang clang clang…

The golden blade landed on Cooking Luck Pot, golden sparks appeared due to the collision.

In a few breaths of time, the golden blade slashed for several hundred times before fading away on its own.

Cooking Luck Pot completely defended against this killer move, even though cracks appeared on the surface, it was intact overall.

The golden blade was a rank eight luck path killer move, while Cooking Luck Pot had been elevated to a rank seven Immortal Gu House, it could resist rank eight attacks.

"Cooking Luck Pot?" Qin Ding Ling exclaimed in shock, recognizing it immediately.

She was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's concubine after all, she knew about the existence of Cooking Luck Pot.

"Your Cooking Luck Pot is only rank seven, even if it can block me ten times, can it stop me twenty times? Thirty times?" Qin Ding Ling snorted coldly in her mind, attacking Fang Yuan furiously.

Cooking Luck Pot was only rank seven, even though it could resist rank eight, Qin Ding Ling was not an ordinary rank eight Gu Immortal, she was specialized in luck path. Cooking Luck Pot could block her now but the duration would not be long.

Fang Yuan noticed this too, he immediately withdrew his strength path giant hands and stopped this immortal killer move.

Duke Long was still sustaining the qi wall, he could not attack, Fang Yuan was able to retreat with ease.

"Qin Ding Ling, you did well." Duke Long praised secretly.

In the deadlock earlier, Duke Long was in a disadvantage, over half of his dragon spirals in the qi wall had dissipated.

Thankfully, Qin Ding Ling interfered and forced Fang Yuan to retreat.

Thoughts clashed like lightning in Fang Yuan's mind as he analyzed the situation.

He had abundant methods, but as long as the transportation formation existed, he could not use most of his methods casually.

Once he activates these methods and Fairy Zi Wei tries to teleport him forcefully, it might greatly disrupt Fang Yuan, causing his activation to fail.

Once his killer move fails, he would suffer varying extents of backlash.

If Fang Yuan suffered a backlash now, the consequences would be unthinkable!

Because of his dao mark amplification, the power was at least one thousand five hundred times! The backlash would be equally amplified.

And more terrifyingly, the sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks, Fang Yuan had to endure the complete backlash. That way, as long as Fang Yuan faced one backlash, he would likely die.

Only moves like strength path giant hand with low activation time could be used as they only needed few thoughts to maintain. Even if the killer move was destroyed, only the strength path giant hands would break apart, the Gu Immortal's own backlash would be very marginal.

"In that case, let me try another move." Fang Yuan began to prepare his killer move.

He cultivated all paths, he had abundant methods, in this regard, even Duke Long and Thunder Ghost True Monarch, these dual cultivators, could not match up.

In a few breaths of time, Fang Yuan's killer move was prepared.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self!

Swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh…

Countless Fang Yuan spread out into the sky from Myriad Year Flying Warship, a ten thousand person army was formed instantly.

The original myriad self killer move was turned into an Immortal Gu recipe by Fang Yuan, in which he refined Immortal Gu Myriad Self.

But the myriad self killer move that Fang Yuan used now was not the original version, it was a human path killer move that used myriad self Immortal Gu as the core!

At the next moment, all of the Fang Yuan clones charged towards the qi wall.

Their strength was lower than the main body of course, but because his main body had too many dao marks, all of these myriad self clones all had at least desolate beast level battle strength.

After using this killer move, Fang Yuan gained a desolate beast army that numbered to ten thousand. All of these clones were controlled by Fang Yuan with ease, as if they were extensions of his limbs.

A portion of the myriad self army charged towards the qi wall, some charged at Qin Ding Ling, while the bulk of them got past the qi wall and attacked the transportation formation behind instead.

Even though Duke Long's qi wall was strong, it could not compare to the primordial qi wall. Duke Long's heart jumped, he tried to cancel this move but Fang Yuan's main body came charging with Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Duke Long grunted as he dispelled that thought, continuing to maintain the qi wall.

In a battle between experts, activating killer moves was not easy, but dispelling them was similarly difficult.

On the other end, Qin Ding Ling was surrounded by Fang Yuan's clones as they fought. Qin Ding Ling was very powerful, these clones were no threat to her, but they were enough to distract her, she had to waste time and effort to deal with them.

Fairy Zi Wei took in a deep breath of shock.

She instantly realized, this was a huge test to her. If she failed the test, the transportation formation would be destroyed, it would cause a series of problems, the entire battle situation would crumble, the plan to repair fate Gu would fail!

"There is no time to mobilize Heavenly Court's forces. I can only rely on myself!" Fairy Zi Wei had a determined expression as she did her best, instilling all of her attention into the formation.

She was wholeheartedly concentrating!

Star Constellation Chessboard buzzed incessantly, its chess pieces were shining in starlight on the surface of Star Constellation Chessboard, with three of them being the brightest.

These were the three pieces that Star Constellation's silhouette had tossed over earlier!

Fairy Zi Wei's mind had countless thoughts that resembled the starry sky, they shined brightly.

The formation activated, shooting out waves of starlight specks. Countless specks landed on Fang Yuan's clones, very few missed their target, even though Fang Yuan's clones were doing their best to dodge.

As long as they were hit by the starlight specks, they would be teleported outside of Heavenly Court, vanishing instantly.

These clones did not have the killer move heaven form, they could not rejoin the battle.

"Good!" Duke Long and Qin Ding Ling let out sighs of relief.

Fairy Zi Wei did not disappoint them, at the crucial moment, she gave a display of a wisdom path great expert!

Fang Yuan frowned lightly: "This will not do. Fate Gu is slowly being repaired, Heavenly Court has the overall momentum in this battle. Fairy Zi Wei cannot last long but she is planning to stall for time. Over here, I am obstructed by Duke Long and Qin Ding Ling…"

Fang Yuan looked at Longevity Heaven's side again.

These people were obstructed by the transportation formation too, Calamity Luck Altar was charging towards Heaven Overseeing Tower but a starlight pillar was moving them back each time.

"If I ask them to reinforce me, they would receive the same treatment too. Furthermore, if they come here, I will not be able to use my methods freely, I should let them attack the surroundings to pressure and drain Fairy Zi Wei's energy."

Duke Long's qi wall could move, it could not block the myriad self clones but it could block Myriad Year Flying Warship wholeheartedly.

As Fang Yuan fought against Duke Long, he contacted Eastern Sea's immortals.

Heavenly Court's transportation formation had one great weakness, it needed stars as the springboard. Even within Heavenly Court, that was the case, the starlight pillars shot down from white heaven's countless stars.

Fang Yuan could not destroy the transportation formation now, but it was the same if the stars in white heaven were destroyed.

Luckily, a group of Eastern Sea rank eights were there!

Chapter 1937: Rod Transformation!

Eastern Sea's eight Gu Immortals had already arrived in white heaven, they destroyed many stars.

Their ambition was not as large as Southern Border, Northern Plains, and Western Desert, they only wanted to plunder some Central Continent resources and expend its foundation.

Because they were worried that Heavenly Court would send reinforcements to stop them, they targeted the stars in white heaven instead.

Their strategy had coincidentally become the most crucial point in the entire battle right now!

Among them were Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, and the other dragon generals, Wu Shuai did not recall them, they were left in this group, to try to destroy the stars.

Wu Shuai made a wise decision.

If only Shen Cong Sheng, Qing Yue An, Hua Cai Yun, and Song Qi Yuan were left, they might not have enough guts to destroy the stars.

Eastern Sea's eight immortals were quite efficient in destroying the stars.

The eight of them arrived in front of a giant sized star.

The star was so huge that these eight immortals felt very minute.

Heavenly Court scattered countless stars in white heaven, they were mutually connected, creating a web that had its own arrangements.

Each area had a giant star as the formation core, around the giant star were many large sized stars.

And around the large sized stars were countless mid and small sized stars, flying around casually, they did not have fixed locations.

Song Qi Yuan first flew onto the giant star as he shut his eyes, quietly sensing the connection between the stars.

More than ten breaths later, he shut his eyes, activating a light path killer move as he pointed far away.

Each time he pointed, a sharp profound light would shoot out of his finger at lightning speed, vanishing into the horizon.

Far away, mid and small sized stars exploded into smithereens.

This light path killer move was very special, it could trace the source of any light and attack it. It could even target gazes.

In the previous life, Song Qi Yuan used this move to destroy a star that Fang Yuan refined, causing his star eyes Immortal Gu to fail.

In this life, Song Qi Yuan used this move against Heavenly Court, the effect was immediate as well.

After Song Qi Yuan destroyed all of the stars he could sense, he stopped and nodded at Qing Yue An.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Mountain Ranges!

Qing Yue An gave a cry as the phantom image of countless mountains appeared, the entire mountain range crashed into the giant star.

The giant star was huge but it was just an immortal material, under the attack of the rank eight killer move, it shattered and was destroyed, breaking into countless star fragments.

Almost at the same time the giant star was destroyed, Fairy Zi Wei, who was within Heavenly Court's transportation formation, sensed it.

Her expression changed.

The destruction of one giant star was not an issue. Heavenly Court scattered many stars in white heaven, the loss of one was insignificant.

But in this situation, it had a different implication.

Currently, Northern Plains' immortals and Fang Yuan's clones were attacking all the important areas of Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei had to activate the formation to transport them away.

The formation was constantly activated, it was like a person running while keeping a dangerous balance. If the person steps on a rock, no matter how small it is, they would lose their balance and fall, getting injured. The faster they are running, the heavier their injuries when they fall.

The transportation formation was being used so intensely now, if any errors happen when the destroyed star is needed for the process, the transportation formation would be severely damaged by its own backlash, it might get destroyed.

Fairy Zi Wei had thought that these Eastern Sea immortals held the lowest threat to them, but to think that in this situation and time, the eight Eastern Sea immortals were her most fatal threat!

She had to be careful now, any suspicious stars could not be used now.

Fang Yuan acutely sensed the changes in the formation, he attacked wildly while activating myriad self, and also transmitting information to Shen Cong Sheng.

Shen Cong Sheng received Fang Yuan's message and understood Heavenly Court's situation, he became very excited.

He urged the seven immortals: "Now is our best chance, Fang Yuan has already made his move, Heavenly Court cannot divert its attention. The more stars we destroy, the more problems Heavenly Court will face. Heavenly Court's main forces are restrained in Hairy Foot Mountain, while Heavenly Court itself is being attacked by Longevity Heaven and Fang Yuan. If we do well here, we might have a chance of destroying Heavenly Court!"

Shen Cong Sheng's words raised the morale of the other seven immortals, their efficiency went up at once.

Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield.

The sharp sound of phoenix chirping pierced the eardrums and ran through the battlefield.

The source of the sound was Prince Feng Xian's killer move — Phoenix Chirping Divine Flame!

The flames burned with raging intensity, coiling around Di Zang Sheng's body as it was set ablaze.

At the other side, Bai Cang Shui also used her killer move, countless water waves rushed towards Di Zang Sheng's body without stopping even for a moment.

Di Zang Sheng was attacked by more than just these two people, it was just too large, Heavenly Court's immortals had their own area to target and attack.

Di Zang Sheng roared continuously, it was attacked by flames and water, lightning and poison, but it still rushed towards the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation, the attacks of the Heavenly Court immortals did not distract it successfully.

Its performance did not fit historical records, back then, Di Zang Sheng caused chaos and attacked everything in its sight, it was easily drawn away, it had never shown such a clear objective.

"Oh no! This legendary immemorial beast has likely been enslaved." Zhou Xiong Xin shouted.

Heavenly Court's main forces did not have wisdom path Gu Immortals, but Zhou Xiong Xin cultivated information path, he was most skilled at collecting information and clues.

He even had information path killer moves that could mimic wisdom path effects.

After fighting for some time, Zhou Xiong Xin immediately deduced the truth behind Di Zang Sheng.

Di Zang Sheng was attacked by the Heavenly Court immortals, it was covered in injuries. In terms of defense, it was inferior to Duke Long, it also had no wild Immortal Gu, it was fighting with its own innate abilities.

Every time it waved its claws, it could create a gale. The Heavenly Court immortals avoided them, none of them wanting to try the feeling of being caught by Di Zang Sheng.

Each of its roars could set off shocking waves of sound, violently impacting everyone's eardrums and hearts.

Its size was too large, even if it suffered countless blows, it was not a big deal to its entire body.

It endured the furious attacks of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, it persevered towards the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation as it began to cause destruction.

Heavenly Court's immortals felt a sense of helplessness, against Di Zang Sheng, even if they used their full strength, they were like rats trying to topple an elephant.

"What do I do?"

"At this rate, the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation cannot sustain itself."

"Attacking the enemy will save it, we have to face offense with offense!"

Heavenly Court's immortals had rich experience, they quickly found a countermeasure.

Vortex Space Boy and Jun Shen Guang moved ahead while Zhu Que Er and Zhu Que Er became the middle group, they all moved towards the five regional limit formation.

At this moment, Di Zang Sheng opened its mouth, an Immortal Gu House flew out.

This Immortal Gu House was shining in orange-gold light, it was grand and overbearing, this was the rank eight Immortal Gu House — Dragon Palace.

A wave of smoke flew out of Dragon Palace like an illusory dream.

"Dream path killer move?!" Heavenly Court's immortals recognized it, they were shocked and fearful, quickly dodging.

Wherever dreamy light smoke went, Heavenly Court's immortals dodged and gave way.

The light smoke covered the five regional limit formation and quickly retrieved it.

Heavenly Court's immortals tried to use methods to attack dreamy light smoke but dream path killer moves were unstoppable in this era, all of their hard work ended up in vain.

The five regional limit formation was brought into Dragon Palace, Zhan Bu Du stored it away, after landing inside Dragon Palace, he met with Wu Shuai.

Wu Shuai used Dragon Palace's methods to immediately heal him.

Heavenly Court was a strong foe, even though they were in a disadvantage, they could still retaliate. Heavenly Court's main forces used the best tactic, forcing Zhan Bu Du to store the five regional limit formation.

This formation had already been attacked countless times, it was at its limits already.

Not only did Zhan Bu Du need healing, this five regional limit formation also needed to be repaired.

Without the formation, even though there was still five colored smoke in the battlefield, it lost its source and quickly dwindled.

Wu Shuai drove Dragon Palace directly into the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation with Di Zang Sheng, without tangling with Heavenly Court's members.

"Hold on! We need to hold on!" The Gu Immortals controlling the formation shouted, the atmosphere was tense and solemn.

In order to protect Hairy Foot Mountain and Infallible blessed land, they had to keep the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation up.

However, be it the five colored smoke or Di Zang Sheng, they were fatally dangerous to the formation.

After entering the formation, Di Zang Sheng's strength rose greatly.

It was restricted in the five colored smoke earlier, after all, it was a Central Continent legendary immemorial beast, it was not from the nine heavens.

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Wind!

While Heavenly Court's main forces retreated, Wu Yong found a chance and permanently expended wind path dao marks to unleash the unceasing tornado.

The tornado rampaged, suppressing the nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation from the outside, adding an additional problem to Heavenly Court.

Emperor City battlefield.

Myriad Statue Palace and Divine Bean Palace helped each other, firmly holding Western Desert's ground.

Thousand Transformations Ancestor charged into the battle alone, using all sorts of powerful transformation path killer moves to force back Yue Yang Palace and Frost Dragon Manor.

Like Zhang Fei Xiong and Flesh Whip Immortal, Thousand Transformations Ancestor also had the ability to fight Immortal Gu Houses with his body!

But the overall situation was, Central Continent still had the upper hand.

They were all affected by heroes among people, this human path killer move was indeed a venerable method, it could not be assessed with common sense.

Within Emperor City, the competition was also at a crucial stage.

Hong Yi stared at the fire with his full concentration. No matter how the immortals fought outside, they could not disturb him.

Ye Fan was the same, he wholeheartedly wanted to compete with Hong Yi. But different from Hong Yi, he was using a light path refinement method, aurora lights constantly moved vividly, reflecting off his face.

In the competition ground, one by one, Gu Masters failed, success dao marks were sent to Infallible blessed land by batches.

Next, the success dao marks in Infallible blessed land were extracted by Heavenly Court and sent to Yuan Qiong Du.

Yuan Qiong Du controlled the refinement path Gu formation, he continued to repair fate Gu, he was making quick progress.

Within this refinement path Gu formation, there were Cong Yan and Che Wei defending the place with their full strength.

As Northern Plains' Gu Immortals got near the formation, starlight would land on them, they would be teleported out without resistance.

"As expected of Lady Zi Wei."

"She is so dependable."

Che Wei and Cong Yan sighed.

"Persevere, persevere!" Fairy Zi Wei was covered in sweat now, her face was pale and her head was emitting steam from overheating.

She encouraged herself continuously: "The situation is still within my grasp, persistence will lead to victory!"

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan, who was on Myriad Year Flying Warship, laughed loudly.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Beings Assimilation Transformation.

Immortal killer move — Falling Star Rod Transformation!

He suddenly turned into a huge rod, black and thick.

Next, he used a star path killer move — Leading Countless Stars!

"Oh no!" Fairy Zi Wei's expression changed, she felt like she was sitting on a wild horse carriage that could not stop.

The horse pulling it was rampaging, even if she held the reins, she could not stop this horse carriage anymore.

Boom!

At the next moment, the entire transportation formation self-detonated, starlight specks faded away, no longer shining down.

Fairy Zi Wei suffered an immense backlash, she was at the point of near death, falling unconscious.

Chapter 1938: Heavenly Court's Crisis

The transportation formation's self-detonation shook all the surroundings as Heavenly Court's battlefield froze for a moment.

Next, Northern Plains' immortals erupted with cheers and caused a huge commotion.

"Zi Wei!" Qin Ding Ling turned pale with shock as she turned into a flash of light, saving Fairy Zi Wei from the rubble of the transportation formation.

Fairy Zi Wei had fainted, she was in poor shape, Qin Ding Ling needed to save her immediately.

Qin Ding Ling had no hesitation, she immediately retreated, no longer assisting Duke Long in battle. She knew her limits, she was not very useful for Duke Long, while Fairy Zi Wei was the strategist of Heavenly Court, she was vital and could not be lost.

Fang Yuan wanted to use this chance to kill Fairy Zi Wei of course, but Duke Long blocked his advancement each time.

Undeniably, Duke Long's modified qi wall was very strong, it got past the immobile weakness of the primordial qi wall, it was agile and durable. After Duke Long used this move, even Fang Yuan's Myriad Year Flying Warship could not break through it.

Within the qi wall, Duke Long had a grim expression, he treated Fang Yuan as the greatest enemy of his life, the disdain and contempt he showed earlier were completely gone.

Only until Fang Yuan destroyed the transportation formation did Duke Long realize: Fang Yuan's myriad self killer move earlier was just a distraction, it was intended to stall for time.

Fang Yuan's true method was waiting all along in the dark, once used, it caused a huge impact!

"Why does Fang Yuan have the method to break the formation so coincidentally?"

Duke Long knew that Fang Yuan was able to break the qi wall earlier because of his rebirth. But this transportation formation was definitely out of Fang Yuan's expectations, he was troubled by it earlier after all, if he had seen it in a previous life, he would have been prepared against it.

"This means that Fang Yuan deduced the method to break the killer move during battle? How can that be possible?" Duke Long was perplexed.

Heavenly Court made such an arrangement, they naturally guarded against Fang Yuan, they knew about his wisdom path attainment.

With Fang Yuan's foundation, he would need a lot of time to unravel this transportation formation.

Speaking of which, this was quite a coincidence.

When Fang Yuan explored the Dragon Whale Paradise, he had obtained the falling star rod tree from Shen Cong Sheng.

The growth conditions of this immemorial desolate plant were still a mystery as it had been extraordinarily rare and low in quantity since ancient times.

It had the unique trait of constantly attracting stars, falling into the trunk of the tree and turning into a single star mark. That was why it was called falling star.

According to rumors, one of the motives that Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had when he traveled the world alone was to collect this tree.

The value of the falling star rod tree did not just lie in itself.

By planting it in the immortal aperture, the Gu Immortal could use it to create an entire system of orbiting stars. It was a unique ecology that brought incremental gains every year, and the total amount of gains over time, day after day, year after year, was almost impossible to estimate.

Without this tree, even if Fang Yuan knew about the falling star rod tree, he could not transform into it. But after obtaining it, he observed and studied it, gaining the falling star rod tree transformation.

Other than the rod tree transformation, Fang Yuan also had Dong Fang Chang Fan's myriad star fireflies, and Ye Lui Qun Xing's leading countless stars killer move. These were all loot he gained in the past.

Leading countless stars was exceptional. It used the star fragments primarily and expended little immortal essence. Using the attractive force of star fragments, it could generate starlight magnetic force to continue manipulating stars. The more stars there were, the stronger this move would be.

Back then during the Northern Plains battle, Ye Lui Qun Xing used this move and was virtually unstoppable.

The killer move leading countless stars was targeted against stars and made use of them. On top of that foundation, Fang Yuan also had star path and formation path grandmaster attainment level, as well as the light of wisdom. By modifying the killer move in battle, he was able to achieve amazing results.

Duke Long was very shocked that he could destroy the transportation formation.

In Duke Long's eyes, Fang Yuan started to become unfathomable.

On Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan dispelled falling star rod tree transformation and returned to his human form.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self!

Bam bam bam...

A vast number of Fang Yuan's clones appeared again, filling the sky, they were like fireflies that spread out to the surroundings.

Heavenly Court felt a little troubled, in this battle, they were suffering from a lack of manpower.

Even though Star Constellation's will awakened many Heavenly Court rank eights earlier, because the transportation formation was destroyed, they were all stuck in Hairy Foot Mountain now.

"Troops far away cannot salvage the situation!" Duke Long sighed, he had no choice but to use a method.

Qi path immortal killer move — Qi Engulfing Mountains and Rivers!

At that instant, an unparalleled force descended from the sky, pressing down on the entire place.

The world became still, nothing was left unaffected.

Fang Yuan's clones were all destroyed, Calamity Luck Altar was forced to the ground, resisting stubbornly with creaking sounds. The Heavenly Court Immortal Gu Houses within the range of this killer move were even more badly affected, they were directly destroyed as the place turned into ruins.

Fang Yuan and Myriad Year Flying Warship were not spared either, they were enveloped by qi engulfing mountains and rivers, the warship's speed fell as it rapidly descended from the sky while bearing the weight of mountains and rivers.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, instead of shock, he felt joy.

Duke Long's qi engulfing mountains and rivers was quite familiar to him, in the previous life, when fighting for Dragon Palace, he had used it to claim victory.

But now, Duke Long had to use this move to destroy Fang Yuan's myriad self. He was truly in a passive spot, he had to give up Heavenly Court's own Immortal Gu Houses.

Immortal killer move — Immemorial Year Monkey Transformation!

Fang Yuan transformed again, all of his dao marks turned into one million and five hundred thousand time path dao marks.

Myriad Year Flying Warship itself was a time path Immortal Gu House, it was activated by Fang Yuan with full force now, its power rose drastically, it was re-energized and shot out like a flying sword, as if qi engulfing mountains and rivers did not exist!

Duke Long stared at Fang Yuan furiously, he could not catch up now, he watched as Fang Yuan charged towards the immortal graveyard.

Fang Yuan did not intend to target Heaven Overseeing Tower. Firstly, Heaven Overseeing Tower was defended by a formation now, time was needed to get in, secondly, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's painting path method was still around, Fang Yuan was wary against it.

The immortal graveyard was an important place of Heavenly Court, it was likely to have a venerable method, but Fang Yuan had to take the risk.

The immortal graveyard was a huge variable, destroying it now would greatly benefit Fang Yuan and the rest!

Within Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

Seeing that Fang Yuan approached the immortal graveyard, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette's expression changed as she grabbed a chess piece, preparing to toss it.

But at this moment, Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette smiled lightly as he placed a piece on the chessboard.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette stopped her action, if she tossed this chess piece, Limitless Demon Venerable would gain an absolute advantage, she would not be able to turn this game around anymore!

"Limitless, you really think highly of Fang Yuan." Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette sighed, she placed the chess piece back onto the board.

Next, her gaze turned sharp as blades, she said coldly: "But it is not so easy to stop me."

Before she finished her words, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable made several moves at once, placing pieces on the chessboard continuously.

Limitless Demon Venerable quickly followed after her, not giving her any advantage.

Both sides exchanged moves, they placed over a hundred pieces in a few breaths of time, the entire chessboard was filled with pieces but the strange thing was, this chessboard seemed to have no size limit, no matter how many they placed, the chessboard could hold them!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette was restrained by Limitless Demon Venerable, Fang Yuan managed to reach the immortal graveyard by moving straight ahead without obstacles.

"Fang Yuan! If you do anything to it, I will make sure you die without a proper corpse!!" Duke Long was still chasing him from behind.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, using strength path giant hand.

Slam, his giant hand was huge but extremely fast, it slammed down rapidly.

But the process of the giant hand's movement became very slow, space seemed the same but it was actually tens of thousands of li long now.

At the crucial moment, someone interfered, but it was not a venerable method.

"Who is it?!" Fang Yuan shouted, his eyes shined like lightning as he looked towards his left.

In Fang Yuan's vision, a female immortal slowly revealed her appearance.

She had a peculiar appearance, her entire body was made of wood, she wore a green dress made from vines, even though she had a human face, one could see the trunk rings on her tree bark skin, her eyes were clear as a tranquil lake.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, from her aura, this female immortal was close to Di Zang Sheng's level!

"Human immortal, stop. Don't try to destroy Heavenly Court, otherwise, I, Cang Xuan Zi, will have to stop you." The female immortal spoke, her voice was gentle but contained immense determination.

"Cang Xuan Zi?" Fang Yuan realized after a moment.

Heavenly Court had three legendary immemorial beasts, they were Shabi Ninety-five, Ruan Dan, and Cang Xuan Zi.

Cang Xuan Zi was a vast heaven vine, it was a unique existence in Heavenly Court, it did not need to follow orders, but only had to provide a batch of vast heaven fruits every thousand years.

In the previous life, when Longevity Heaven attacked Heavenly Court, Cang Xuan Zi watched the battle without doing anything. But to think that she would take action in this life when Fang Yuan invaded!

"It seems that Cang Xuan Zi and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had some sort of special agreement, nobody else knows about it!" Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he mobilized Myriad Year Flying Warship to charge towards the immortal graveyard.

Cang Xuan Zi sighed, she turned into a green light and blocked Myriad Year Flying Warship.

With a loud sound, Myriad Year Flying Warship crashed into Cang Xuan Zi's body, its momentum was halted while Cang Xuan Zi was sent flying away.

She spat out a mouthful of green blood, but she continued to attack Myriad Year Flying Warship.

"Fang Yuan, your life is mine!" At this moment, Duke Long arrived, he opened his mouth and bore his fangs, turning into blades that slashed at Fang Yuan.

Instantly, Fang Yuan became trapped from the front and back.

He was not flustered, he first pointed at Duke Long to use spring scissors, before pointing at Cang Xuan Zi as the Myriad Year Flying Warship below him shot out countless flying swords, they were all daybreak flying swords!

Spring scissors flew out and snipped the dragon fangs, before approaching Duke Long with an unstoppable force.

Duke Long had to retreat.

Daybreak flying swords shot out like a waterfall towards Cang Xuan Zi, after enduring it for a few moments, Cang Xuan Zi could not hold on anymore and retreated.

Fang Yuan yelled, Myriad Year Flying Warship soared into the sky again, before rapidly descending towards the immortal graveyard.

But distance was extended once again, an unobservable profundity was occurring around the surrounding space!

Fang Yuan turned around and stared at Cang Xuan Zi, saying a sentence fiercely: "You are courting death."

Cang Xuan Zi was covered in sweat, she had tried her best to use the space path killer move, but she could only stall Fang Yuan temporarily.

Thankfully, Duke Long was around, he attacked Fang Yuan once more but was forced to retreat yet again.

Fang Yuan's strength suppressed both Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi.

The two sides fought for over a hundred rounds, the more they fought, the stronger Fang Yuan's aura and the more injuries gathered on the bodies of Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi.

Rumble!

With a loud sound, Fang Yuan's Luo Po seal landed on Cang Xuan Zi as she screamed, his giant hand slammed Duke Long to the ground.

"Duke Long, you are already old! With this aged body of yours, how long can you last?" Fang Yuan smiled coldly.

"Until I die." Duke Long was filled with determination and battle intent, one of his dragon horns was broken, his dragon scales were cracked, he was covered in blood.

But he would rather fight to the death!

Within the refinement path formation, Northern Plains' past generation experts surrounded Cong Yan and Che Wei.

"Kill, kill them both!"

"They are already at their limit."

"How can merely two people stop us? Hmph, they are overestimating themselves!"

Northern Plains' immortals were ready to attack, killing intent surged and filled the entire space.

Che Wei and Cong Yan were covered in blood, as long as they stood at the same spot for a few seconds, a pool of blood would gather below them.

"It seems that we are going to die here."

"Hehehe, then we will die. Even if we die, we will use our lives to get as much time as we can for Yuan Qiong Du."

The two looked at each other, they smiled with the determination to die.

"Come, this is our final battle!" As the weaker side, they shouted even louder than the Northern Plains immortals.

The Northern Plains immortals' expressions changed.

"These are two respectable opponents."

"I will use my strongest killer move to send you off, this is my respect towards you both!"

Boom boom boom!

Intense battle erupted once again.

Emperor City.

Countless gazes were heatedly locked onto the final competition grounds.

Most of the Gu Masters had failed, they all left the stage.

There were only two people left, one was Ye Fan, the other was Hong Yi. The final victor would be either one of these two!

"The competition is ending, our mission to defend is about to succeed!"

"Persevere, everyone!!"

Central Continent's troops cheered in advance.

"What do we do?" Thousand Transformations Ancestor could not take them down, he started to feel anxious.

Fang Di Chang was silent but he snorted coldly in his heart: "You are all too naive, so what if we are blocked? Hahaha, it has finally arrived!"

At this precise moment, the ground cracked open, the earth shook as a huge Earth Trench appeared, the terrifying crack expanded towards Emperor City!

"What is happening?"

"An Earth Trench! Damn it, Emperor City is in the path of the Earth Trench."

"Quick, save the people!!"

Central Continent's troops were flustered, they wanted to salvage the situation. But Fang Di Chang was prepared from the start, he manipulated Divine Bean Palace and charged out to block the Central Continent troops.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals had no choice but to block Divine Bean Palace in a panic, they did not have the strength to save the mortals in Emperor City.

"We are doomed!"

"Who can save us?"

"No, we cannot give up hope!"

Emperor City was in complete chaos.

River of Time.

The river water moved in waves, Feng Jiu Ge stood in a time path Immortal Gu House as he pondered with his eyes closed, he was quietly comprehending.

Suddenly, his eyes opened, his expression was of utter shock.

A stone lotus island slowly appeared in Feng Jiu Ge's vision.

"This is..." At this instance, Feng Jiu Ge thought of the words Qin Ding Ling said before he left —

"I observed your luck for you, it shows that your fortuitous encounter is in the River of Time. Go, your fortune is there, it will lead you to great accomplishments! You originally wanted to go to the River of Time and increase your comprehension to complete destiny song, this is a wise decision, it cannot go wrong."

"Don't tell me, this is my fortuitous encounter?" Feng Jiu Ge restrained the shock in his mind as he entered the stone lotus island.

Chapter 1939: Blood-Kin Heart Revenge

Heavenly Court battlefield.

"You finally woke up!" Qin Ding Ling looked at Fairy Zi Wei who was slowly opening her eyes, she let out a breath of air.

"I..." Fairy Zi Wei was a little dazed but she soon regained her senses: "How is the battle situation now?"

"The situation is not good!" Qin Ding Ling said grimly, she spread her palms as a golden silhouette appeared.

Within the silhouette, one could see the scene of Fang Yuan suppressing Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi.

Immortal killer move — Purple-Gold Dragon-Shaped Qi!

After using this killer move, be it offense, defense, healing, or movement, all of Duke Long's actions would have accompanying purple-gold dragon-shaped qi.

This was his main method in qi path, it was very comprehensive.

In the previous life, Five Elements Grandmaster died from this move by Duke Long.

But even in this state, Duke Long was repelled by Fang Yuan continuously.

Duke Long was still very strong, but Fang Yuan relied on Myriad Year Flying Warship, displaying unprecedented time path battle strength!

Spring scissors and summer fan had incredible power, even Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi could not block these attacks.

Fairy Zi Wei took a few glances and exclaimed: "Fang Yuan's battle strength is so terrifying! He seems to have a transformation path method to turn all of his dao marks into the same path. Not only did he advance to rank eight, his dao marks are at an absurd number. How did he do it?"

"Rather than thinking about this, you should think about how we can resolve this crisis now!" Qin Ding Ling urged.

Fairy Zi Wei was silent for a while before analyzing as she pointed at the silhouette: "Lord Duke Long's strength is not inferior to Fang Yuan, it is just that he is too passive now as a result of protecting the immortal graveyard. This gives Fang Yuan the initiative, Lord Duke Long has to endure every offensive killer move he uses to make sure the immortal graveyard is intact."

Fang Yuan could casually dodge Duke Long's attacks but Duke Long had to block Fang Yuan's attacks. This was too great of an advantage.

If one analyzed this, they would see that Duke Long and Fang Yuan were quite similar in power level. But Fang Yuan's tactic was too wise, Duke Long would not be overly concerned if he attacked Heaven Overseeing Tower with high defense, but the immortal graveyard was different.

The primordial qi wall was destroyed by Fang Yuan, that was truly a huge move, it was crucial. It caused Duke Long to be taxed with defending against Fang Yuan's attacks now.

Star Constellation's will could have awakened more Gu Immortals from the immortal graveyard, but Limitless Demon Venerable was stopping her at the moment.

How could they resolve this issue?

Fairy Zi Wei started to think about this deeply but she felt a strong headache, the intense pain made her body shake as she almost fainted again.

"Be careful, your injuries are still quite severe!" Qin Ding Ling called out in concern.

Fairy Zi Wei nodded, frowning and enduring the headache, she spoke with difficulty: "The immortal graveyard is the biggest foundation and accumulation of Heavenly Court, we cannot lose it! We need to get rid of the problem which is Fang Yuan now, go and reinforce Senior Duke Long, get Gu Yue Fang Zheng to fight as well. He has been cultivating in the Demon Judgment Board recently, he progressed quite a bit. If you enter the Demon Judgment Board and coordinate with him, there will be good results."

"What about you?" Qin Ding Ling looked at Fairy Zi Wei with worry.

Fairy Zi Wei spat out a mouthful of blood: "I need to heal my injuries. Thankfully, there is a healing hall that can help me greatly. Don't worry, this Immortal Gu House is at the periphery of the battlefield, it will not attract attention."

"Okay, be careful!" Qin Ding Ling hesitated for a moment before gritting her teeth and flying away.

Fairy Zi Wei felt her vision turning dark, after taking several huge breaths for a while, she stabilized her injuries and decided to move towards the healing hall.

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Whoosh! Intense winds blew, sweeping everything in their path, rampaging through heaven and earth.

Duke Long grunted as he flew back by three hundred steps, countless purple-gold scale fragments were scattered along the way.

The storm also engulfed Cang Xuan Zi, the female immortal cried out in pain as her vines snapped, she used her defensive killer moves with much difficulty to resist the attack.

Her space path defensive killer move was quite amazing. Any move that landed on her would have to travel through a huge distance to reach her.

But no matter how long the distance was, the time path tornado still went into the immortal graveyard. Even though it only suffered a minor loss, still far from total destruction, Heavenly Court's immortals still felt deeply pained when they saw that.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, looking at Cang Xuan Zi coldly.

He was not happy with the current situation.

Cang Xuan Zi... he did not expect her to participate, Fang Yuan knew nothing about her. Especially when she cultivated space path, Fang Yuan's attainment level in this path was too low.

Without enough space path attainment level, even though Fang Yuan had wisdom path attainment level, he could not deduce anything useful.

"The bigger threat between them is Duke Long." Standing on Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan looked at Duke Long again.

Not long ago, when Fang Yuan used summer fan, Duke Long flew back by five hundred steps, but now, it was only three hundred steps.

Summer fan was an old killer move, even though Fang Yuan modified it, it had already been used before. At this point, Duke Long was getting used to dealing with it.

Of course, the bigger reason was that Duke Long was continuously getting stronger!

"Heavenly dragon's last stand..." Fang Yuan muttered, he could feel what the Northern Plains immortals felt in the previous life when they fought Duke Long.

Duke Long was strong to begin with, and more terrifyingly, he was continuously getting stronger.

Fang Yuan knew that even though he had the upper hand now, it was because of his wise tactic of targeting the enemy's weakness! Duke Long was forced to defend it.

In terms of real battle, if he fought Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi, they would be evenly matched.

Fang Yuan had Myriad Year Flying Warship, he coordinated well with it. This was the first time Duke Long was fighting with Cang Xuan Zi, and even though Cang Xuan Zi had deep foundation on par with Di Zang Sheng, she was unfamiliar with fighting techniques, it showed that under normal times she faced combat rarely.

Thus, Fang Yuan could also sense that she was getting more proficient in her methods as the fight went on.

After all, a battle of life and death was the greatest form of training.

"Time is pressing, if I cannot succeed soon, I will need to give up on this target." Fang Yuan took a look at Heaven Overseeing Tower, once Genesis Lotus' method was activated, he would attack that place.

Before that, he should destroy the immortal graveyard first. After all, nobody knew which monster would emerge from it next! After all, including Duke Long, Heavenly Court should have a total of four Dao Guardians.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light, countless thoughts moved in his mind at rapid speed, countless battle tactics were being created.

At this point in time, he still had many trump card killer moves left. There was time cutting edge, unlimited qi sea, five finger fist heart sword, lead soul into dream, and other killer moves.

If he faced other enemies, these methods would decide the battle and kill them. But Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi were not simple characters, against them, if his move failed, they would be prepared against the attack, Fang Yuan would not be able to use them effectively anymore.

Kill Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi? It was not impossible for Fang Yuan!

But at the same time, Duke Long still had the killer move triple qi retraction, it was very threatening. If Fang Yuan got hit by it, the consequences would be severe. Fang Yuan was similarly wary of it.

Furthermore, other than triple qi retraction, did Duke Long have other methods of similar strength?

Fang Yuan was not sure.

At the same time, Cang Xuan Zi was quite an unknown factor, she had lived much longer than Duke Long and also had a complex relationship with Genesis Lotus, who knew what methods she could bring out, it would not be surprising.

Fang Yuan continued to attack, he aimed attacks at the immortal graveyard while looking for an opportunity.

Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi were experienced monsters, their battle experience was incredibly vast.

Fang Yuan tried for a long time but he could not create any opportunities.

Amidst the intense battle, a cloud of blood suddenly appeared.

The cloud of blood approached Fang Yuan, it had a peculiar aura.

Fang Yuan stepped softly as Myriad Year Flying Warship shook, a group of daybreak flying swords flew out and attacked the cloud.

The blood cloud was pierced by Fang Yuan, it was easily torn to shreds and vanished, but Fang Yuan's expression changed.

At the next moment, Cooking Luck Pot appeared above him, blood markings appeared and stuck themselves onto Cooking Luck Pot, attempting to corrode Fang Yuan's luck.

"Blood path killer move?" Fang Yuan's heart shook, his attacks slowed down as he split his attention to mobilize Cooking Luck Pot.

But no matter how he tried to cook his luck, he could not get rid of the blood markings. To get rid of them, Fang Yuan would need to concentrate fully, it would expend a lot of his time.

Fang Yuan cast his gaze far away as an Immortal Gu House approached him.

This was a red tombstone with countless words moving on it, it was the rank eight Immortal Gu House — Demon Judgment Board!

"Fang Zheng... is that you?" Although lacking a clear reason, Fang Yuan guessed the identity of the person inside the Demon Judgment Board.

Within Demon Judgment Board, there was Gu Yue Fang Zheng and also Qin Ding Ling.

"Fang Yuan was hit!" Fang Zheng was surprised and joyful: "Thank you for amplifying the power of my killer move."

At this moment, behind Fang Zheng, Qin Ding Ling was placing both palms on his back as she helped him with her full strength.

Seeing that this move had effect, Qin Ding Ling was surprised too, she looked at Gu Yue Fang Zheng in a new light.

Fang Zheng only had rank seven cultivation level but like what Fairy Zi Wei predicted, the killer moves he created were very effective on Fang Yuan.

"Worthy of Fang Yuan's nemesis, the pawn left behind specially by heaven's will." Qin Ding Ling sighed to herself.

Heaven's will attempted to destroy Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's plan, using Fang Yuan as the pawn. But Fang Yuan as an otherworldly demon was the greatest variable himself, thus heaven's will arranged for Fang Zheng as well, to become the counter to Fang Yuan.

Thus, after Fang Zheng became the Demon Judgment Board Lord, he used the experience of the previous generations of Board Lords to create his own killer move, blood-kin heart revenge.

This blood path mimicked luck path, it also contained the profundity of human path. Qin Ding Ling's amplification was only icing on the cake.

Blood-kin heart revenge activated again!

The blood cloud approached while Fang Yuan dodged it.

But the blood cloud followed him closely, it did not stop chasing after him.

"I've already used sovereign immortal fetus Gu, this body has no bloodline relationship with him, why is the blood cloud still approaching me?" At once, Fang Yuan's gaze flickered with uncertainty.

Chapter 1940: Limitless, Please Turn Around

Fang Yuan's current main body was made from sovereign immortal fetus Gu.

Sovereign immortal fetus Gu was a consumable Gu worm, it could turn any life form into a pure bred human. Because the body was not created by normal birth, it had the trait of being half an otherworldly demon.

The sovereign immortal body had no blood relationship with Gu Yue Fang Zheng, he was only related to Fang Yuan's rank six time path clone.

But his clone was currently hidden in the sovereign immortal aperture, isolated from the world. Could Fang Zheng's method pierce through that boundary and sense the clone in his immortal aperture?

"Most likely, this move does not use our bloodline relationship but the mental connection with the user." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he felt that this deduction was more logical.

He had very little understanding of Fang Zheng's killer move as he had just seen it.

Fang Yuan tried for a while and could not get away from the blood cloud. If he destroyed the cloud, blood markings would appear and attack his luck.

If others used this killer move, there would not be this effect.

But Fang Zheng was closely connected to Fang Yuan, not just in terms of bloodline. He was an arrangement of heaven's will, both of their lucks were connected in some way. For example, after Fang Yuan obtained Cooking Luck Pot, Fang Zheng's luck turned into a pot lid, it showed that he was a counter to Fang Yuan.

The connection of blood-kin heart revenge was much more complex than Fang Yuan thought.

The first aspect was bloodline connection, the second was the mental connection, and the third was their luck's connection.

Using the resonance of their luck, the blood markings were able to corrode Fang Yuan's luck.

This was a huge problem for Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan changed his target now, trying to destroy Demon Judgment Board and kill Fang Zheng directly. But whenever he made this choice, Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi would interfere, they would thwart his plan each time at the perfect timing.

Even if Fang Yuan's attacks landed, it would only cause Demon Judgment Board to shake and crack. Afterwards, the Gu Immortals inside would repair it fully.

Demon Judgment Board was different from most of Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses, it was comprehensive in defense, movement, recovery, and others, it had no clear weaknesses.

"If I had the all living beings luck inheritance, no, as long as I had heart blood Immortal Gu… even if I cannot unravel this move, it will alleviate my situation." Fang Yuan had a sensation back then, it was a pity that he could not obtain heart blood Immortal Gu during the qi sea banquet, that was truly a huge pity, to think that it would take effect here.

In the previous life, Fang Yuan lost the five regional limit formation, it was a huge pity. In this life, it was heart blood Immortal Gu.

Even though Fang Yuan had Spring Autumn Cicada and had the advantage of rebirth, when he changed things, the influence would spread out, his enemies and the entire world would generate new changes that would target him once again.

It was like someone shouting at a valley, no matter how he adjusted his voice or tone, the echo would also come back to find him.

At the qi sea banquet, Fang Yuan already felt something. But it was a pity that all sorts of undercurrents and circumstances forced Fang Yuan to let go of this opportunity.

From this aspect, one could see Spring Autumn Cicada's weakness.

The rebirth provided by Spring Autumn Cicada was merely a second chance. Afterwards, especially later into the future, the situation would still depend on the user's own actions.

If one kept relying on the advantage of rebirth, they might gain a lot during the initial stage, but they would be like overconfident swimmers in the sea, eventually drowning themselves.

Thus, even after being reborn for countless times, Red Lotus Demon Venerable only managed to damage fate Gu.

This way, with Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi as the main force, with Fang Zheng and Qin Ding Ling as the supplementary force using Demon Judgment Board, they attacked Fang Yuan together, finally resisting this demon's great might.

"Fang Yuan is trapped!" Within Calamity Luck Altar, Bull Demon spoke, he had kept a lot of attention on Fang Yuan.

Of course, he was not the only one, all of the other Gu Immortals did too, after all, Fang Yuan's victory or defeat would influence this entire battle.

Flower Lady hesitated: "Should we help him?"

The two look at Bing Sai Chuan. They knew that he was still concealing a trump card, they could ask Limitless to turn around.

In the previous life, Bing Sai Chuan used this trump card to temporarily trap Duke Long.

Furthermore, in this situation, as long as Duke Long was trapped, Fang Yuan would not have any restraints, he could break the stalemate.

But Bing Sai Chuan shook his head, his gaze was heated: "Let them fight, this is our best chance, let us take fate Gu and return to Longevity Heaven, we will refine rank nine destiny Gu!"

His original goal was this, with rank nine destiny Gu, Longevity Heaven would replace Heavenly Court's position, they would rule the five regions.

Earlier, Bing Sai Chuan was trapped in a predicament, he had to give up on this thought and ask Fang Yuan for help. Now that Fang Yuan has taken action and changed the situation, Bing Sai Chuan's situation turned for the better.

Be grateful to Fang Yuan and help him?

Bing Sai Chuan laughed coldly in his heart. Their grand ambitions were about to be fulfilled, after years of waiting and expectation', Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's goal of domination was close! How could he give up?!

As long as there was hope, he had to try, he could not give up!

At this moment, even though the refinement path formation was not destroyed, a path was already opened.

"Go! For Longevity Heaven, for Northern Plains, for Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, go and retrieve Fate!" Bing Sai Chuan screamed in a loud voice.

The phantom images in the River of Time stirred, the historical experts of Northern Plains roared and echoed Bing Sai Chuan's words.

Mao Li Qiu had entered battle long ago, using the killer move perfect pair to fight Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan.

Bull Demon and Flower Lady also flew out of Calamity Luck Altar, engaging in their attack. Many Northern Plains Gu Immortals were with them, they had a much larger force than in the previous life.

"No!" Yuan Qiong Du's eyes were red, he shouted for reinforcements but nobody came to help.

Yuan Qiong Du was inside the refinement path formation, he could not leave. At this moment, he was in grave danger himself.

Rank nine Fate was about to be repaired but if it was snatched away, their efforts would have been in vain.

Seeing this situation, Duke Long became anxious, he called out: "Fang Yuan, to think that they are also making use of you."

Fang Yuan casted his gaze at Heaven Overseeing Tower, with just this action, Bing Sai Chuan held his breath.

If Fang Yuan turned around now and attacked Longevity Heaven, what would they do?

Bing Sai Chuan had made this decision after shouldering huge pressure.

The truth was, Fang Yuan had been paying attention to Heaven Overseeing Tower's situation. When he saw that Northern Plains' Gu Immortals were going to Heaven Overseeing Tower, he became happy: Somebody was finally going to step on the land mine for him.

"Duke Long, you should be more concerned with yourself. I will kill you first before dealing with Longevity Heaven!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Duke Long was silent, his attacks went beyond his original limit yet again, becoming even stronger.

"Fate Gu!" Bull Demon and Flower Lady shouted, they charged up to the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, seeing fate Gu.

But at the next moment, Genesis Lotus' method activated.

"Ahhh!"

"What is this?!"

"Painting path, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's method!"

Like what Fang Yuan had expected, these Northern Plains Gu Immortals were all stuck inside the bamboo forest painting now.

This change was so unexpected that all the other immortals were stunned. Within Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan was dumbstruck.

Yuan Qiong Du, Cong Yan, and Che Wei gained some time to recover, they quickly rested.

Bing Sai Chuan gritted his teeth, phantoms moved in the River of Time but no Gu Immortals appeared, Mao Li Qiu was the closest to it but it was fighting against two legendary immemorial beasts, it could not leave.

In this situation, only Bing Sai Chuan could go himself.

At this moment, Qi Ci Lang woke up slowly.

"What are you hesitating for? Use Calamity Luck Altar to crash into Heaven Overseeing Tower!" Qi Ci Lang said.

When he was unconsciously, he still collected information about the outside world, once he woke up, he received the information.

Fate Gu was inside Heaven Overseeing Tower, it was the core component.

Fate Gu could only be destroyed by otherworldly demons, if Heaven Overseeing Tower was destroyed, the other core Immortal Gu might be destroyed but fate Gu would be intact.

But Heaven Overseeing Tower was a genuine rank nine Immortal Gu House, it had great defense. If Heaven Overseeing Tower attacked it, they would lose precious time. This was why Bing Sai Chuan sent Gu Immortals to invade Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Bing Sai Chuan could not decide.

He looked at the phantom River of Time again, some time had passed but no Gu Immortals came out. There were still many experts in Northern Plains' history, like those forming Seven Extreme Desolation, they did not show up despite Bing Sai Chuan's expectations.

Bing Sai Chuan's expression was uncertain, even though he did not know the previous life's situation, he sensed something amiss!

He was a time path great expert after all.

Being appointed by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as the West Desolation Immortal, having slumbered for three hundred thousand years due to Giant Sun's request, he was the crucial leader that was designated to achieve Longevity Heaven's grand ambitions!

"This call of the ancient killer move is quite fishy, I cannot rely on it solely. Red Lotus Demon Venerable was once a righteous path member after all, nobody knows what his true objectives are."

Thinking of this, Bing Sai Chuan said to Qi Ci Lang: "Seventh Prince, please take action."

Qi Ci Lang spat out: "Are you a luck path cultivator? I am! I am more suited than you to control Calamity Luck Altar. How much of this Immortal Gu House's power can you use? The urgent matter at hand is to… Bing Sai Chuan, fuck your ancestor!"

Qi Ci Lang had just said his words when suddenly, Bing Sai Chuan teleported him out, he could not help but curse.

Calamity Luck Altar's control was in Bing Sai Chuan's hands. Qi Ci Lang was able to control it earlier because Bing Sai Chuan gave him a portion of the authority.

"Seventh Prince, please attack quickly." Bing Sai Chuan spoke politely but Calamity Luck Altar was ready to attack.

Qi Ci Lang suspected that if he refused to act, Calamity Luck Altar would attack him first.

"Bing Sai Chuan, very good!" Qi Ci Lang gritted his teeth in deep anger.

Bing Sai Chuan was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's old general, his status and seniority gave him the assurance to deal with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's own son like this.

"Just you wait. If not for father's ambitions…" Qi Ci Lang was furious and helpless, he charged into Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Yuan Qiong Du and the rest were helpless to stop him.

Since when could enemies enter and leave Heaven Overseeing Tower at will?

Yuan Qiong Du and the other two felt sadness in their hearts, they could only bank on Genesis Lotus' arrangements activating again.

Qi Ci Lang carefully stepped onto the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, he was immediately attacked by a jade light.

He received a shock, looking at Genesis Lotus' painting on the walls, he tried his best to maintain his position but he could not resist it.

Right as he was about to be dragged into the painting, Bing Sai Chuan shouted: "Limitless, please turn around!"

In Imperfection Regret Pavilion, similar to the previous life, Limitless Demon Venerable did not turn around, he only tossed out one chess piece.

The chess piece flew into Heaven Overseeing Tower and floated above Qi Ci Lang's head.

Qi Ci Lang's body immediately regained freedom as the jade light got blocked by this small chess piece, only a faint amount of jade light remained around him.

Qi Ci Lang was overjoyed, as long as he got rid of the jade light, he would be able to move freely and snatch fate Gu!

Chapter 1941: Contented Lifestyle

Emperor City battlefield.

Rumble, dust clouds spread.

The earth cracked open, a large trench spread out and extended forward, swallowing everything in its path, approaching Emperor City.

Emperor City's destruction was about to occur!

At this moment, there were still several Central Continent Gu Immortals guarding Emperor City, but to save the lives of everyone in such a short time, none of the Gu Immortals could do it.

Earth Trenches were formed naturally, nobody could predict where the next Earth Trench would appear. But only Fang Yuan knew.

Because this Earth Trench appeared in his previous life and destroyed Emperor City.

Both Central Continent's and Western Desert's forces were caught off guard, the Earth Trench was truly a huge shock to them!

But Western Desert was shocked and happy while Central Continent was shocked and fearful.

Right when Emperor City was about to be destroyed, an Immortal Gu House emerged and turned into jade light as it flew into the sky rapidly.

It was Divine Bean Palace!

"Stop him!" Central Continent's Gu Immortals subconsciously shouted.

"What is Fang Di Chang doing?" Thousand Transformations Ancestor and the rest were quite surprised, Divine Bean Palace's action was not what they had planned.

Fang Di Chang was shocked at the moment, not only could he not connect to the outside world, his entire body was immobilized.

Divine Bean Palace shook intensely, a formless force was restraining him completely.

On the painting that surrounded the walls, a lump of will emerged.

The will quickly gathered into human form, he had the appearance of a young man with a gentlemanly air, wearing green clothes and a white headband, his long hair extended to his shoulders.

Seeing this will, Fang Di Chang's expression turned ashen, he shouted: "Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable!"

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable... the venerable with the most abundant immortal essence in history, the third generation Immortal King of Heavenly Court, the creator of Heavenly Lotus Sect, he was the one who cleansed the demonic trend, he restored order to the world.

Indeed, this was Genesis Lotus' will!

"Damn it, he was hiding in the painting so I could not discover him?" Fang Di Chang understood at once, he had no understanding of painting path after all.

"But why did I lose control of Divine Bean Palace the moment Genesis Lotus' will appeared, I am restrained here without any freedom left?" Instantly, Fang Di Chang thought of Qing Chou.

His heart turned cold, he had once thought he completely refined Divine Bean Palace but the cruel truth was exposed here, Divine Bean Palace still continued secrets, its owner was still Genesis Lotus' will all along.

This method was a secret to both the real Fang Di Chang and Fang Yuan's clone, they were unaware of it.

How could a venerable's Immortal Gu House be taken so easily?

Boom, Divine Bean Palace landed on the ground, right in the center of Emperor City as if it was overseeing the situation.

An endless amount of green light spread out from Divine Bean Palace, the light was as warm as water, it was not glaring at all, radiating half the sky.

The whole of Emperor City was covered in green light. Within the light, paintings in all the corners of Emperor City started to surface and show themselves.

These were all paintings of the lives of people, they portrayed the scene of Emperor City at certain points in time.

There were marketplaces, crowded with people, vendors vied for attention while selling a wide variety of goods.

There were the silhouettes of courtyards of several houses, and on the tall trees in the courtyard, a few birds' nests had young chicks waiting to fly. Under the trees, there was a group of children playing and chasing each other, full of hope for the future.

There was a group going towards the bride's house, they traveled from the north with the groom riding on a large horse, behind him was a mortal Gu House carriage[1]. This kind of mortal Gu House was usually only used during marriage ceremonies in Central Continent, and the surface of the carriage was decorated with colorful blooming flowers. Behind the carriage was a group of servants carrying the bride's generous dowry.

There was a teahouse, the street in front of the entrance was crowded with pedestrians, and the upper level of the teahouse was filled with guests who were eating breakfast while looking through the windows, watching the street. The banners of the teahouse, used to attract customers, fluttered along with the slight morning breeze.

There was also a painting depicting dusk. At the corner of the street near the city gate, there was a stall where a blind old Gu Master, who perhaps owned a wisdom path Gu worm, was acting as a fortune teller, predicting the future prospects of a female customer.

...

Be it dusk or dawn, the city gates or the vibrant markets, the contented lifestyles of the people in Emperor City could be clearly seen in these respective paintings.

Undeniably, this was a painting path method filled with the profundities of human path.

Immortal killer move — Contented Lifestyle!

"Emperor City actually has such a hidden method from Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable?"

"Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had once lived in Emperor City as a mortal for some time... Don't tell me that these rumors were actually true?"

"Painting path is truly profound!"

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were joyful.

Western Desert's side felt that the situation was turning bad.

Divine Bean Palace was connected with Emperor City and formed a gigantic Immortal Gu House. The central area was Divine Bean Palace, while the periphery was the former Emperor City.

As the Earth Trench approached, the monstrous mouth opened, attempting to engulf Emperor City.

But Emperor City had transformed already, it floated in the sky without moving at all.

The countless people in the city cheered loudly.

They jumped in joy as they cheered and shouted, they had escaped a certain death situation!

A group of people were sobbing with joy, they knelt down on the ground and started to kowtow to the paintings.

Suddenly, many new paintings appeared all over the place, the content of the paintings were the scenes of these kowtowing people.

This killer move, contented lifestyle, was able to draw power from mortals to strengthen itself.

As the power of the paintings accumulated unceasingly, it was transmitted into Divine Bean Palace.

Genesis Lotus' will controlled this power, he had a form grasp of Divine Bean Palace, he looked towards Fang Di Chang with a seemingly smiling face: "Fang Yuan, I have to thank you for bringing Divine Bean Palace here, you prevented a catastrophe for the mortals."

This was Genesis Lotus's arrangement when he was alive! In the previous life, Divine Bean Palace was not brought here by Fang clan, thus Emperor City was destroyed. In this life, using Fang Yuan's clone as the tool, Divine Bean Palace appeared to save the mortals.

As his feeling of danger increased, Fang Di Chang struggled intensely.

But a profound power restrained him and directly sent him into the painting of Divine Bean Palace.

Fang Di Chang's vision changed, when he took a second look, he was already inside the painting.

The scene was quite familiar to him, he saw a grey-white land with deep pits in it, he had planted the immortal beans here back then.

Right now, most of the beans were used up in the fight, there were only some sprouts left here, slowly growing.

Fang Di Chang found that he could move again but it was useless, no matter how he tried, he could not escape from this painting.

"I am sealed within the painting!" Fang Di Chang thought about Flower Lady in his previous life, she had been suppressed in the painting that was in Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Fang Di Chang tried to connect to his main body but he found that he could not communicate with the outside world. He could not even sense treasure yellow heaven, all of his communicative methods were ineffective.

"Calm down, calm down, I still have my final hope!" Fang Di Chang pondered for a moment before activating the killer move karma divine tree.

Thankfully, this move had been modified already, once he activated it, Genesis Lotus' will, which was outside the painting, had a change of expression.

This method was truly the only way to resist, even Genesis Lotus' will could not stop him.

At this time, in Emperor City, the final competition of the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was undergoing.

This great competition was finally at its last moment, the victor was about to be decided.

"I succeeded."

"Success!"

Hong Yi and Ye Fan spoke at the same time, they refined the Gu refinement at the same time.

To decide the victor, a time path Gu Master would need to inspect the specific timing of their completion.

But at this moment, jade light shined, the two were enveloped by it, dragged by it and flying far away.

This jade light was extremely fast, it brought Hong Yi and Ye Fan into Divine Bean Palace almost instantly.

Genesis Lotus' will in Divine Bean Palace gritted his teeth, seeing this, the two people brought by the jade light were extremely close to Fang Yuan, they were either his pawns or his capable subordinates!

Genesis Lotus' will quickly activated Divine Bean Palace, the light that carried Ye Fan and Hong Yi took a twist as it landed in a painting of Emperor City, both of them were sealed as well.

"What is going on?"

"Who won?"

Hong Yi and Ye Fan looked at each other with a dumbfounded expression, they were currently inside a painting created by the killer move contented lifestyle, all they saw was a peaceful and serene environment in front of them.

This made them feel extremely confused.

"Where in the world are we?"

"Aren't there Gu Immortals fighting outside Emperor City? Why can't we hear anything?"

"Am I dreaming?"

Hong Yi gave himself a hard pinch, he gritted his teeth as he felt a sharp pain!

[1] We call it a Chinese Sedan, otherwise known as Litter(Vehicle), google for image. Back

Chapter 1942: Destiny Song

Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield.

Only a small portion of the five colored smoke remained, Di Zang Sheng roared as it used its mighty strength to tear the formation. Its mountain range-sized body was still charging forward.

"Stop it!"

"Another sub-formation has been broken!"

"How many sub-formations do we still have?"

"Only one is left!"

"Quickly construct the sub-formations!"

"We can't, its destructive force is too great, we won't make it in time!"

The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was in chaos. Many Central Continent Gu Immortals were stationed here but got restricted by the five colored smoke, be it controlling the formation or constructing sub-formations, they had to face backlashes. The more powerful the person and the more strength they used, the stronger the backlash would be.

Di Zang Sheng was extremely powerful, it could break the sub-formations so quickly with just its physical strength!

And it was constantly becoming stronger.

The five regions' regional walls grew increasingly fragile, the earth veins of the five regions were gradually merging into one, the Earth Trench that spread to Emperor City was huge evidence. Earth Trenches had already spread to the central region of Central Continent, this meant that the merging of earth veins had reached the highest point.

Be it the other four regions or Central Continent, the rapid spread of new Earth Trenches led to countless tragedies and deaths, human emotions were surging.

Di Zang Sheng was different from other legendary immemorial beasts, it was born from the power of earth veins fused with the negative emotions of humans.

Right now, Central Continent's earth vein expanded to become the five regions' earth vein, Di Zang Sheng's strength rose to five times of before. Negative emotions were also increasing wildly in the humans of all regions, Di Zang Sheng's strength was further soaring because of this!

Duke Long was growing stronger continuously because of heavenly dragon's last stand.

And Di Zang Sheng's strength was growing at an even more horrifying speed than Duke Long's. As such, even though Heavenly Court's main force was here, using all their abilities and staking their lives, they were unable to stop Di Zang Sheng's charge.

Heavenly Court's main force was furious.

"We can't let it move forward."

"We must stop it even if we die!"

"Damned Evil Dragon."

"Get out of my way, let me stop it!" Zhang Fei Xiong suddenly roared, becoming a giant with a bear head and human body. He attacked with no fear of death.

Bam.

A muffled sound echoed, he was directly crushed into meat paste, dying on the spot.

This rank eight transformation path great expert could only obstruct Di Zang Sheng for a brief moment.

"Zhang Fei Xiong..." The eyes of Heavenly Court's immortals were filled with tears.

At the crucial moment, the Heavenly Court members showed no hesitation towards sacrificing themselves!

"Let me." At the next moment, Flesh Whip Immortal went forward. She transformed into an immemorial walking meat tree, which was her strongest form.

Bam.

Another muffled sound echoed, Flesh Whip Immortal was smashed to pieces, her blood splashing everywhere.

"Flesh Whip Immortal!" The group of immortals cried out.

When she was needed, she charged ahead without any regard for herself. A grand rank eight, a genius of her generation, could only stall it for a breath of time.

Even the Southern Border immortals were visibly moved.

What was urging them to do so?

Seemingly... Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had all been like this since ancient times.

Their spirit had never waned, it had instead been fostered and enhanced.

Heavenly Court had never lacked brave members!

Primordial Origin might have passed away, but his spirit did not!

"Unfortunately, your efforts are futile." At Wu Shuai's will, countless clones flew out of Dragon Palace.

They were Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies!

These dream path clones turned into a huge vanguard army and flew in front of Di Zang Sheng, attacking the final sub-formation.

"Watch this!" Under the immortals' expectant gaze, Feng Jin Huang stood up, her youthful face was filled with seriousness and solemness.

She borrowed the immortal formation's strength to activate immortal killer move shatter dream.

Bam bam bam...

Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies exploded directly, becoming lumps of dream realms on the spot that rotated and moved slowly.

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

Feng Jin Huang activated another method.

These restored dream realms transformed back to human form again, but this time, they belonged to Feng Jin Huang.

With Feng Jin Huang here, dream path was no longer Heavenly Court's weakness.

"What about this then!" Before Heavenly Court's force could relax, a large formation was sent out from Dragon Palace at this crucial moment.

Five regional limit formation!

Five colored smoke spouted once again and rapidly spread to cover the whole area.

Heavenly Court's main force had bloodshot eyes as Zhu Que Er shouted hoarsely: "Destroy it!"

Vortex Space Boy and Jun Shen Guang had already moved towards the formation.

"Too late." Zhan Bu Du exclaimed with joy from inside the formation.

He did not let down everyone's expectations, at this crucial moment, he finished repairing the whole formation and joined the battle again!

Five colored smoke expanded and covered the sub-formation.

Puff puff puff.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals were still setting up the formation, they were caught unprepared and coughed blood repeatedly, most fainted on the spot while some even died from the backlash!

By now, they were all exhausted and the five regional limit formation became their death warrant.

As for the Gu Immortals controlling the main formation, they were forced to ease their strength while resisting the injuries from the backlash.

Roar—!

Di Zang Sheng took the chance to attack, it directly smashed into the final sub-formation. The nine-nine consecutive unceasing formation was finally broken at this moment!

The formation collapsed, the obstruction disappeared, Hairy Foot Mountain that had been hidden by the formation got exposed.

This mountain was small and inconspicuous, it was as ordinary as could be but it held Infallible blessed land.

The Gu Immortals who had been controlling the main formation were lying on Hairy Foot Mountain.

The formation's destruction inflicted serious injuries on these Gu Immortals again, almost none of them were in a clear-headed state.

Most of the Gu Immortals had already lost their lives, while a small portion were in a dazed state. Feng Jin Huang, who had been protected tightly, also had a pale face, she fell down to the ground in exhaustion and did not have any strength to escape.

At this moment, she could only look on as Di Zang Sheng came charging, she could do nothing but wait for death.

A strong sense of death suffocated Feng Jin Huang.

"Am I going to die?" At this moment, this young female Gu Master felt a sense of loss.

"Protect Feng Jin Huang!"

"Save her."

"No need to care about Infallible blessed land, the final batch of success dao marks have already been sent to Heavenly Court."

Heavenly Court's main force staked all their energy to rescue Feng Jin Huang.

"Wishful thinking!" The Southern Border Gu Immortals laughed wildly as they used their strength to hold back these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals as much as possible.

Wu Yong's unlimited wind blew while making heavy sounds. This giant tornado stalled a large number of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Jun Shen Guang and Vortex Space Boy charged to the front again. One cultivated light path, another space path, their activation speed of killer moves was fastest.

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Dragon Palace withstood all sorts of explosions and forcibly attacked Jun Shen Guang and Vortex Space Boy.

Jun Shen Guang and Vortex Space Boy finally could not dodge, they were carried away by dreamy light smoke the moment they were struck.

After capturing these two, Dragon Palace had reached its limits and could not capture any more people unless these two were killed.

"Destroy Hairy Foot Mountain and Infallible blessed land!" Wu Yong shouted as he took the lead to charge in front. He was not on Heavenly Court's side and naturally was unaware that Heavenly Court had already completed the task. Even if he were to destroy Infallible blessed land now, it did not have any influence on the big picture.

"Don't even think about it!" A lump of fire obstructed Wu Yong, from which Prince Feng Xian flew out.

"By you alone?!" Wu Yong's eyes shined with sharp killing intent, he suddenly disappeared and when he appeared, he was already behind Prince Feng Xian.

Immortal killer move — Farewell Friend Wind!

"We became friends at first sight, yet you have to go now. This is farewell, my good friend, let me send you off." Wu Yong smiled lightly.

Hearing these words, even Prince Feng Xian, a person who infiltrated and went undercover in Northern Plains for many years, turned pale with fright.

Next, Prince Feng Xian lost control over his body and slowly floated towards the front.

While floating, his hair, clothes, and limbs started to disintegrate.

"Damn it! Farewell friend wind is actually in Wu Yong's hand!" Prince Feng Xian shouted inwardly but was unable to articulate his words.

He could not move at all, none of his methods could be used.

With the final obstruction gone, Wu Yong charged down towards Hairy Foot Mountain like an eagle hunting its prey.

The remaining Heavenly Court members wanted to reinforce but were held back by others.

Wu Yong revealed awe-inspiring might, before he had even truly descended, the wind pressure from him was already as heavy as a mountain, Feng Jin Huang could not even budge from this pressure and slowly closed her eyes in despair.

But the pain that she anticipated did not manifest.

Feng Jin Huang slowly opened her eyes in doubt and saw a figure blocking Wu Yong in front of her like an impenetrable fortress.

The moment she saw this extremely familiar figure, she cried out in joy: "Father!"

The rank eight Gu Immortal who appeared at the crucial moment was none other than Feng Jiu Ge.

He wore a red and white robe, standing straight like a spear or sword.

Hearing Feng Jin Huang's cry, Feng Jiu Ge turned sideways and looked at Feng Jin Huang. His eyes under his sharp brows revealed warmth and concern as well as confidence.

Feng Jiu Ge did not say anything and only nodded at Feng Jin Huang before facing Wu Yong.

But just that nod made Feng Jin Huang feel immense security and let her relax completely. This groundless comfort was completely baffling and had no basis, but Feng Jin Huang believed in it, this was her father Feng Jiu Ge.

Wu Yong's eyes emitted dangerous light.

"Feng Jiu Ge," Wu Yong mumbled this name as he exposed his killing intent: "You stopped me from chasing Fang Yuan before, I will settle the score with you properly now."

He then prepared his killer move, trying to use farewell friend wind again.

Feng Jiu Ge did not dodge or evade, he remained floating in the air as he slowly sang with a smile on his face.

His voice was illusory and deep, it was filled with conflict and was very unique.

Wu Yong was unconsciously influenced by the song, his attack paused.

Initially, the song was like a small stream of water in the mountains, flowing slowly. Gradually, the stream turned into flowing lava that expanded the river's width, in the range of mountains, like a wandering dragon.

"Damn it, what song is this?" Wu Yong's expression changed intensely, he began to struggle with difficulty, he had been the first to be struck by the move because he was the nearest.

The song made Wu Yong feel unwell, it made him feel like he had returned to when he was young, he was always shrouded under his mother Wu Du Xiu's shadow and had received her strict teaching and restrictions. During that time, he could only receive her lessons obediently.

At the next moment, Wu Yong's eyes opened even wider.

The farewell friend wind killer move he had used earlier on Prince Feng Xian had actually stopped.

"What song is this? It can actually break farewell friend wind?" Wu Yong was shaken.

Prince Feng Xian felt a different sensation.

He felt like he had returned to the past when he had disguised his identity and finally cultivated to rank eight in Northern Plains. He had a grotto-heaven and finally had a feeling of joy, no longer having to endure the overbearing attitude of Northern Plains' super force Gong tribe.

Under the effect of destiny song, the Southern Border immortals were weakened and dispirited, on the contrary, Heavenly Court's side felt free and elated, their condition picked up and their injuries recovered.

Destiny song's ability was extremely comprehensive, what was even more amazing was that it could distinguish between allies and enemies. This was something that the previous life's destiny song could never compare to.

Even Wu Shuai and the rest were constrained by the song, only Di Zang Sheng roared and forcibly endured the song, still continuing to charge forward!

Feng Jiu Ge concentrated on Di Zang Sheng. Di Zang Sheng's body was so huge that it almost covered the sky and earth, just its dragon head was as big as a mountain. Feng Jiu Ge, in comparison, was as minuscule as an ant.

But at the next moment, the effects of the song concentrated and focused on Di Zang Sheng.

Di Zang Sheng felt like it had returned to the time when it was suppressed in Hidden Dragon Cave; it was in a dark cage, unable to regain freedom even though it had a thousand desires and endless strength.

Helplessness.

Di Zang Sheng started to slow down.

It wanted to roar and cry out, but it ended up letting out whimpers.

The immortals were shocked.

This scene was too shocking.

Feng Jiu Ge defeated Di Zang Sheng in one move!

This was the strongest legendary immemorial desolate beast of this age!! In the previous life, it could fight Duke Long who was at his final moments of life, if he had not captured Dragon Palace, it would have been impossible for him to handle Di Zang Sheng so easily.

"This is my personal creation, destiny song. It has just been completed, please feel free to critique it." Feng Jiu Ge continued to sing while transmitting his voice.

"Destiny song!!" The immortals, be they enemies or allies, engraved the name of this killer move deep in their hearts.

The moment this move appeared, it became famous.

From today onwards, everyone in the world would know of it!

Destiny was constantly moving, it had ups and downs. Who would not have low points in their life? Even Fang Yuan, even the venerables had times when they were at their lowest points. Destiny song could bring out the lows and highs of the destiny of all living beings.

At times, even heaven and earth will help you, at times, even heroes cannot emerge unscathed!

Feng Jiu Ge's ninth song, sound path rank eight immortal killer move — Destiny Song!

"This is troublesome." Wu Shuai's expression was extremely heavy.

"He actually created the complete destiny song. As expected of Feng Jiu Ge." Zhan Bu Du sighed heavily.

This battle situation was transmitted to Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei was naturally overjoyed.

Feng Jiu Ge had been in a state of comprehension, he took the initiative and requested to explore the River of Time. Qin Ding Ling inspected his luck and saw his fortuitous encounter, so she fully supported it. Fairy Zi Wei had thus secretly arranged a time path Immortal Gu House to send Feng Jiu Ge to the River of Time quietly.

Fairy Zi Wei believed Qin Ding Ling's words and she also saw Feng Jiu Ge's potential, but she had never imagined Feng Jiu Ge would actually give her such a huge surprise!

Rank eight immortal killer move destiny song, just this move alone raised Feng Jiu Ge's strength to the peak, he became one of the strongest people in the world.

Heavenly Court wanted to restore rank nine fate Gu and seize fortune rivalling heaven Gu to try to refine rank ten destiny Gu. Longevity Heaven also had the same plan, but their target was set lower, they wanted to use the damaged fate Gu to refine rank nine destiny Gu.

But both sides had not expected that ahead of them, a Gu Immortal actually created the initial draft of the Immortal Gu recipe of destiny Gu!

Immortal killer moves could be condensed into Immortal Gu recipes.

The best example was Fang Yuan's myriad self Immortal Gu, the refined myriad self Immortal Gu recipe had been derived from the killer move myriad self.

It was no exaggeration to say that this move alone allowed Feng Jiu Ge's name to be written down in history.

Worthy of a Dao Guardian!

Such overwhelming talent, even Fairy Zi Wei felt stunned and dazzled, she admitted her inferiority.

"Father, you are amazing!" Feng Jin Huang stared at Feng Jiu Ge's back with her eyes wide open, feelings of idolization and love almost overflowed.

The girl's heart was filled with pride and joy at this moment.

"Yes, my father has never disappointed me."

At this moment, Feng Jin Huang was filled with bliss as she cheered inwardly: "Father, you are most amazing, your broad shoulders will forever be my most reliable support!"

Chapter 1943: Fang Yuan's Strongest Offense!

Heavenly Court's battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Roaring Wave.

Immortal killer move — Body Flicker.

Duke Long's figure suddenly appeared on the right of Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Too close!

Almost at the same time, the daybreak swords that were floating around Myriad Year Flying Warship swarmed in and submerged Duke Long.

Countless dragon shaped tattoos floated around Duke Long's body, blocking the powerful sword attacks.

This was Duke Long's main defensive killer move — Nine Dragons Protection.

Nine was just a general number implying countless tattoos. This was a rare passive defensive method and usually stayed hidden on Duke Long's skin, but when there was an attack, it activated automatically and did not need Duke Long's wills or thoughts to be maintained.

Duke Long forcibly withstood the daybreak swords' attacks with this move, then clenched his hands into fists.

Immortal killer move — World Shaking Dragon Hammer!

Boom!

The dragon hammer's strike directly sent Myriad Year Flying Warship flying.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was sent flying, but it stopped suddenly. The surrounding space crumbled like countless pieces of glass. These glass pieces were extremely sharp and as long as they touched Myriad Year Flying Warship, they would leave behind deep marks, killing many Gu worms. Fang Yuan, who was standing on the deck, also got a cut on his cheek.

This was Cang Xuan Zi's ability, she used space path killer moves to set up countless traps everywhere in the battlefield, they had extremely high power!

But this scene only flashed in Fang Yuan's mind, it had not happened yet.

This was time path killer move — Three Breaths Future Vision!

Three breaths future vision was an investigative killer move that came from Hei Fan's true inheritance, it allowed the Gu Immortal to see three breaths into the future related to them.

Due to Fang Yuan's dao mark amplification, its power had increased by fifteen hundred times and thus could show its effect even when battling an expert at the level of Duke Long. However, this move was essentially only rank seven, so it did not show effect every time, it succeeded sometimes but failed at other times as well.

At the next moment.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Roaring Wave.

Immortal killer move — Body Flicker.

Duke Long's figure suddenly appeared on the right of Myriad Year Flying Warship, just like the scene displayed by three breaths future vision.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly and controlled Myriad Year Flying Warship to move far away, brushing past the countless space path traps.

"What a pity!" Cang Xuan Zi sighed deeply in her heart, just a little and Fang Yuan would have triggered the space path traps.

She was floating in the air without any obvious movement, but she was secretly and quietly forming and laying space path traps.

After fighting Fang Yuan for a long time, the battle experiences that had remained deep within her memories were coming to life and her methods became more experienced.

After Cang Xuan Zi and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable made a secret agreement three hundred thousand years ago, she had moved to Heavenly Court and lived a peaceful life, never having to fight again. But before this, Cang Xuan Zi's name and the legendary immemorial beast's position were personally established by her!

Fang Yuan controlled Myriad Year Flying Warship and dodged while observing Cang Xuan Zi.

Although Cang Xuan Zi's battle strength was recovering, her combat style was obvious. She retained the habits of fighting as an immemorial desolate plant; her battle style leaned towards staying at one spot and attacking with long ranged attacks, using space path methods to create distance from her enemies before laying space path traps.

Her nature could be seen from her combat style, she liked to fish patiently, this also meant she was not aggressive and would not take risks.

Although many of Cang Xuan Zi's methods were still mysterious, Fang Yuan had already begun to understand the details of Cang Xuan Zi. On the contrary, Duke Long was still unfathomable and not easy to comprehend.

Fang Yuan fought Duke Long in the previous life and he also knew Duke Long's methods for the most part, but Duke Long's combat style was ever-changing, he defended at times while becoming aggressive at other times. He suddenly attacked and evaded at times, making others unable to see a clear pattern.

This combat attainment was not just due to Duke Long's battle experience but also his innate talent!

As far as Fang Yuan was concerned, defeating Cang Xuan Zi might be difficult but he had a high chance. But he was still unable to see even the slightest chance of defeating Duke Long till now.

"Unless I can break Duke Long's defensive killer move!" Fang Yuan analyzed inwardly.

Duke Long's main defensive killer move was nine dragons protection. Fang Yuan was collecting information during the battle and breaking it down.

But his gains were minimal.

It was extremely difficult to break a strong enemy's killer move during a battle.

Compared to nine dragons protection, Fang Yuan wanted to break heavenly dragon's last stand much more. But this killer move left no trace, Fang Yuan did not even have a way to gather its information.

Based on his original expectation, Steal Life was the best method to deal with Duke Long, but it showed no effect even after hitting...

"Wait, I seem to have neglected something?" Suddenly, a light of inspiration flashed past Fang Yuan's mind.

But when he wanted to explore this inspiration, it was interrupted by an attack.

Fang Yuan did not even have to look to know that this was an attack from Demon Judgment Board.

This rank eight Immortal Gu House was truly an annoyance!

It did not have any weakness, its speed was so fast that it did not lose to Myriad Year Flying Warship and had extremely powerful defense. If it was one versus one, Demon Judgment Board could never be Fang Yuan's match, but it would definitely consume some time.

Theft path methods were the best way to deal with this Immortal Gu House, but it was not easy to use them in front of Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi.

Fang Yuan had currently transformed into the immemorial year monkey which coordinated well with Myriad Year Flying Warship. If he transformed his dao marks to theft path, his battle strength would fall greatly, giving Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi an opportunity instead.

What made Fang Yuan even more wary was that even if he were to transform into a theft path immemorial desolate beast and used great thief ghost hand, his attack might not hit Demon Judgment Board. Even if it hit, it might not be able to steal Immortal Gu. Fang Yuan's luck path superiority was already dealt for most part by Qin Ding Ling, Demon Judgment Board moreover had Gu Yue Fang Zheng who restrained Fang Yuan in terms of luck.

So, theft path methods were not the correct methods to change the situation.

"Fang Yuan..." At this time, Fang Zheng who was in charge of Demon Judgment Board had a complicated mood.

Could Fang Yuan be considered his own brother?

No.

Fang Yuan's physical body had changed, his soul was also of an otherworldly demon.

Then, was he a stranger?

No.

The memories of childhood could not be erased, they had once been in each other's company.

Anger?

There was.

Fang Yuan toyed around with him and disregarded his life, he definitely had a sinister scheme for putting him in Lang Ya blessed land.

Hatred?

Definitely.

Fang Yuan killed his own clan and had been the shadow and nightmare of Fang Zheng's childhood.

What else beyond these?

Having experienced many things, Fang Zheng had slowly begun to understand Fang Yuan and even felt some admiration for Fang Yuan.

People often had to compromise in this world. Fang Zheng had started realizing his shallowness and gained an understanding of himself. The so-called A-grade aptitude was just a kind of narcissism, Fang Zheng had already become mature.

Besides understanding and admiration, Fang Zheng even felt a trace of gratitude towards Fang Yuan.

He was grateful to Fang Yuan for creating obstacles for him, for giving him suffering and hardships. These were all wealth that helped Fang Zheng grow to what he was now. If it were not for the hardships during the continental war in Lang Ya blessed land, how could Fang Zheng have merged the various cultivation experiences of the past Demon Judgment Board Lords and created the killer move blood-kin heart revenge?

Fang Zheng had once dreamed of a day where he could fight Fang Yuan and take revenge with his own hands.

But now that the moment really came, Fang Zheng felt a lot different from what he had imagined; he neither felt the pleasure of taking revenge nor felt satisfaction.

His thoughts were complicated, very complicated.

"Duke Long, Cang Xuan Zi, Fang Zheng, and Qin Ding Ling, besides them, there is also Fairy Zi Wei." Fang Yuan's expression turned increasingly serious as he received attacks from all sides.

As Duke Long continued to grow stronger and the coordination of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals became more tight, Fang Yuan's thoughts were almost fully used to maintain this battle.

His ability to analyze the whole situation was continuously falling.

Be it activating killer moves or controlling Myriad Year Flying Warship, both expended a lot of energy. Fang Yuan also needed to be aware of the overall situation, to keep an eye on all the battlefields, and secretly influence the Gu Immortals of other regions.

In fact, Duke Long's group was also in the same state. The battle was becoming more intense, powerful and complicated killer moves involving many Gu worms were activated more frequently, which demanded more attention and control.

"If Fairy Zi Wei recovers, I will be at a disadvantage whether she joins the battle or takes charge of the overall situation." Fang Yuan's eyes shined with coldness.

"Hahaha!" Duke Long suddenly laughed as he got the latest report of the battle in Hairy Foot Mountain, "Fang Yuan, no matter how many times you are reborn, it is useless. Use all your abilities, otherwise it will be too late."

Fang Yuan's expression was grim as he also learned of the recent battle situation.

In the Emperor City battlefield, his clone Fang Di Chang was lost and Divine Bean Palace had defected to the enemy's side. In the Hairy Foot Mountain battlefield, Feng Jiu Ge appeared and used the extremely powerful destiny song, which even made Di Zang Sheng fall into a disadvantage!

Heavenly Court's foundation was truly too deep.

Fang Yuan was not only fighting against Duke Long's group, he was also contending against Heavenly Court's millions of years of accumulation!

The situation in the outside world was not dependable, as such, all the pressure was on Fang Yuan's shoulders.

Fang Yuan's gaze suddenly turned sharp like lightning: "Indeed, I cannot hold back anymore."

He was not able to find Duke Long's weakness, but with the situation forcing him, even if there was no weakness, Fang Yuan had to use his full strength.

Myriad Year Flying Warship rose to the air, rapidly creating distance as Fang Yuan began preparing a killer move.

Duke Long did not give chase, he remained standing in the air, looking above with concentration. His expression looked like he was facing a great enemy, he no longer looked down on Fang Yuan.

Cang Xuan Zi took a deep breath and was extremely vigilant.

Qin Ding Ling, Fang Zheng, as well as Fairy Zi Wei who was recuperating at the edge of the battlefield fixed their gazes on Fang Yuan.

Even Bing Sai Chuan, who was crazily attacking the refinement path formation and bombarding Heaven Overseeing Tower, split a portion of his attention towards Fang Yuan's every move.

Everyone was aware the victory or defeat in the following battle could very likely determine the outcome of the whole situation.

Immortal killer move — Twelve Zodiac battle formation.

Fang Yuan first summoned twelve immemorial year beasts, this method had already been revealed before.

But different from before, the Twelve Zodiac battle formation did not condense into a giant monster but transformed into a golden helm.

The helm was like a carriage wheel, it had six spokes and twelve handles; each handle had a carving of a year beast.

The Twelve Zodiac battle helm flew towards Myriad Year Flying Warship and merged into it rapidly. The dazzling silver Myriad Year Flying Warship suddenly had a large golden image that looked like flying sand, transforming at every moment. The golden image transformed into a coiling dragon at one time, a giant tiger at other time, a crowing rooster, or a ramming ox...

The twelve immemorial year beasts combined perfectly with Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Fang Yuan's previous concept was fully displayed to the world at this moment.

"He actually merged an ancient battle formation into an Immortal Gu House perfectly!" Qin Ding Ling's eyes opened wide.

Fang Zheng looked on, dumbfounded.

"Such amazing talent!" Even Duke Long could not help but praise.

He had never seen this sight, Fang Yuan was the first to achieve this in history!

Although it was said that ancient battle formations and Immortal Gu Houses were immortal killer moves in essence, no one had succeeded in combining these two killer moves prior to Fang Yuan!

"Careful, it is attacking!" Cang Xuan Zi shouted with a trace of panic. Myriad Year Flying Warship was letting out a frightening aura that even shook her.

Immortal killer move — Daybreak Torrent!

Myriad Year Flying Warship swooped down, leaving behind a trail of sonic booms.

It was already an outstanding rank eight Immortal Gu House, the Twelve Zodiac battle formation that merged with it even possessed a mighty strength that could match Duke Long's. After they merged, their strength combined to a horrifying level!

Duke Long roared as he unleashed a qi wall.

Myriad Year Flying Warship's momentum was slightly slowed before it broke through Duke Long's qi wall.

Duke Long frowned as he activated qi wall again.

Myriad Year Flying Warship broke the qi wall again.

Duke Long erected the qi wall again while Myriad Year Flying Warship broke it again. After five times, Myriad Year Flying Warship's momentum finally fell sharply.

Fang Yuan sneered, immortal killer move — Myriad Year Hunting!

At the next moment, the River of Time phantom under Myriad Year Flying Warship enlarged suddenly, countless year beasts surged out like a huge tide!

The sky-covering year beast army began attacking the immortal graveyard like a giant tsunami that engulfed everything.

The large army had countless year beasts, with large numbers of ancient year beasts, and even immemorial year beasts were not in a small quantity.

What was even more terrifying was that this year beast army moved to Fang Yuan's will!

"Terrifying! Just this move alone can let Fang Yuan attack any super force in the world by himself!"

"Does he want to summon all the year beasts in the River of Time?"

"This is almost like a copy of call of the ancient! It is just that while Red Lotus's method summons past Gu Immortal experts, Fang Yuan is summoning the year beasts in the River of Time!"

"But didn't myriad year hunting only attract year beasts and had no ability to control them?"

"This is probably the qualitative change caused by the merging of Twelve Zodiac battle formation!"

Heavenly Court's side was shaken.

Fang Yuan's trump cards were truly peerless, he just used one and it showed towering might. Duke Long, Cang Xuan Zi and the rest immediately felt troubled.

The scale of this year beast army was too large, moreover, Fang Yuan was still summoning them with no end in sight.

The year beast army scattered and spread everywhere like a blossoming flower, attacking every corner of Heavenly Court; Heavenly Court's side, which lacked manpower, was unable to defend properly.

Cang Xuan Zi clenched her teeth as she continuously activated space path killer moves to kill as many year beasts as possible in an attempt to ease the current pressure.

"Be careful!!" Duke Long suddenly shouted.

"Huh?" Cang Xuan Zi seemingly saw the image of a small knife, her pupils shrunk to the size of pins as she reacted but it was too late, she was already struck!

"How is this possible... so fast? I clearly arranged..."

Cang Xuan Zi gazed at Fang Yuan in incredulity. Her body stiffened, a bloody hole appeared on her forehead, piercing through the back of her head. The injury was filled with dense time path dao marks that even a legendary immemorial beast's self-recovery could not regenerate.

Immortal killer move — Time Cutting Edge!

This was the supreme method of Central Continent's Bo clan, once this knife was shot out, it would not miss, anyone hit by it would die. It had once shaken the whole Central Continent with terror.

The killer move's contents were extremely complex and its steps were ever-changing. Among Fang Yuan's methods, it was no doubt the number one in terms of complexity.

The more absurd thing was its activation conditions, its activation time could not cross three breaths. For this, Fang Yuan had to use the supplementary killer move shrink time every time he activated this move.

Its side-effect was also terrifying, every time it was used, a portion of the memories related to it would disappear. It was like an eraser, erasing the enemy while consuming itself.

After Cang Xuan Zi was struck, Fang Yuan's mind immediately turned blank, most of the memories of time cutting edge turned vague.

"At this rate, after I attack Duke Long with it, I will completely lose this move." Fang Yuan's mind was as calm as the snowy plains.

He glanced at Duke Long.

Without realizing, Duke Long retreated several steps.

Boom!

A loud sound resounded as Cang Xuan Zi fell to the ground. Her body returned to its original form in mid-air, turning into a giant green vine.

This green vine once held the sky and was like an extremely eye-catching heavenly pillar, but now it collapsed in the immortal graveyard without moving and had no life force.

The damage to the immortal graveyard from this crash was much more than the sum of all previous damage, but Duke Long did not care about this. His gaze was fixed on Fang Yuan.

He needed to concentrate fully to have a chance at blocking the time cutting edge that was amplified by at least fifteen hundred times!

In Demon Judgment Board, Fang Zheng's mouth was opened wide and his head was soaked with sweat as he looked at the vast heaven vine that had collapsed on the ground.

Qin Ding Ling who was behind him was rigid like a statue.

"If this move had struck Demon Judgment Board, could we block it?" The same doubt flashed in the two's minds but neither had the confidence to say they could defend against it!

This move was too horrifying, one move and it was unknown whether Cang Xuan Zi was still alive, her aura could not be detected.

"Don't be terrified, he used myriad year hunting's aura to conceal this move. If he used this move alone, its aura would be too grand and would not be hidden." At the crucial moment, Fairy Zi Wei's words spread throughout the battlefield.

"As expected of a wisdom path great expert." Fang Yuan snorted coldly as the flaw was exposed.

Duke Long's expression eased a little.

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan left Myriad Year Flying Warship and charged forward alone.

"He is going all out!" Duke Long's heart shook.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Beings Assimilation Transformation.

Immortal killer move——Immemorial Sword Dragon!

Roar—!

Fang Yuan immediately transformed into a giant dragon.

Immemorial sword dragon!

The dragon was over three hundred meters in length, its two horns were long and sharp, its eyes were silver-white, its scales were pure-white and emitted dense sword intent.

All of Fang Yuan's dao marks were transformed into sword path dao marks.

And everyone knew that sword path's superiority lied in offense!

At this moment, Fang Yuan finally showed his strongest attacking form.

Chapter 1944: Swords Destroy Immortal Graveyard

Roar—!

The tyrannical immemorial dragon roared as it swung its tail and moved, its speed was so fast that it left behind a white afterimage at its original spot.

Bam.

Demon Judgment Board was hit head-on and fell like a meteor.

Duke Long immediately rushed forward to reinforce it.

Fang Yuan sneered and rose to the air suddenly, leaving behind an afterimage.

In the air, he suddenly changed from an extremely active state to extremely still and his aura erupted.

Sword path killer move — Triple Layered Sword Wave!

The offensive killer move that was amplified by at least fifteen hundred times had power that was completely different from the past.

Giant waves surged and filled the battlefield. Every drop of the silver-white waves had sword path's strength and was extremely sharp.

The sword waves did not target Demon Judgment Board or Duke Long but attacked the immortal graveyard.

From the start, Fang Yuan's main target was the immortal graveyard.

Duke Long clenched his teeth as he used self-moving dragon qi wall.

The qi wall could only hold back the sword waves for eight breaths of time before crumbling to pieces.

Duke Long let out a muffled groan as blood flowed out of his nose.

He wanted to continue using the qi wall killer move but the towering sword waves had already reached the immortal graveyard.

Heavenly Court could defend with ease earlier because of Cang Xuan Zi's space path methods that could shorten and lengthen distance. This gave Duke Long enough time to repeatedly activate qi wall to put up defense.

But now that Cang Xuan Zi's vitality was gone and was lying dead on the ground, there was no more protection of space path methods, Duke Long had no time to activate the qi wall killer move again.

Duke Long was not a rank nine but a rank eight like Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan's dao marks far surpassed his and he could only count on heavenly dragon's last stand. But regretfully, till now, although Duke Long was becoming stronger constantly, there was still some gap between him and Fang Yuan. Especially when Fang Yuan revealed his trump cards and showed his strongest attacking form.

"No—!" Duke Long let out a sad and furious roar as he looked at the sword waves engulf and sweep through the immortal graveyard.

The Gu Immortals sleeping in the immortal graveyard could not resist at all, they were sliced into pieces by the sword waves.

Even the enormous vast heaven vine was being cut down repeatedly by the extremely sharp sword waves. Cang Xuan Zi did not wake up during the whole process, it seemed she was truly dead!

Demon Judgment Board rose to the air but Fang Zheng was dazed: "He really did it, he destroyed the immortal graveyard!"

"The immortal graveyard!!!" Compared to Fang Zheng, Fairy Zi Wei and Qin Ding Ling had a greater reaction. They were veteran rank eights and genuine members of Heavenly Court.

The immortal graveyard was not just an important area of Heavenly Court, it was even more a spiritual sacred land to them, it was defiled by Fang Yuan now. Countless predecessors sleeping inside were killed like chickens without being able to resist!

"Fang Yuan, I want you to die!" Qin Ding Ling cried out in sorrow.

"We have failed you all, seniors…" With a loud thud, Old Man Zheng Yuan fell as he knelt on the ground in Central Great Hall, crying silently.

Fairy Zi Wei felt her entire body turning numb, the immortal graveyard was heavily damaged, and as the leader and planner of Heavenly Court, she could not shirk this responsibility!

"It's me, I am too incompetent…" Tears of sorrow trickled down Fairy Zi Wei's face.

In Imperfection Regret Pavilion, the images began to fluctuate intensely.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette wanted to make a move but was firmly held up by Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette, she could only stare at Fang Yuan slaughtering Heavenly Court's members and destroying the immortal graveyard.

Shock and anger filled Star Constellation's silhouette's face, her gaze was icy cold as she looked at her opponent: "Good, very good!"

Limitless' silhouette smiled: "This is pretty good. Back when I invaded Heavenly Court, I also wanted to destroy the immortal graveyard. But bearing in mind that the scale of variant humans at that time was still enormous, and thinking for the humans, I did not make a move."

"Hmph, so what if you destroyed the immortal graveyard or even the whole of Heavenly Court. As long as you don't destroy fate Gu, with heaven's will continuing to favor humans, Central Continent can still establish a second Heavenly Court, or third or fourth immortal graveyard!" Star Constellation's silhouette retorted.

"You are right." Limitless Demon Venerable's silhouette heaved a sigh: "Fate Gu is the fundamental cause of your Heavenly Court, as long as it remains, your Heavenly Court will stand erect no matter how many losses you suffer. Instead, the more you suffer defeat, the tougher you will become, old will be eliminated and new blood will be brought in, you will be closer to the tides of the new era."

Eras changed constantly and Gu Immortal cultivation also developed without stopping.

The prosperity and decline of qi path and strength path was proof of this.

Limitless Demon Venerable had not touched the immortal graveyard back then because of this consideration. It was better to spare the qi path and strength path Gu Immortals who were left behind by the eras than let Heavenly Court bounce back by absorbing large amounts of rule path, wisdom path, and other paths' Gu Immortals who would emerge in response to this.

"I am really curious, how long can you last over there now that the immortal graveyard is destroyed?" Limitless' silhouette said with a smile.

Star Constellation's silhouette could no longer be indifferent: "You are disregarding the big picture and bringing demise to the rule of humanity! You are unworthy of being a human venerable."

Limitless' silhouette smiled coldly: "My main body was bound by this responsibility back then, but now… hasn't humanity already achieved this goal? Humans should now pursue an even greater goal. You should know what I mean."

Star Constellation's silhouette narrowed her eyes, falling into a rare silence.

"Fang Yuan, I will tear out your tendons and burn you to ashes!!" Duke Long roared, his anger and hatred had accumulated to an extreme level and he charged towards Fang Yuan without regarding anything.

Fang Yuan dodged and did not fight with Duke Long, he continued to activate triple layered sword wave.

Swoosh! Swoosh! Swoosh!

The immortal graveyard was completely covered by sword waves, the sword waves even dug into the ground, not letting go of any hibernating immortal.

Heavenly Court's millions of years of accumulation was destroyed overnight!

"Ahhhhh!" Duke Long's hair was a mess, his face was distorted, and his eyes were bloodshot.

Every attack to the immortal graveyard was like a strike to his heart; he was bleeding internally and overwhelmed with grief.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Offspring.

At this critical juncture, Duke Long roared with fury; his purple dragon scales flew out and mixed with his blood, transforming into dragonman Gu Immortals.

They were of all shapes and sizes, with all kinds of appearances. There were rank six, rank seven, and even rank eight dragonmen.

Duke Long was not an enslavement path Gu Immortal but he had a similar killer move.

"This is a transformation path killer move that contains human path profundity!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk as he ridiculed: "Duke Long, oh Duke Long, you massacred the dragonman race back then, so the reason was to refine them into a killer move. Hahaha, how is your action any different from a demonic immortal? You disregarded morals and ethics, you trampled on your own blood and kin. Not only did you kill all your children and grandchildren, you even refined them into puppets to fight for you!!"

Duke Long did not refute Fang Yuan's accusation, deep sadness showed in his eyes as he charged towards Fang Yuan again.

At the same time, the large number of dragonman Gu Immortals spread like a blooming flower, blocking the sword waves as well as countless year beasts.

At the level of Duke Long, there were indeed no apparent weaknesses.

A huge chaotic battle unfolded in Heavenly Court.

Demon Judgment Board was paving paths of blood through the year beast army. But the atmosphere inside Demon Judgment Board was stifling, Qin Ding Ling and Fang Zheng were both silent.

Duke Long's dragon offspring killer move was indeed using the members of the dragonman race, Fang Yuan's accusation was not false. It was no wonder Duke Long rarely used this move, he was forced to use it now because of Fang Yuan.

Many dragonman Gu Immortals surrounded the immemorial sword dragon.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he had already activated triple layered sword wave, he now activated another immortal killer move, golden thread sword.

Immediately, the sword dragon's body turned hazy and its every scale emitted soft yellow light.

Each scale suddenly shot out a golden thread.

The number of scales on the immemorial sword dragon was the number of golden threads shot out, they were incomparably fast.

The golden threads pierced every obstacle in their way, the encircling dragonman Gu Immortals resembled honeycombs as the countless golden threads passed them.

Bam bam bam…

Suffering such a heavy injury, these dragonman Gu Immortals were unable to maintain their shape as they detonated softly, returning to scales and blood droplets.

Fang Yuan cleared all the enemies in his surroundings, the sword waves which he had activated just before were still spreading as he rode the waves down.

The immortal graveyard was already wiped out, the greatest variable was destroyed, and now, Fang Yuan charged towards Duke Long.

Cang Xuan Zi had no vitality, her vine body was also in a miserable state. Demon Judgment Board was unable to fight Fang Yuan by itself, if Duke Long fell, who could stop Fang Yuan?

Immortal killer move — Five Finger Fist Heart Sword!

Dragon claws clenched tightly, Fang Yuan's aura suddenly fell to almost a negligible level.

However, warning signs were ringing in Duke Long's mind. He shot forward, his purple-gold dragon-shaped qi flickered constantly and his figure appeared and disappeared, moving in all directions as he tried to evade crazily.

First sword!

Fang Yuan's dragon pupils let out a strange light as a sword light shot out of his claws.

Fast! Fast! Fast!

The sword light's speed was beyond belief.

Duke Long had just seen the light shoot out of Fang Yuan's claws when he found the sword light was already in front of him.

In an almost impossible situation, he forcibly turned his body to one side.

The sword light brushed past him.

Blood splattered, a large cut spread from his left shoulder to his left chest. The cut was clean; bones, scales and even a part of the left lung were gone completely.

Five finger fist heart sword was truly horrifying!

If this had struck Duke Long's head, it would have been severed immediately.

Since the start of the battle, this was the first time Duke Long felt a fatal threat. It had been a long time since he felt such a feeling.

Duke Long gave a loud roar and shot towards Fang Yuan like lightning.

Fang Yuan applauded inwardly.

Every sword in five finger fist heart sword required time to prepare. Duke Long saw through this weakness and took the chance to attack.

Fang Yuan's dragon body moved as he retreated, trying to pull some distance from Duke Long.

Sword path's offensive advantage was obvious, if it were an ordinary opponent, Fang Yuan could directly smash through them. But Duke Long was an extremely powerful expert, he could not be careless.

Chapter 1945: Combat System

Fang Yuan's immemorial sword dragon form similarly possessed an advantage in speed. Duke Long tried his best in chasing but found that he could not shorten the distance easily.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Gate!

A dragon gate appeared, there were two red pillars by the side with a dragon coiling around each of them, their upper body left the pillars and gathered in the middle, forming the top of the gate. The dragon mouths were open with a radiant dragon pearl in each of them, forming a scene of two dragons and two pearls.

Two dragon gates appeared simultaneously, one appeared in front of Duke Long while the other appeared behind Fang Yuan.

Duke Long disappeared into the dragon gate in front of him and appeared from the dragon gate behind Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's mind rang with warning signals as he dodged immediately, but Duke Long used qi engulfing mountains and rivers to delay his speed.

Immortal killer move — Chaotic Dragon Fist!

At the next moment, Duke Long's fists smashed upon immemorial sword dragon's head and kept on punching it, forcefully knocking Fang Yuan down to the immortal graveyard.

Bam.

The immemorial sword dragon crashed fiercely on the ground, dust, soil and stones flew everywhere.

Although the immemorial sword dragon struggled to raise its head, its claws were still intact and it continued to shoot the second sword light.

Five finger fist heart sword, second sword!

Duke Long was already on maximum alert. The moment Fang Yuan moved, he immediately dodged and appeared on Fang Yuan's dragon back.

The second sword struck air, brushing past the dragon body and piercing the sky, forming a vacuum along the way.

Five finger fist heart sword's sword lights were extremely fast but they could not curve. Duke Long might not be able to ward off the sword light but he could dodge. It was somewhat difficult to dodge the sword light, but he could observe Fang Yuan's movement and judge when he was going to use the sword light, and thereby, dodge in advance.

Undoubtedly, five finger fist heart sword was an extremely powerful killer move and it had a huge advantage compared to time cutting edge — it would not be forgotten.

But because of Duke Long's proper battle tactic, five finger fist heart sword became useless, Fang Yuan's immemorial sword dragon had to face Duke Long in close combat.

In just a dozen or so breaths of time, Fang Yuan had already received many heavy strikes from Duke Long's dragon fists.

There had never been a strongest Immortal Gu or killer move, only Gu Immortal!

Five finger fist heart sword's most ideal environment was when the first sword was released. Fang Yuan was quite far from Duke Long and could use it for long-range attack while he was in an invulnerable position. Even if Duke Long's reaction was extremely keen, he would be hard-pressed to defend against them and every sword could push him to a near-death state.

But when Duke Long closed in the distance and forced close combat, Fang Yuan's dragon body instead became the obstacle for the sword lights and even became a cover for Duke Long.

Looking over the battle, Duke Long could be said to have restrained Fang Yuan's five finger fist heart sword by using dragon gate. Without some distance, there was no space to effectively use five finger fist heart sword.

So, after the second sword, Fang Yuan immediately stopped using five finger fist heart sword and turned to golden thread sword.

Duke Long saw Fang Yuan's dragon scales beginning to flicker with yellow light, he immediately chose to retreat far away with dragon gate.

Countless golden threads covered every inch around Fang Yuan, but Duke Long had already retreated.

But there was no issue, Fang Yuan once again pulled apart some distance between him and Duke Long, he could continue using five finger fist heart sword.

Duke Long's situation turned dangerous, he had no choice but to get near Fang Yuan again and attempt close combat.

When he approached Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan would need to cancel five finger fist heart sword and change to other methods to fight Duke Long.

"This demon has modified five finger fist heart sword to this degree! He can casually cancel the killer move with no backlash. Or should I say that he has modified every sword strike into an individual move." Duke Long's thoughts moved rapidly.

Five finger fist heart sword was Bo Qing's trump card, how could Heavenly Court not know of it?

Duke Long knew a lot of information and it would have been easily countered if Fang Yuan had not modified it.

Duke Long's dao marks were lower than Fang Yuan's so he could not use defensive killer moves to ward off Fang Yuan's various sword path methods, his best option was to dodge.

Fortunately, he had much more battle experience than Fang Yuan.

More importantly, as long as he did not die, he would continue to grow stronger along with his shrinking lifespan!

"Although I modified five finger fist heart sword and am able to cancel it freely, the amount of thoughts required have increased sharply, which makes me unable to use other offensive methods at the same time… the other problem is that Duke Long is getting stronger!" Fang Yuan was feeling anxious.

Previously, he could suppress Duke Long and Cang Xuan Zi, mostly because of his battle tactic — Fang Yuan attacked the immortal graveyard, Heavenly Court had no choice but to defend with all their strength and take a beating passively.

Now, the immortal graveyard was destroyed by Fang Yuan. There might be some hibernating Gu Immortals still alive in there somewhere, but Duke Long no longer was burdened.

Duke Long could now advance or retreat, he immediately showed his true strength and aura in battle.

Fang Yuan battled Duke Long, both were in a stalemate.

Duke Long was happy to see this, but Fang Yuan was not.

So, he turned his head and spat out a waterfall.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Thought Sword Waterfall.

The sword waterfall crashed down with a huge momentum, every drop of water was a sword thought.

Immortal killer move — Swordsman!

Sword thoughts surged and collided, forming human shaped warriors. They had the appearance of Fang Yuan and were wielding long swords. Countless swordsmen charged forward.

Fang Yuan created this move after becoming a human path grandmaster, it contained the profundities of sword path and human path.

The moment Duke Long saw this killer move, he retreated.

Fang Yuan took the chance to get free and charged towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Outside Heaven Overseeing Tower, Calamity Luck Altar was destroying the refinement path formation with ease. And inside the tower, Qi Ci Lang was struggling against the remaining jade light on his body.

Duke Long paled with fright when he saw Fang Yuan's movement.

Demon Judgment Board went forward to block the path but was sent flying by one strike from Fang Yuan.

Right at this crucial moment, the sound of singing suddenly appeared in the battlefield and coiled around the immemorial sword dragon's body.

Fang Yuan suddenly felt his condition slipping rapidly, like he had returned to the low point of his life where his actions were controlled by others, his talents and ambitions unable to be expressed, his freedom was lost and his future was dark.

The immemorial sword dragon's speed fell sharply.

Duke Long quickly caught up and blocked Fang Yuan: "Great job, Feng Jiu Ge! Fairy Zi Wei!"

At the crucial moment, Feng Jiu Ge's destiny song successfully obstructed Fang Yuan.

And the one who had guided him in time was Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei had opened Central Heaven Gate.

This Immortal Gu House was the gateway to Heavenly Court, it had the ability to transport people but it was far inferior to the enormous teleportation Gu formation and was only for convenience.

Destiny song continued, Fang Yuan's battle strength kept falling while Duke Long strength's kept increasing.

Boom boom boom!

The immemorial sword dragon was beaten back repeatedly by Duke Long and had no way to approach Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Since the battle started, this was the first time Fang Yuan fell into such a disadvantage. With no other choice, he stopped all sword path killer moves and began preparing reverse flow protection seal.

Duke Long saw him retreating and his aura fluctuating, he immediately knew Fang Yuan was preparing some other killer move but why would he give him the chance?

Duke Long roared, the purple-gold dragon-shaped qi around him chased and attacked Fang Yuan like a storm.

Fang Yuan's immemorial sword dragon body was lacerated with scales and blood flying everywhere. What was even more terrifying was Duke Long's that chaotic dragon fist could disturb thoughts, causing Fang Yuan's killer moves to fail when activating.

At this difficult time, Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture slightly and released the accumulated Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies flew towards Duke Long and self-detonated.

Duke Long was extremely wary and dodged immediately, stopping his offenses. Fang Yuan got some time and successfully activated reverse flow protection seal.

Duke Long could not help but sigh when he saw this move. The timing just now was perfect but he did not grab it, he had exchanged many moves with Fang Yuan and saw through Fang Yuan's fighting style.

When Fang Yuan transformed into an immemorial beast or plant using the transformation path killer move, he could also transform all his dao marks into the same path. On such a basis, any killer move he used would have amplified strength. Even rank seven killer moves would be able to threaten rank eights.

Fang Yuan had many methods, it was very difficult to imagine that he had accumulated and cultivated them to such a degree in less than one hundred years. Even if he had venerable inheritances, it was still a shocking achievement.

Duke Long was certain: As long as Fang Yuan had enough time, he could reach an unprecedented height. Fortunately, fate Gu's recovery was the crucial point and Fang Yuan had no choice but to invade Heavenly Court in advance.

Fang Yuan might be able to rely on some profound and terrifying methods to win against most of the enemies in the world. But facing an existence like Duke Long, a few methods were far from enough, he also needed a combat system that was sufficiently powerful and stable, with ample trump cards.

Just like Duke Long, his transformation path and qi path methods formed two sets of combat systems.

Nine dragons protection formed powerful defense, clear dragon vision was used for scouting, dragon claw strike, chaotic dragon fist, spiraling dragon fangs, and world shaking dragon hammer were in charge of offense; these four methods covered close, mid-range, and long range combat. World shaking dragon hammer was even more powerful and had the strength to turn around a situation. Dragon roaring wave and body flicker were standard movement methods and there was also dragon gate for long distance movement. Dragon offspring made up for the lack of capability to fight a group. In this combat system, the strongest method was heavenly dragon's last stand.

As for his qi path system: there was qi wall and self-moving dragon qi wall as defensive methods; qi breath mountain, hidden dragon qi explosion, qi engulfing mountains and rivers, great qi hand explosion, and qi current scissors were offensive killer moves. Compared to his transformation path system, these offensive methods had much more obvious long range power. Purple-gold dragon-shaped qi was a jack of all trades, this killer move was so excellent that it provided help to Duke Long in all aspects. Naturally, its most important use was still for movement. Reverse worm dragon was a killer move that was specially prepared to target battlefield killer moves. The trump card of this qi path combat system was triple qi retraction.

Duke Long's two combat systems included all aspects like offense, defense, movement, and so on, they also did not have weaknesses or gaps in the various aspects. What was remarkable was these two battles styles could complement each other. For instance, transformation path's offensive methods were stronger in close and mid-range combat, while weak in long-range combat. Meanwhile, qi path's offensive methods were the exact opposite.

Comparatively, there was no need for many trump cards. One for each system, two methods were enough.

In a real battle, the most useful were still those standard killer moves. For example, Duke Long had triple qi retraction, but he had not used it once in the fight with Fang Yuan. The battle was extremely fierce and Fang Yuan was not stupid enough to give Duke Long the opportunity to use it.

Another example was Fang Yuan's five finger fist heart sword, this was a trump card method. But even though Fang Yuan used it, the effect was not decisive for the battle. Duke Long was still able to maintain the stalemate and it was essentially because his combat systems were even more comprehensive than Fang Yuan's.

Chapter 1946: Zi Wei's Eerie Change

How many combat systems did Fang Yuan have?

Form what Duke Long saw, Fang Yuan only had two mature combat systems.

One was time path, and the other was sword path.

The time path system was the most comprehensive; three breaths future vision, year beast summoning, Myriad Year Flying Warship, spring scissors, winter coat, autumn perception, summer fan, as well as spring ploughing, summer hoeing, autumn harvest, winter storage, and so on covered the two main domains of battle and immortal aperture management. There were two trump cards; time cutting edge that was combined with shrink time, and the other was spring autumn success, the core of which was Spring Autumn Cicada!

Sword path had immemorial sword dragon transformation, triple layered sword wave, golden thread sword, dark assassination, myriad thought sword waterfall, swordsman, and other methods. Its trump card was five finger fist heart sword. This combat system took offense to the extreme, being even more powerful than time path style in this aspect, especially five finger fist heart sword which was modified by Fang Yuan. But there was nothing to commend about it in other fields, Duke Long's combat systems were much superior in terms of movement, healing and other aspects. This formed shortcomings. In front of an enemy with extremely rich battle experience like Duke Long, these shortcomings turned into weaknesses which held back the offensive prowess of the sword path system.

Besides these two systems, Fang Yuan had many qi path methods as well, but as far as Duke Long was concerned, it was incomplete. Unlimited qi sea was clearly a trump card with a power that could break the primordial qi wall, but it had not been used after the first time, and it looked like the possibility of it being used again was low.

In the soul path aspect, Duke Long knew Fang Yuan had plenty of methods and the trump card killer move was no doubt Luo Po seal. But Heavenly Court and Duke Long had already made sufficient preparations for this. Fang Yuan not using any soul path methods from the start was a wise move.

Besides these, reverse flow protection seal was of rule path, myriad self was human path, strength path giant hand belonged to strength path, familiar face was transformation path, lead soul into dream, Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation, and switch soul in dream were dream path killer moves. These methods were terrifying, but they were all independent moves resembling large pearls, while a mature combat system was a pearl necklace formed from methods that complemented each other. This necklace formed from small pearls was more valuable than the large pearls.

Against most Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan could rely on the large pearls to change the situation and determine victory. But in front of Duke Long, the weaknesses of Fang Yuan's combat systems became conspicuous.

"Fang Yuan, what you lack is time and I believe you have already felt it, it is such a pity, a mature combat system needs at least a few hundred years of accumulation!" Duke Long looked at Fang Yuan, his gaze sharp as blade: "Even if you used the inheritances left by predecessors to hasten your growth, it is still not perfect enough."

He activated spiraling dragon fangs to attack Fang Yuan from a distance but they were blocked by reverse flow protection seal.

Duke Long was not discouraged, reverse flow protection seal was quite powerful but it lacked a mature style to support it and make up for its weakness. Reverse flow protection seal's greatest weakness was that it expended Reverse Flow River, despite Fang Yuan conserving it as much as possible after his rebirth, how could it endure such intense expenditure?

Reverse flow protection seal was an immortal killer move that used Reverse Flow River as the core, its defensive strength was terrifying and could reflect almost all external attacks. This move was created by Fang Yuan, from which one could see his astonishing talents. Unfortunately, Fang Yuan lacked a stable combat system for this trump card. For instance, supplementary defensive killer moves to defend and reduce external attacks, or a killer move to increase the power of reverse flow protection seal, or methods to restore Reverse Flow River itself.

Suppose reverse flow protection seal was a fish with exquisite flavor. Although it would be a delicacy even if it was eaten raw, if it was seasoned with salt, it could be turned into salted fish that could be stored for a long time. If it was accompanied with other ingredients like sugar, ginger, spring onion, or garlic, it could turn into all kinds of delicious meals, providing much more flavors.

Compared to Heavenly Court and Duke Long, Fang Yuan's accumulation was still insufficient.

He could not avoid falling into a predicament.

Duke Long attacked again and again while enduring reverse flow protection seal's backlash, forcefully expending Reverse Flow River. His healing methods were also extraordinary.

Feng Jiu Ge's destiny song was shrouding over Fang Yuan all the time. Destiny song interchanged between strong and weak, triggering counterattacks from reverse flow protection seal. The profundities of the song actually weakened Fang Yuan even with reverse flow protection seal activated, but the weakening was much smaller.

What was even worse was that destiny song weakened Fang Yuan while amplifying Duke Long's strength. Duke Long's battle strength soared, growing increasingly stronger, he had the complete upper hand and his attacks were like tidal waves, showing extreme power!

Fang Yuan canceled immemorial sword dragon transformation and returned to his human form. The sword dragon's body was enormous, using reverse flow protection seal on it expended Reverse Flow River much faster, it was much more steady with a human body.

Fang Yuan counterattacked continuously using Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

But soon, these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were also targeted, they detonated and turned into dream realms. The dream realms then transformed back into new Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies which fought for Heavenly Court.

It was Feng Jin Huang!

Fairy Zi Wei had not only recalled Feng Jiu Ge through Central Heaven Gate, she had also recalled Feng Jin Huang. With her here, Fang Yuan's dream path methods would be highly restrained.

Sure enough, Fang Yuan's dream path methods were all targeted and dealt with.

"Feng Jin Huang!" Fang Yuan frowned inwardly: 'In the previous life, she used the immortal Gu formation to activate immortal level dream path killer move and spoiled my plan. And now, she is using immortal formation or an Immortal Gu House to target me once again?'

Fang Yuan really wanted to find her precise location and deal with her, but he did not have the freedom to do so at this moment.

He was not even able to approach Heaven Overseeing Tower, becoming further and further away from it.

The reason was that his opponents were Duke Long and Feng Jiu Ge!

The current and previous Dao Guardians had joined hands!

As for Fang Zheng and Qin Ding Ling in Demon Judgment Board, they were no longer able to interfere and began to deal with the year beasts and swordsmen that were all over Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court's main force also started returning to Heavenly Court from Hairy Foot Mountain through Central Heaven Gate and joined in the clearing up work.

Year beasts and swordsmen were not their opponents and were defeated again and again.

Calamity Luck Altar was the focus of the joint attacks of Heavenly Court's main force, some even entered Heaven Overseeing Tower; Qi Ci Lang could not move properly, his situation turning perilous.

"Not good! Heavenly Court's main force has returned, doesn't this mean Infallible blessed land has lost its purpose? Heavenly Court possesses enough success dao marks and can restore Fate completely." Fang Yuan's face was grim, bad news was coming one after the other, and the situation was turning extremely disadvantageous and dangerous.

"Fairy Zi Wei, use benevolent equality quickly, his reverse flow protection seal will shatter soon!" Duke Long transmitted his voice.

"Yes!" At this moment, Fairy Zi Wei had already stabilized her injuries and could battle again. She activated an Immortal Gu House and flew to the sky, her sight contained Duke Long, Fang Yuan, as well as Feng Jiu Ge and the rest.

Immortal killer move — Benevolent Equality.

"Benevolent equality activated successfully, Fang Yuan won't be able to escape this time!" Fairy Zi Wei transmitted her voice.

"Good job, Zi Wei." Duke Long laughed heartily and his attacks became more violent.

Fang Yuan was forced to retreat again and again.

"It is useless now, Fang Yuan, no matter how you persist, you will still be defeated." Fairy Zi Wei smiled.

But at the next moment, she heard a female voice: "Is that so?"

"Who said that?" Fairy Zi Wei was shocked, this voice was familiar and yet strange, what made her shocked was she had never detected any Gu Immortal existences near her.

"What are you looking for? I am you." Fairy Zi Wei was horrified to discover that she was actually replying to herself.

What is going on?

My body is actually out of control!

Soul, there is an issue with my soul!

Suddenly, the eerie light in her pupils grew and spread rapidly. The white part of her eyes were completely covered and turned pitch-black.

Fairy Zi Wei struggled and resisted with all her strength, but it was all in vain. In her last moment of clarity, she suddenly realized: She was controlled by Spectral Soul, every time she soul searched Spectral Soul, her soul had actually been tampered with slowly. Spectral Soul's methods were too advanced, she had not been able to detect it at all. She had already been corroded and infiltrated by Spectral Soul's power, the various decisions she made before Central Continent's Refinement Path Convention also had Spectral Soul's influence in them.

It was just that Spectral Soul's interference was small at the start. But later on, this secret influence kept on growing. And now, he could even cause Fairy Zi Wei to be under an illusion.

Just earlier, Fairy Zi Wei had not used benevolent equality but she thought she had already successfully activated it and even informed Duke Long!

"Maybe in the previous life too, I was taken over like this by Spectral Soul. Although I have benevolent equality, I did not truly use it." This was the last clear thought of Fairy Zi Wei.

At the next moment, she slowly raised her head and looked at the battlefield quietly with a black light in her eyes. Her lips curled up to form an extremely sinister smile.

She maintained the opening of Central Heaven Gate while approaching Soul Suppression Hall quietly.

She had the clearest picture of the locations here.

She quickly cleared all kinds of shackles and restored Spectral Soul's freedom.

"Zi Wei pays respects to master!" She knelt down and prostrated before Spectral Soul with not even a trace of pride of a Heavenly Court member.

Spectral Soul was extremely weak, he turned into a translucent soul sphere which slowly floated towards Fairy Zi Wei: "Let's go watch the show first."

Fairy Zi Wei held the soul sphere in both hands and walked out of Soul Suppression Hall.

At this moment, Wu Yong, Wu Shuai, and others also appeared in Heavenly Court's battlefield.

"What's going on? Fairy Zi Wei!" Duke Long roared, Central Heaven Gate was still being activated and actually brought these enemies as well.

Duke Long was unable to contact Fairy Zi Wei, his heart sank and he wanted to directly destroy Central Heaven Gate. But at this moment, Fang Yuan charged towards Heaven Overseeing Tower again.

Duke Long was seething with anger, but he was forced to intercept Fang Yuan and give up on his previous plan.

Gu Immortals entered one by one through Central Heaven Gate.

"Follow Lord Wu Yong!"

"So Heavenly Court actually looks like this."

"Kill! Kill! Kill!"

"Heaven Overseeing Tower is there, follow me!"

The final decisive battle unfolded in Heavenly Court.

Chapter 1947: Paradise Earth Takes Action

"Come, come, take a look, this is high grade silk!"

"Candied fruits, candied fruits, buy three sticks and get one free."

"Sir, what do you need?" Inside a store that sold Gu worms, a clerk welcomed Hong Yi passionately.

Hong Yi first fixed his gaze on this clerk before carefully scanning the layout and decoration of the store. He frowned on the inside: "Everything here is so lifelike, what is going on?"

"I heard you have scholar Gu for sale?" Hong Yi asked.

"Oh, yes. But lord, this scholar Gu is a rank five Gu worm." The clerk was somewhat hesitant.

Hong Yi smiled lightly and released his rank five Gu Master aura, immediately causing a huge disturbance in the store.

The clerk's face was filled with shock, the store manager was also drawn in by the aura. He cupped his hands and greeted Hong Yi respectfully, personally taking out a scholar Gu for him to observe.

"It is indeed scholar Gu." Hong Yi examined it carefully for a while, the doubts in his heart growing deeper, "May I test it?"

"Go ahead, sir." The store manager immediately gave scholar Gu to Hong Yi.

Hong Yi poured his primeval essence into scholar Gu. This scholar Gu immediately flew out from Hong Yi's finger and landed on the ground, turning into a young handsome scholar.

The young scholar bowed respectfully towards Hong Yi with cupped fists: "Student greets teacher."

Hong Yi nodded in excitement. Scholar Gu was extremely rare, it was a human path Gu worm, and Hong Yi had only heard of it in rumors.

Hong Yi took out a wisdom path mortal Gu and an information path mortal Gu from his aperture, throwing them to the scholar: "Use them."

The scholar received these two Gu worms and used them without any need for gaining familiarity, and he used them rather proficiently at that. In particular, some small habits during the activation were the same as Hong Yi's.

"What do you think, sir?" The store manager asked with a smile.

Hong Yi nodded repeatedly: "Great, I want this Gu."

The store manager was exulted: "Great, it will be six hundred thousand primeval stones."

Hong Yi's brows furrowed.

This price was not expensive, in fact, it was too cheap. The price for a rank five mortal Gu ranged from one hundred thousand to one million primeval stones, but this scholar Gu was a rare top quality rank five Gu, its price was definitely above one million. Moreover, there was no market for it, so it was difficult to get even with sufficient funds.

But it was being sold for only six hundred thousand primeval stones here!

Hong Yi had many fortuitous encounters and was wealthy, he immediately paid the sum and received this scholar Gu.

Coming outside the store, Hong Yi's heart was fluctuating with waves: "This place is like Emperor City, but weren't there immortal battles going on around Emperor City? But this place is peaceful. What is going on?"

"Also, there doesn't seem to be any difference between here and reality, but looking carefully, there are a large number of human path Gu worms here. Scholar Gu is only one of them. Moreover, there are so many human path Gu worms here that it can even be called overflowing, but it is commonplace to these people. And the common fire path, water path, and other paths' Gu worms are instead rare here. It seems like human path is the main cultivation path here."

"Really strange! I wonder what Brother Ye found on his end? I better go join him quickly."

After Ye Fan and Hong Yi were sent to the painting by Genesis Lotus's will, they split up to explore the area after discussing with each other.

Hong Yi's discovery was also discovered by Ye Fan.

But at this moment, in the corner of a street, Ye Fan saw an unexpected person.

"Master!" Ye Fan was astonished.

He had also bought a rank five human path Gu worm from a store, it was called hero Gu. He had just come to a corner to activate it, and the situation became different from when he activated it in the store.

Hero Gu actually transformed into his master's appearance!

"No need to be shocked, my disciple. This is our chance encounter." Lu Wei Yin smiled.

Ye Fan immediately understood the meaning behind the words and was joyous: "Master, you know the oddity of this place? What place is this? Why did we suddenly end up in this place?"

Lu Wei Yin smiled lightly: "I need to explain from the beginning. Three hundred thousand years ago, in the Medieval Antiquity Era, Central Continent gave birth to an Immortal Venerable named Genesis Lotus. He created the killer move karma divine tree, and when he roamed Western Desert, he refused a child's request to resurrect his parents, as a result, he saw a certain scene in the future where Emperor City was destroyed by an earth trench and all lives were extinguished."

"Therefore, he placed Divine Bean Palace in Western Desert. When he returned to Central Continent later, he used the painting path killer move contented lifestyle on Emperor City, forming a painting world. You two have your luck connected to Fang Yuan tightly, Genesis Lotus's will was wary and thus it locked you in here."

Ye Fan was dumbstruck, the wealth of information made him unable to react for a while.

He was extremely shaken: "This matter is actually related to Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable? Also master, when did I connect luck with Fang Yuan?"

"That was done by Fang Yuan secretly, he wanted to accomplish something with the help of your luck. The upper extreme heavenly eagle was also his immemorial desolate beast." Lu Wei Yin replied calmly.

"Fang Yuan took the initiative to connect luck with me to get help from my luck?" Ye Fan was even more shocked.

Ye Fan had acknowledged Lu Wei Yin as his master and was thus half a step into the Gu Immortal world, and knew much more secrets than Hong Yi. He was extremely clear on what kind of big shot Fang Yuan was! Fang Yuan was an unparalleled demon, a powerful character that even Heavenly Court was without options against. He was actually connected to him, this was simply like a fairytale!

Lu Wei Yin shook his head: "Disciple, don't look down on yourself. You are a person favored by the Heavenly Dao, you possess an innately strong luck. Although you are insignificant at the start, you will definitely make huge accomplishments in the future. In the entire five regions, there are not even ten people with luck like yours. It is not strange for Fang Yuan to want to get help from your luck."

"However, the Heavenly Dao balances everything, he once used your luck and obtained great benefits, now, you are also using him to obtain an enormous immortal fortune. The upper extreme heavenly eagle was only one of them, in front of you now is Genesis Lotus' true inheritance!"

"Genesis Lotus' true inheritance?!" Ye Fan exclaimed in shock once again, he suddenly understood and his gaze towards Lu Wei Yin changed: "Master, you know all this like the back of your hand. Does this mean this was all your plan?"

"Haha, my disciple, you overestimate me. This was all Lord Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangement, I am only his inheritor."

When Ye Fan heard the great name of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, he realized he had also become a follower of Paradise Earth, but he did not feel exulted as he was already numb from the shock.

Lu Wei Yin waved at Ye Fan: "We don't have much time, we will talk as we move."

Ye Fan quickly followed, the two followed the crowd in the street and walked towards the front.

Lu Wei Yin explained in detail: "This Genesis Lotus true inheritance has extremely high value, it is divided into three parts. The first part is this contented lifestyle killer move, the second part is the luck of being the child of humanity, and the third part is the rank eight Immortal Gu House formed from Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City — Divine Emperor Palace!"

Lu Wei Yin continued after a slight pause: "We will first take the second part and make you the child of humanity."

Ye Fan questioned: "Master, what is the child of humanity? What should I do?"

Lu Wei Yin replied: "Central Continent is different from the other four regions, it uses the sect system and human path is most prosperous here with the deepest foundation. Emperor City is the greatest congregation of Central Continent's human vein. Why do countless geniuses emerge here? It is because of the human vein. As long as you absorb the strength within the human vein, your luck will get a huge boost and you will gain the favor of human path, becoming the child of humanity. And to achieve this, we need Hong Yi's help."

"Hong Yi? He is my sworn brother, how is this connected to him?" Ye Fan continued to be shocked.

Lu Wei Yin replied: "Fang Yuan connected luck with him as well, but his luck is different from yours, you are the favored child of the Heavenly Dao while he is one of the children of humanity of Central Continent, he is favored by human path. With his help, you can smoothly make use of Shen Shang's actions and quietly obtain the recognition of the human vein. With the status of a child of humanity, we can then borrow Fang Yuan's strength to attempt to get the first part of the true inheritance, or even the third part as well."

Divine Bean Palace, painting world.

"Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan..." A voice was heard intermittently in Fang Di Chang's ears.

Fang Di Chang had already stopped using karma divine tree and was using wisdom path killer moves to think of how to get rid of this predicament when he heard this voice.

"It is Shen Shang's voice! He learned of my identity from the main body?" Fang Di Chang hesitated, he had some guesses in his mind but he did not respond immediately.

Sure enough, Shen Shang's voice continued to transmit: "Fang Di Chang, I already learned of your true identity from your main body. Who could have thought Fang Yuan had such an arrangement, he actually placed his clone inside a Western Desert super force. I am going to help you escape."

"Hmm? How are you going to help me?" Fang Di Chang was puzzled.

Shen Shang laughed: "You should know that I have been trying to decipher the venerable human path methods and I have already found the key to them."

"I know." Fang Di Chang nodded.

Shen Shang continued: "Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City have merged into one, I have all along been hiding myself and haven't let Genesis Lotus' will discover me, so I am still deciphering human path killer moves."

Fang Di Chang asked: "And what about them?"

Shen Shang explained patiently: "This is a perfect opportunity! I have been constantly transferring the four regions' human will inside here. Originally, I had been unable to involve myself with Emperor City and disrupt the venerable methods from inside so I had to infiltrate it quietly. But now, Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City have merged. You previously refined Divine Bean Palace, it is just that your authority is lower than Genesis Lotus' will. Use your karma divine tree killer move to shake the whole Immortal Gu House and coordinate with me to spread out the venerable methods so that everyone's power is amplified."

"You want me to cooperate with you to break the venerable human path methods?" Fang Di Chang got to the point.

Shen Shang laughed: "We are helping each other!"

"Alright, I'll work with you." Fang Di Chang did not hesitate, agreeing directly.

Chapter 1948: Restoration Halted

Heavenly Court's battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Finger Wind Dragon!

Wu Yong activated his killer move but was met with the joint attack of three Heavenly Court members.

"Die, Wu Yong!" Prince Feng Xian used inexhaustible flames that charged ahead while he stood behind, covered in flames. His offensive attack also had defensive properties, it was a stable choice of attack.

Zhou Xiong Xin attacked from behind, the killer move rumors become tigers roared, like a group of tigers that pounced towards Wu Yong.

And Ye Qiao Zi activated long range killer moves, vines grew out of thin air and spread towards Wu Yong, trying to bind him.

Wu Yong sighed internally, he had to retreat repeatedly. He moved back into Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

With the help of the Immortal Gu House, he resisted the fierce attacks of the three immortals.

But as such, his plan to approach Heaven Overseeing Tower was stopped.

"The amplification of the human path killer moves to Heavenly Court is too big....wait a moment, this is?!" Just as Wu Yong was getting a headache, specks of white lights appeared on Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and even entered his body.

Human path killer move — Hope of the People!

Human path killer move — Heroes Among People!

"Ahhhh." Inside the Immortal Gu House, other Southern Border Gu Immortals beside Wu Yong were roaring with vitality.

"This strength, this strength...." Old Treeman Ba De, who was fighting outside, looked at his own hands with shock.

Transformation path great expert Yi Hao Fang was similarly puzzled: "Why are Heavenly Court's human path killer moves helping us?"

This heavy doubt was pressing down on the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals' minds like a mountain.

"Shen Shang, you really didn't let down my expectations, great job." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, he had also received the amplification and his condition was improving rapidly.

Duke Long's face was ashen!

He was a dragonman, a variant human, he could not receive the amplification of heroes among people unlike Fang Yuan. When Fang Yuan returned to his human form, even if it was created with sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it was still a pure human!

Boom!

Duke Long was sent flying by Fang Yuan.

"What in the world is going on?" Qin Ding Ling transmitted her voice to Old Man Zheng Yuan, asking him anxiously.

Old Man Zheng Yuan was not dead yet and had already moved out of Central Great Hall. He was all along responsible for activating the human path methods left behind by Central Continent's venerables.

The old man transmitted his panicked reply to Duke Long, Qin Ding Ling and the rest: "There is a problem in Emperor City. Someone is causing trouble, he poured in the human will of other four regions into Central Continent. Hope of the people and heroes among people distinguish allies based on human will. There was only Central Continent's human will previously, but now the human wills of all five regions are gathered, so everyone will receive amplification."

Duke Long warded off Fang Yuan's attacks while asking: "How can we resolve this issue?"

Old Man Zheng Yuan replied with a heavy voice: "I am giving it my all but I don't have any confidence in succeeding!"

Duke Long's heart sank further: "Who could have tampered with our venerable human path methods to this degree?"

He had never imagined the venerable human path killer moves to have such changes. The enemy did not break these two killer moves directly but instead expanded the effectiveness of the killer moves to everyone, this was no different from breaking them.

"Is it Shen Shang?" The soul sphere in Fairy Zi Wei's hands shook lightly as if it was laughing to itself.

Back then, the information Fairy Zi Wei had given to Duke Long contained details of Shen Shang's location. This action was made under Spectral Soul's influence.

Duke Long, however, had full trust in Fairy Zi Wei. Moreover, at that time, Fang Zheng had been detained by Shen Cong Sheng and had to be exchanged for urgently, thus there was the series of later events. In the end, Shen Shang left Dragon Whale Paradise, infiltrated Emperor City and achieved this accomplishment.

"Perhaps I should say, this is worthy of Paradise Earth." The soul sphere shook once again.

Fairy Zi Wei was holding the soul sphere and continuously using wisdom path methods to imitate soul path and heal the soul sphere.

The soul sphere was becoming increasingly solid under her healing.

On the other side, Central Heaven Gate was still open, bringing in Gu Immortals from the outside world into Heavenly Court.

"Hahaha, bring all those people in, let them kill, let them die! The more they kill the better it is, the more deaths there are the better this is, hahaha." The soul sphere laughed madly.

The first batch who came were the Southern Border immortals in Hairy Foot Mountain, as well as Wu Shuai, Zhan Bu Du, and others.

Right now, the second batch of Gu Immortals was teleported over. They were Northern Plains' reinforcements who allied with Southern Border's group in the previous life.

The leader was an old man with a walking stick, Yao Huang.

As well as Heavenly Lord Bai Zu who was walking forward proudly.

Behind the two great rank eight Gu Immortals were Domination Immortal Chu Du who was famous throughout the five regions, Black Extremity Sun Ming Lu who schemed against Old Ancestor Xue Hu, as well as other Gu Immortal experts.

"Rank seven Gu Immortals will enter Immortal Gu Houses." Yao Huang swept his gaze around the battlefield and gave the command.

Even Chu Du had to listen obediently.

He was shaken by the fierce battle in front, this battle was not something rank sevens could interfere in.

Northern Plains had few Immortal Gu Houses, but they brought over three this time!

"Follow me, we will reinforce Calamity Luck Altar." Heavenly Lord Bai Zu took the lead to charge forward.

Yao Huang and the three Immortal Gu Houses followed closely behind.

Bing Sai Chuan cheered loudly inside Calamity Luck Altar, his attacks towards the refinement path formation were obstructed by the golden pearls left by Golden Pearl Immortal King. And now, he was being besieged from all directions by Heavenly Court's main force.

Bing Sai Chuan was attacking the refinement path formation while repairing Calamity Luck Altar, he needed help and this batch of reinforcements came at a perfect timing.

"Kill!" Heavenly Lord Bai Zu shouted. His figure shook and split into countless clones that fought against the soldiers formed from the golden pearls.

Yao Huang did not want to appear weak, he waved his cane, a strong medicinal fragrance pervaded the battlefield immediately.

The three Immortal Gu Houses also arrived and defended Calamity Luck Altar.

Heavenly Court's main force was immediately divided.

"Don't even dream of leaving." Wu Yong used killer moves one after another, wishful wind whip, soft vajra wind chief, yin wind rope and many others were used alternatively to tie down the enemies.

Ba De, Yi Hao Fang and others also mimicked this.

"Damn it!" Most of Heavenly Court's main force could only curse inwardly as they were pinned down.

If it were before, the Southern Border immortals would never have been able to pose such troubles, but with heroes among people's support now, Wu Yong and others were amplified. Overall, they were still weaker than Heavenly Court's members, after all, the latter were elites in rank eight, but it was still enough for them to become a threat.

"Charge!" Dragon Palace crashed through the battlefield, Wu Shuai and Zhan Bu Du were controlling it from inside.

Feng Jiu Ge had to avoid the collision, destiny song slowed down.

Fang Yuan immediately felt the suppression on him receding sharply, and adding on the amplification from heroes among people, he sent Duke Long flying once again.

Dragon tattoos wriggled around Duke Long, dragon fangs flew around and obstructed the incoming attacks.

Suddenly, a huge figure appeared.

"This is?!" Duke Long's pupils shrank rapidly as he saw the giant figure.

Evil Dragon — Di Zang Sheng had taken the stage!

"Duke Long!!!" Di Zang Sheng spoke human voice, its roar gave rise to endless shock waves. It slammed down its claws on Duke Long like he was a ball.

Di Zang Sheng's claws were cut by the dragon fangs and dripped with blood, while Duke Long collided into the ground, creating a hundred feet deep crater.

Di Zang Sheng's enormous body pressed down.

Rumble!

The entirety of Heavenly Court shook violently, smoke and dust flew, covering the whole battlefield.

Di Zang Sheng flew up slowly, the ground that its stomach pressed on had already formed a shallow trench that spanned from the east to west of Heavenly Court. All the buildings, mountains and rivers in its path were turned into waste.

"He is above!" Zhan Bu Du suddenly pointed.

Duke Long was floating in the air, looking down at Di Zang Sheng. The dragon gate behind him disappeared slowly.

At the crucial moment, he had escaped the dangerous situation by using dragon gate.

"This Evil Dragon!" Duke Long clenched his teeth, his sunken chest bulged up rapidly and soon recovered to its previous state. Clearly, Di Zang Sheng's attack had not been without effect.

On the other side, Myriad Year Flying Warship flew back and took in Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan looked at Duke Long and sneered, he directly ignored him and charged towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Duke Long's eyelids twitched at this sight.

The force at Heaven Overseeing Tower's side was barely resisting Calamity Luck Altar and was on the verge of collapse. If Fang Yuan and Myriad Year Flying Warship joined, the situation would directly collapse.

"Fang Yuan, don't even think about it! Everyone gather and protect Heaven Overseeing Tower!" Duke Long sent his command, he himself was the first to move as he used dragon gate and blocked the path of Myriad Year Flying Warship.

"Get lost!" Dragon Palace came to reinforce, its owner Wu Shuai was resolute and direct, he released the suppressed Jun Shen Guang and Vortex Space Boy, and thus could activate the killer move dreamy light smoke again.

Dreamy light smoke engulfed Duke Long.

Duke Long's heart pounded crazily, he had no choice but to dodge, leaving behind a path through which Fang Yuan moved forward.

"Damn it, this is a dream path killer move, my methods are useless." In a corner far away, Feng Jin Huang was hiding in an inconspicuous Immortal Gu House, stomping her feet in anxiety.

Right at this time, destiny song reverberated through the battlefield once again.

Heavenly Court's condition rose rapidly and Duke Long also received great benefits, while Fang Yuan and the group's offenses immediately weakened.

"Unbelievable, we entered Heavenly Court!" Eight Eastern Sea immortals joined the battlefield through Central Heaven Gate.

"Heavenly Court's side is being besieged!" The eight immortals' eyes brightened, especially when they saw Fang Yuan, Di Zang Sheng, Myriad Year Flying Warship, and Dragon Palace forcing back Duke Long and Feng Jiu Ge.

"Good, we will join and deal the final blow to them!!" The eight immortals' morale soared as they joined the chaotic battle.

"How did they come here?" Fang Yuan was slightly surprised.

Zhang Yin, Granny Rong and the other dragon generals joining the battle was a given, but Qing Yue An and the rest were very conservative, why would they take risk in joining the battle?

"Hehehe, this is the side effect of heroes among people. When they received the amplification, they also received the influence of the four regions' human will and hate Heavenly Court even more now." Shen Shang's voice transmitted over: "A pity that Western Desert's side is still in a stalemate against Central Continent's Immortal Gu Houses and cannot participate in this battle."

"Shen Shang, well done." Fang Yuan did not hesitate to praise.

Shen Shang laughed heartily: "Naturally. But then again, you being able to control Central Heaven Gate was truly beyond my expectation. This move was truly spectacular. Ah, I can also feel Central Heaven Gate's transportation power, we will join in a while and flip Heavenly Court upside-down, hahaha!"

Fang Yuan only smiled: "Then come fast!"

Central Heaven Gate's change was beyond Fang Yuan's expectations, but why would he cut himself short at this time? Even if someone was scheming from the dark, Fang Yuan would only follow the tides and prioritize in defeating Heavenly Court as well as destroying fate Gu.

"Damn it, why at this time..." Just as Shen Shang was about to accept the transportation, black fire appeared on his body. His internal threat had erupted again.

"I used all my strength to decipher the venerable killer moves and my injuries were left unattended..." This was Shen Shang's last clear thought before he sank into madness and chaos.

The moment Shen Shang turned mad, Old Man Zheng Yuan sensed it.

The old man's spirit was roused: "The enemy's strength has disappeared! Regardless of the reason, I can use this chance to take control again and there is even a chance to turn around the situation. Hmm? Who is it?!"

Old Man Zheng Yuan suddenly shouted, Fairy Zi Wei appeared in front of him with empty hands and a smile on her face.

"Zi Wei? No, you are not normal!" The old man's eyes shone sharply as he quickly retreated.

But at the next moment, a solid pitch-black soul sphere appeared behind him and entered his body.

"No!" Old Man Zheng Yuan seemed to have suffered a heavy attack as he collapsed on the ground, his eyes rolled and saliva foamed from his mouth while his body quivered continuously.

The twitching lasted for a while before Old Man Zheng Yuan became still all of a sudden, his eyes were the same as Fairy Zi Wei, turning completely black.

He stood up silently and wiped off the saliva, he lowered his hands and greeted the floating soul sphere respectfully: "This old servant pays respects to master!"

Spectral Soul let out a light grunt of agreement, he did not have any Immortal Gu currently but he was not without methods. The soul beast modification killer move he developed in the past had already become a type of innate ability of his soul. This innate ability could let him modify any soul and make the target offer their complete loyalty.

"Now, we should subdue Feng Jin Huang, I know her location as well and can also cut off that Immortal Gu House's teleportation ability." Fairy Zi Wei said of her own initiative.

"No hurry." Spectral Soul, however, rejected her suggestion: "Feng Jin Huang is not only favored by the Heavenly Dao, she also receives the adoration of humanity itself, her luck is strong enough to be second only to Red Lotus Demon Venerable. Don't think she is alone right now, the moment we make an attempt on her, we will be met with obstructions. Forget others, just Feng Jiu Ge alone is a huge problem. This person is strong enough to match Duke Long right now! We will observe the changes in the battlefield, let these people kill each other as their luck dissipates, then we will see if there is a chance to make a move on Feng Jin Huang."

Spectral Soul and the two servants walked out of the Immortal Gu House and observed the battlefield from far away.

Right now, Heavenly Court's side was gathered around Heaven Overseeing Tower and defended with all their strength. Their situation had become extremely perilous.

The other immortals' attacks were unusually fierce, they were under the amplification from heroes among people, but also the weakening from destiny song. With Fang Yuan and Di Zang Sheng at the lead, every minute action made Heavenly Court's side nervous.

Duke Long and Feng Jiu Ge were like main pillars, one person blocked Fang Yuan while the other suppressed Di Zang Sheng, but both were disadvantaged since they had to defend Heaven Overseeing Tower as well.

Demon Judgment Board was struggling to defend against Myriad Year Flying Warship and Dragon Palace's joint attacks.

Golden pearl soldiers were completely destroyed, Heavenly Court's main force was on a constant retreat and the defensive line continued to pull back.

"Heavenly Court's defeat is imminent." Fairy Zi Wei commented, the eerie light in her eyes flickered.

Only Yuan Qiong Du was standing on the top floor of Heaven Overseeing Tower. Cong Yan and Che Wei were lying on the floor, on the verge of death, there was no one to heal them and Heavenly Court also did not have the ability to spare manpower.

Originally, Qi Ci Lang was resisting the jade green light, but when Heavenly Court's main force arrived, they easily handled him. Qi Ci Lang was still bound and could not resist at all, he was directly beheaded and died with grievance.

The refinement path Gu formation was already destroyed, Yuan Qiong Du could only continue restoring fate Gu by himself.

"Almost there, almost there!" Yuan Qiong Du mumbled, a fire was burning in his palm.

Boom!

Heaven Overseeing Tower suffered a heavy attack and shook violently. Yuan Qiong Du's refinement was disturbed, he coughed out a large mouthful of blood and fell to the ground, unconscious.

Fate Gu's restoration was forcefully halted!

Chapter 1949: Beheaded By One Slice!

Immortal killer move — Five Rotational Destruction!

Five Elements Grandmaster shouted in fury, he faced the sky with his palms and pushed, a five colored ring appeared.

The ring flew to the sky and let out a powerful attraction force, absorbing all kinds of killer moves and even desolate beasts.

Heavenly Court's defensive line fell into chaos.

"Charge!" Southern Border's Gu Immortals grasped this chance and activated rank eight Immortal Gu House Great Space Temple to charge in through the gap.

Heavenly Court's Yu Zhu Zi gritted his teeth as he pointed at Great Space Temple and shouted: "Go!"

Most of the jade pearls floating around him flew out and struck Great Space Temple before detonating.

Bam bam bam...

The detonation of jade pearls resounded like thunder, jade fragments scattered everywhere and attached themselves onto Great Space Temple, actually slowing this rank eight Immortal Gu House by several times.

With this chance, Heavenly Court's members quickly reinforced and used all their strength to force Great Space Temple out.

But, although Great Space Temple was forced out, Wu Yong made his move on the other side.

Immortal killer move — Finger Wind Dragon!

Immortal killer move — Chaotic Shooting Blades!

Wu Yong flicked his fingers repeatedly, throwing out several dark jade worms.

The small worms grew larger as they flew in the sky, expanding to ten feet, fifty feet, a hundred and fifty feet!

In just a few breaths of time, they turned into vicious wind dragons that was two hundred and twenty feet long, baring their fangs as they attacked Heavenly Court's defensive line.

Wu Yong's eyes flashed with a green light, the wind dragons roared and turned into countless jade wind blades, shooting everywhere.

The wind blades were sharp, cutting everything in their path, Heavenly Court's main force could only grit their teeth and face the killer moves forcibly.

Using this chance when they were too occupied, Wu Yong turned around and infiltrated the defense line.

"Don't even think about it!" A delicate voice sounded, flower petals flew in the sky; Wan Zi Hong blocked Wu Yong.

She had been paying heavy attention towards Wu Yong without daring to be careless. The moment Wu Yong made the move, she went to fill the gap.

Wu Yong sighed and could only drop the plan.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals inside Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building were shouting towards the Eastern Sea Gu Immortal Hua Cai Yun: "Go in quickly!"

Previously, Wan Zi Hong had been fighting with Hua Cai Yun and Qing Yue An. Right now, Wan Zi Hong went to fill the defensive gap which left behind a hole, letting Hua Cai Yun and Qing Yue An infiltrate the defensive line.

Hua Cai Yun and Qing Yue An glanced at each other and sensed the other had no intention to charge in, so they both chose to battle in the same place without having any intention to invade.

The human wills influenced the Eastern Sea immortals' resoluteness, but the influence was limited. Right now, Hua Cai Yun and Qing Yue An were already feeling regret, how could they have joined the decisive battle in Heavenly Court because of a moment of hotheadedness?

Wasn't it quite good and satisfying to plunder immortal materials in Central Continent?

Why did they have to fight to the death here!

They were not fools, the first ones to invade the defensive line would definitely be met with fierce counterattacks from Heavenly Court's forces, they might even die if they were just a little bit careless.

Because she had seen through this, Wan Zi Hong boldly went to fill the defensive gap and block Wu Yong.

"The nature of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals is like this." Wan Zi Hong's eyes shone sharply, she had a deep understanding regarding Eastern Sea.

But at the next moment, Shi Miao suddenly charged into Heavenly Court's defensive line.

He was also an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, Heavenly Court's main force were barely able to maintain the defensive line and when they were forced, they would let the defensive gap appear in front of the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals. But Heavenly Court's main force would have never imagined that Shi Miao was already controlled by Dragon Palace and had become a dragon general, unafraid of death in battles.

Heavenly Court's main force was dazed and allowed Shi Miao to smoothly charge into the defensive line and near Heaven Overseeing Tower. Just as he was about to charge inside, a figure suddenly appeared in front of Shi Miao.

"In your dream!" Duke Long's voice resounded in Shi Miao's ears.

Shi Miao had already put up his defenses, his skin was like a layer of rocks, extremely firm. But his tough skin was immediately pierced by Duke Long's right hand and his neck was grabbed firmly.

Shi Miao immediately felt suffocation, an intense force spread from Duke Long's right hand and cracked the rock skin on his neck.

"What kind of strength is this!" Shi Miao was horrified, he struggled with all his might but it was fruitless.

Just as his neck was about to snap, a sword light arrived.

Duke Long dodged immediately, but this was predicted, the sword light struck his waist, then passed through behind like a ray of light.

Duke Long's body was almost cut apart by this sword light, an enormous wound appeared on his stomach from where blood flowed out without stopping.

The sword light continued with its momentum and struck Heaven Overseeing Tower. Fortunately, defensive measures were already activated around Heaven Overseeing Tower, it was not unprepared like when Bo Qing's sword light cut it, a white barrier flickered around the tower before finally stopping the sword light.

"Fang Yuan!" Duke Long turned his head towards where the attack came from, at that direction was Fang Yuan who had once again transformed into an immemorial sword dragon.

The sword dragon's claws were clenched into a fist, the attack just now was five finger fist heart sword!

This killer move had terrifying might, Duke Long absolutely could not sit idly and watch Fang Yuan use it casually. He immediately gave up on Shi Miao and used dragon gate to approach Fang Yuan.

But at this time, Shi Miao suddenly revealed a strange smile, his whole body melted and rapidly covered Duke Long's body.

This change caught Duke Long off guard, and Fang Yuan was able to activate five finger fist heart sword again!

Second sword, third sword, fourth sword!

Every sword light struck Duke Long and passed through his body, the remaining force struck Heaven Overseeing Tower till it shook.

"Lord Duke Long!!!" This unexpected situation caused Heavenly Court's immortals to pale in fright.

Even Duke Long had never expected Shi Miao to willingly give up his life to pin him down! Fang Yuan's five finger fist heart sword struck him but Shi Miao was also struck.

There were three terrifyingly large sword wounds on Duke Long's body, he was dripping with blood but he still had a breath of life left in him.

Shi Miao, however, could not be anymore dead. His form was a severed corpse, he died with a smile on his face.

"Duke Long, your life shall end here." Fang Yuan said softly before pointing the fifth sword of five finger fist heart sword!

The sword light seemed to pierce through time and space, no one could block its speed.

Heavenly Court's immortals watched the sword light strike Duke Long with a horrified gaze.

At the moment of death, Duke Long's eyes lost their light as he fell into a whirlpool of memories.

Childhood...

Duke Long was lying on the bed and crying: "Father, mother, don't die, don't leave me behind!"

"Child." Duke Long's father rubbed his head and showed a carefree smile even when death was impending: "Don't cry and don't grieve. We suffered these fatal wounds to stop Di Zang Sheng's rampage, this is our responsibility as members of Heavenly Court, and it is also something we are willing to do."

"Death is the final destination of life,the crucial thing is whether we died a worthy death."

"You will understand this when you grow up, my child." Duke Long's mother spoke: "You will understand what our sacrifices signify. Although this leads to separation, it is also our honor and duty to protect humanity. The stronger one is, the greater their responsibilities. Protecting our people is the noble task that has been inherited by us and countless seniors. When you grow up, you will also continue to walk our path. We will be looking forward to your growth in the other world. You need to work hard and persevere."

Adolescence...

Young Duke Long was breathing heavily, he was knocked down by a puppet and was lying down on the ground.

A Gu Master laughed loudly from the side and clapped: "Little Long, your performance is already great. Get up, rest for a while."

"No, I can still continue to fight!" Young Duke Long used all his strength and stood up unsteadily: "I will double my efforts, work hard in cultivation and keep on growing stronger. This puppet in front of me is nothing. There will be a day when I will become an expert like my parents, I will become a Gu Immortal of Heavenly Court and follow their path!"

"Hahaha, such aspirations, I am really looking forward to your future." The Gu Master praised sincerely.

Adulthood...

"This is how it feels to be a Gu Immortal?" Duke Long passed the ascension tribulation and became a rank six Gu Immortal.

"Amazing, kid. You have become an immortal at such a young age. Thinking back to when I was your age, I was still competing with my rival in love, hahaha." A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal laughed.

"Thank you for guarding me during this period." The adult Duke Long bowed towards the Gu Immortal and said with great sincerity.

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortal waved his hand: "You should have realized it by now, your identity is special. You are the Dao Guardian of the future Immortal Venerable, so your cultivation path will always be smooth, even if there are setbacks, it will only signify that you are going to reap even greater harvests later."

"Heavenly Court needs you, the future Immortal Venerable needs you, humanity needs you. Kid, becoming an immortal is not your end point, it is just your starting point. You can't get complacent, you can't stop moving forward. We all need you."

"Yes, I will persevere till I die. I will contribute every bit of my strength and every drop of my blood and sweat for Heavenly Court, for humanity, and for the future!" Duke Long swore.

Middle age...

"Rank eight cultivation, unimaginable... you actually accomplished this at your age!" Duke Tong said with a moved voice.

"Perhaps we should say, worthy of a Dao Guardian? Hahaha, with you, Heavenly Court can be even more prosperous." Duke Mei laughed brightly.

"I am flattered, seniors." The middle-aged Duke Long spoke modestly.

Duke Mei and Duke Tong glanced at each other, the former said: "So, have you considered our suggestion? Become one of us, lead Heavenly Court and guide the future Immortal Venerable seed."

Duke Long nodded with no hesitation: "Yes, I have already prepared myself!"

"Hahaha, then from today onwards, you are Duke Long."

"One of the three dukes of Heavenly Court, and also the most important one. Heavenly Court's heavy responsibility will mainly rest on your shoulders."

Duke Long nodded his head slowly and said with a solemn expression: "This is the path I have been pursuing. This is the expectation that my parents and the countless seniors I have met in life hold, it is the result that Heavenly Court and humanity needs! This responsibility... I, Duke Long, will undertake it with no hesitation!"

Old age...

"Come back, Hong Ting, you can still turn around!" Duke Long called.

"Master, I failed to live up to your teachings and expectations, I am sorry, but I must revive them!" Red Lotus did not turn around, disappearing into the night.

Duke Long closed his eyes in pain, his body on the verge of collapsing. The disciple he had taught with all his heart for so many years chose to walk on such a path.

"I guided an Immortal Venerable to become a Demon Venerable, I have sinned!" Duke Long knelt before Duke Tong and Duke Mei.

"Get up, get up quickly." Duke Tong and Duke Mei held Duke Long's arms and consoled him.

"You need to have faith, Duke Long, we still have hope."

"It is not your fault, Duke Long, we have all seen the efforts you have put in. It is Hong Ting who has disappointed us, not you."

"No." Duke Long shook off the two's hands and said with an extremely solemn expression: "He is my disciple, if he is walking on the wrong path now, it is my mistake! It is my sin! I must pay for this, I will stake all my strength to make up for this mistake!! For Heavenly Court and for humanity, even if I have to give up everything, I will pull Red Lotus back to the righteous path!!!"

And finally, in his twilight years...

Duke Long was sitting cross-legged in the hall, his head lowered and his hair was disheveled.

Two trails of tears quietly trickled down his face.

In front of him on the cold floor were the corpses of people he was familiar with, these were dragonman corpses.

The pain in his heart submerged everything and roared like a tsunami, threatening to drown Duke Long.

He was originally blessed with the joys of familial bonds, but who could have thought he would have to suffer such an impact in his twilight years. What was even more sad was that the killer of his children and grandchildren was he himself!

This was the tragedy that he singlehandedly created.

"It is my fault, back then I should not have..." Duke Long's voice was choked with emotions. He slowly raised his head, his gaze seemed to be under extreme weight as he slowly looked at each corpse. Joyful conversations and laughter along with blissful scenes of him with his grandchildren surfaced in his mind.

"It is not your fault, my children! Everything is my fault!" Duke Long's back bent down, he used his powerless fist to pound his chest, light thumping sounds echoed in the hall.

"I was negligent in my care towards you, I did not guide you well, you ended up walking on the wrong path. I was wrong, I am not a good master, I am also not a good ancestor. But for the prosperity of humanity, for Heavenly Court, I had to sacrifice you."

"Believe me, I never wanted this outcome. But I have no choice, I might be a dragonman but my heart has always stood with humanity. I cannot let you disrupt the rule of humanity, that is the result gained after countless generations sacrificed themselves. And most importantly, your roots also lie in humanity!"

"If you want to blame someone, then blame me, I cannot beg for your forgiveness neither do I dare to do that. Let me bear all the sins, let me pay for them!"

"My children... I cannot bring myself to separate with you. You will merge with me, we will never be apart! As your ancestor, I have failed you and did not give you a beautiful life and stable environment to live in. But this is all I can do."

"I, Duke Long, am just a dying old man."

Present...

The fifth sword flew towards Duke Long so fast that it was already in front of Duke Long!

Whoosh.

There was a soft sound, time seemed to have been slowed down by countless times.

Duke Long's head lightly separated from his neck.

Blood flowed out slowly and spurted out just as slowly.

He was beheaded by Fang Yuan with one slice!

Chapter 1950: The True Triple Qi Retraction

"Lord Duke Long!!!" The Heavenly Court immortals' horrified cries resounded, but to Duke Long, these voices became increasingly weaker, at the start, they were like roaring waves, but almost at the next moment, they became light echoes from the horizon.

Is this the feeling of death?

I, Duke Long, am finally going to die?

Die here?

Thoughts were still flashing past Duke Long's mind.

Die here?

He asked himself again.

Tired, I am really tired!

He had walked till now while bearing heavy duty and expectations, he withstood the burden of endless sins.

There were times when he really wanted to die!

When he first stepped into the immortal graveyard and hibernated, he had let his imagination run wild: If I died like this, it feels like it might be a pretty good thing.

But could he?

Could he?

He asked himself.

No....

He could not!

He, Duke Long, lived all his life while carrying a heavy burden: He shouldered the expectations of his parents, master, and companions, he shouldered the responsibility of Heavenly Court and humanity, he took on the blame for his disciple's betrayal and the calamity he caused, he took on the sin of exterminating his offspring by his own hands.

He got injured, he got old.

His back slowly bent down, his gaze slowly dimmed.

He slumbered in the immortal graveyard, but when the time came, he crawled up and continued to bear his responsibility and mission!

"That's right, I cannot die, I cannot!"

"I still need to deal with the enemies, I still haven't cleared my sins, I still haven't corrected my mistakes!"

"The immortal graveyard is already destroyed, if I fall now, Feng Jiu Ge will not be able to salvage the situation alone. Heavenly Court will be destroyed by the enemies."

"How can I fall now?"

"I cannot fall!"

"My companions need me, Heavenly Court needs me, humanity needs me!"

"They need me, Duke Long!!"

"So...."

"No matter how tired I am, even if I am extremely exhausted, even if I hibernate in the graveyard, even if I die, even if I have been beheaded!"

"I, Duke Long... cannot afford to fall!"

"I need to stand up, I need to..."

"Continue fighting!!"

Instantly, as if the entire universe was responding to his unyielding will!

A miracle happened!

Duke Long's dimmed pupils suddenly burst out with shocking light that rushed towards the sky. The blood that spurted out of his neck returned rapidly, the countless qi in the surrounding condensed and brought his head back to his neck.

An extremely profound aura carried a true inheritance and entered his body, the wounds on his body started healing rapidly, he completely healed within a few breaths.

"It is Lord Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's method! And this qi path true inheritance... so triple qi retraction can actually be used in this manner!" Duke Long immediately comprehended, great joy surfacing on his face.

"Lord Duke Long, he has revived!" The miracle happened right in front of them, Heavenly Court's morale bounced back.

Fang Yuan's expression was still tranquil: "It is Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's method. There was a backup after all!"

"This is Heavenly Court's foundation?" Wu Yong mumbled, his expression was dark, he felt powerlessness.

Duke Long raised his head and floated in the air, he spread out his arms and legs as he said: "I, Duke Long, will not fall right now. Oh Fang Yuan, let me show you the genuine... Triple Qi Retraction!"

"Triple qi retraction?!" This move's reputation was too huge, the moment Duke Long said this, the three regions' immortals slowed down their offenses in fright and uncertainty.

Fang Yuan's expression was also solemn, he had personally witnessed the terrifying might of triple qi retraction.

Back then, Duke Long had used this move to determine his victory, directly defeating Purple Mountain True Monarch.

"Triple qi retraction has a total of three styles: First style, human qi retraction; second style, earth qi retraction; and third style, heaven qi retraction. Human qi retraction greatly reduces a Gu Immortal's human qi and their condition will fall sharply. Earth qi retraction will extract earth qi and cause heavy damage to the immortal aperture. Heaven qi retraction will extract heaven qi and combined with the damage from the previous two styles, the immortal aperture will shatter directly. If one is hit by the first style, the second style and third style cannot be blocked. So, the key is in the first style!"

All kinds of information flashed through Fang Yuan's mind.

He moved his dragon body and retreated cautiously. Although he had transformed into an immemorial sword dragon and seemed to have gotten rid of his human status, he was not certain if human qi retraction could extract his human qi or not.

Since this move was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, even if there was no transformation path back then, Duke Long would have definitely made relevant modifications to fill this gap.

Whoosh!

At the next moment, vast qi surged from all directions and winds moved like waves, gathering around Duke Long's body.

Endless amounts of human qi, earth qi, and heaven qi gathered in Duke Long's body, turning into countless qi path dao marks while also drastically raising his power in every aspect!

Fang Yuan's eyes narrowed: "What is this? Triple qi retraction's three styles are being activated at the same time, plundering a vast amount of qi to empower Duke Long. Is this a condition triggered by Primordial Origin's method?"

Triple qi retraction's effect had already deviated from its usual ability.

Power, power, an unprecedented power!

The feeling of power filled Duke Long's body and mind. He stepped lightly, boom!

The air below him directly exploded as his body flew like a purple meteor and appeared in front of Fang Yuan in an instance.

Fast, extremely fast!

But Fang Yuan had no fear since reverse flow protection seal was still activated.

Boom!

Duke Long's fist struck his head.

Fang Yuan was knocked down like a cannonball, he smashed into the ground, creating a deep pit.

Reverse flow protection seal immediately appeared shallow and illusory from this attack.

Fang Yuan shook his giant dragon head, shaking off the dizziness, when Duke Long appeared in front of his eyes again. Both sides were within one hundred steps.

Duke Long charged over, his whole body emitted blazing qi that raised his mighty disposition to the extreme.

Fang Yuan's eyes were cold as he snorted inwardly.

Whoosh—!

Myriad Year Flying Warship had already been lying in ambush, and when Duke Long charged forward at this moment, it immediately pierced through the air, like a giant blade that cut towards Duke Long with a heavy shadow of death.

Struck!

Myriad Year Flying Warship was like a giant broadsword that cut Duke Long.

Boom!

Dust and soil flew before they were dispelled by the violent qi around Duke Long.

Duke Long was struck by Myriad Year Flying Warship, he was half-crouching on the ground, one hand holding the ground while the other hand released a powerful strength as it grabbed the front bottom part of Myriad Year Flying Warship — he actually held off the whole of Myriad Year Flying Warship's weight with a single hand!

Crack, crack...

A series of sharp sounds could be heard, the muscles on Duke Long's hands bulged as he slowly pushed back Myriad Year Flying Warship inch by inch.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrank slightly, the Myriad Year Flying Warship of this moment was not the same as before, it was merged with Twelve Zodiac battle formation and was enough to rank among the top five Immortal Gu Houses in the world!

Duke Long actually resisted its full-powered collision with one hand.

The strength amplification Duke Long received from triple qi retraction had far surpassed Fang Yuan's estimation.

Hah!

Duke Long breathed out as he exerted strength and stood up, he brought his other hand together and actually threw Myriad Year Flying Warship far away.

Fang Yuan observed the whole process with indifference, his dragon pupils reflecting Duke Long's clear face. Fang Yuan swung his dragon tail and retreated quickly, leaving the Heaven Overseeing Tower battlefield.

Duke Long's speed already surpassed Fang Yuan's but he could only watch as Fang Yuan left. Because at this moment, Dragon Palace and three Immortal Gu Houses were attacking Feng Jiu Ge. Feng Jiu Ge had to split his attention to resist them, so destiny song unavoidably weakened. Di Zang Sheng was free and charged towards Heaven Overseeing Tower once again!

"Evil Dragon! Stop!" Almost in an instant, Duke Long appeared on Di Zang Sheng's head.

Immortal killer move — Qi Breath Mountain!

An enormous translucent qi mountain took shape in a blink of an eye and pressed down fiercely.

Boom, heaven and earth shook, Di Zang Sheng's head was pressed down to the ground by qi breath mountain.

Triple qi retraction increased the might of Duke Long's qi path methods to a horrifying level.

However, after using this move, the qi around Duke Long fell sharply by thirty percent.

"A chance!" Seeing this, Five Elements Grandmaster, Wu Yong, and Zhang Yin attacked at almost the same time. Three long range killer moves attacked Duke Long.

Duke Long did not dodged and also did not use self-moving dragon qi wall, he actually let the killer moves engulf his body.

Smoke and fire rose, thunder rumbled.

The dazzling scene dissipated, Duke Long was still standing in the sky, standing tall and upright.

"Did you want to scratch my itch with these three small tricks?" Duke Long ridiculed loudly. The faces of Wu Yong, Five Elements Grandmaster, and Zhang Yin reddened with anger and shock.

"Triple qi retraction!" Duke Long shouted once again.

In an instant, vast qi surged and appeared from all corners of Heavenly Court before gathering inside Duke Long's body within a few seconds.

Rumble!

Duke Long's aura expanded once again, not only did he return to his earlier state, he even gained an extra layer. From the original ten feet, it broke through to twenty feet. The aura covered his whole body and the translucent fire burned high.

Duke Long's purple hair waved wildly and his scales shone brightly.

Because of heavenly dragon's last stand as well, Duke Long's body right now had already far surpassed the size of an ordinary human, his body expanded several times and gave an extremely oppressive feeling.

Di Zang Sheng roared, unreconciled as it lifted its giant dragon head out from the pit.

Duke Long suddenly appeared to the side of Di Zang Sheng's head and gave a straight punch. The huge force twisted Di Zang Sheng's head and even its enormous body rolled away, destroying countless buildings of Heavenly Court in its way.

But Duke Long no longer cared about these, everything had to prioritize Heaven Overseeing Tower.

In the previous life, Di Zang Sheng's battle strength could match Duke Long's, but in this life, it was directly suppressed!

If it was said that Feng Jiu Ge used the profundity of destiny song to defeat Di Zang Sheng, then Duke Long suppressed Di Zang Sheng by relying on his own strength.

"I understand now. Although I destroyed the immortal graveyard, Heavenly Court still exists. When a Gu Immortal joins Heavenly Court, they will contribute their immortal aperture; countless grotto-heaven worlds merged together to form the current Heavenly Court. Every immortal aperture is a balance of three qi and contains heaven qi, earth qi, and human qi. Currently, Duke Long is using triple qi retraction not against us but on Heavenly Court." Fang Yuan's thoughts moved lightning fast as he deduced the general details.

Heavenly Court's three qi were naturally exploited by Duke Long and it could even be said to be an infinite supply. With such a powerful supplement, Duke Long's battle strength exploded and suppressed Di Zang Sheng with just his body.

But out of Heavenly Court, the killer move triple qi retraction would lose such might. No such vigorous triple qi were around in the outside world and they could not be used by Duke Long freely.

That meant, Duke Long's strength had limitations, he must stay inside Heavenly Court.

However, even though Fang Yuan saw through this weakness, it was useless.

Heaven Overseeing Tower was also inside Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan had to strive to destroy fate Gu, so he could not bypass Heavenly Court or the current Duke Long!

Chapter 1951: Deadlock

"No matter how strong Duke Long is, he is only one person. Charge! We will attack together, Heavenly Court's defensive line is so wide, let's see how he will defend it." Wu Yong shouted, his sharp gaze containing a trace of restlessness. Duke Long's astonishing performance had already triggered subtle changes in people's hearts, he could not let him act so unbridled!

Wu Yong controlled Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and took the lead, this move immediately made the Immortal Gu Houses around him start attacking once again.

Duke Long snorted, he suddenly disappeared and appeared to block Wu Yong's path. His expression was grim and was about to attack Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building when Dragon Palace also attacked him.

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Duke Long stared with wide eyes as he had no choice but to dodge.

One skill to dominate the world!

Facing the dream path killer move, no matter how strong he was, Duke Long did not dare to test it.

His evasion immediately made Wu Shuai, Wu Yong and others let out a sigh of relief.

Duke Long's mighty image that gave a feeling of being invincible was broken by this action.

The three regions' immortals' falling spirits became concentrated again.

"Fortunately, he dodged it." Thin beads of sweat covered Wu Shuai's head.

Dreamy light smoke might be a dream path killer move but it had a limited strength. Facing such a powerful Duke Long, it was like using a small fish net to capture a giant shark.

Duke Long could not resist dream path killer moves, the giant shark could definitely be trapped, but what about after that? The shark would struggle to break free and could tear the small fish net.

Back to the present, even if Wu Shuai captured Duke Long, it was far beyond Dragon Palace's ability to force such a powerful expert inside the palace, let alone suppress him.

The final conclusion might very well be Dragon Palace crumbling apart while Duke Long would be temporarily trapped inside a dream realm. But there was Feng Jin Huang who could deal with dream realms and quickly rescue Duke Long.

So, Wu Shuai's move was only a bluff. Duke Long took the bait because he was not aware of this dream path killer move's details.

This was also why Gu Immortals kept their killer moves hidden and would not display them easily. And when they showed their killer moves several times, they would actively modify them.

Duke Long retreated, the three regions' immortals led a massive attack once again under Wu Yong's lead, using this opportunity to gather and attack.

"Hmph, besides Lord Duke Long, Heavenly Court also has us!"

"You will definitely pay for underestimating us."

"With us around, don't even think of succeeding."

At the crucial moment, Zhu Que Er, Bai Cang Shui, Zhao Shan He and others of Heavenly Court's main force stepped forward, welcoming the violent attacks without fearing death.

"A bunch of old geezers. How much time do you even have left?" Hua Cai Yun sneered, countless thunder clouds shot out from beside her.

Boom boom boom!

The thunder clouds detonated ahead of time, they were all accurately intercepted by Yu Zhu Zi.

"How much time? We never cared! As long as we have a breath of life in us, we will crawl out from our graves!" Yu Zhu Zi shouted and pushed forward the back of his hand, a large patch of jade powder flew forward like fog.

"Retreat!" Facing the unknown killer move, Hua Cai Yun did not dare to test it and immediately retreated to be on the safe side.

"We will never lose this battle! Do you know why?" Zhou Xiong Xin wore a white robe and had thick eyebrows and a square face. He used information path methods, shooting out countless white arrows.

"Because since three million years ago, we have always been the pioneers of the eras, the backbone of humanity, the heroes of Central Continent. We will never forget the disgrace of becoming slaves to variant humans, we will never forget that peace is something we have fought for using our lives, and we will never forget that the happiness of the people needs to be guarded by each generation."

"As for you, you are petty people who don't care about endangering humanity for your selfish interests. Short-sighted fools who cannot even see the future! Come, no matter what methods you have, no matter how many times you attack, you will only receive defeat!"

Zhou Xiong Xin shouted loudly, his endless arrows became stronger with his words; using attack as defense, the arrows forced back Five Elements Grandmaster, Yi Hao Fang, and other rank eights. They could only prioritize defense, the offense they had just started as well as their morale shrank rapidly."

"Look, this is our Heavenly Court's perseverance!" Zhu Que Er and Prince Feng Xian combined their skills, flames surged and formed a completely new defensive line, firmly blocking the charge of several rank seven Immortal Gu Houses.

"Hmph, a bunch of babbling geezers. The immortal graveyard is already destroyed now, after killing you, let me see who else will stand up in Heavenly Court?" A famous expert in Northern Plains' history, Liu Hui had just finished speaking when he felt his vision darken.

Duke Long suddenly appeared right before him!

Boom!

Immortal killer move — Dragon Claw Strike!

Liu Hui's whole body let out a bright green light, his defensive killer move was activated with full power. But it only lasted for a second before it shattered, his whole body was slashed into pieces.

Liu Hui died immediately from Duke Long's one attack.

Five Elements Grandmaster and others quickly retreated in fright, entering their respective side's Immortal Gu Houses.

Duke Long swept his gaze around the battlefield and shouted: "You colluded with the otherworldly demon and attempted to overthrow Heavenly Court, you are all traitors to humanity. You don't understand, even if we battle to the death, our three qi will still remain. This is the grand qi of humanity, it will last forever with mountains and the land itself. Triple qi retraction!"

Boom!!

A huge explosion sounded, the whole sky turned dark. Three qi flocked and gathered into Duke Long's body from all areas of Heavenly Court.

Duke Long's translucent blazing qi expanded wildly, giving a heart-shaking feeling to everyone.

Immortal killer move — Great Qi Hand Explosion!

Duke Long stretched his left arm and spread his five fingers, his palm pointed towards a rank seven Immortal Gu House.

At the next moment, he clenched his left hand.

Bam.

Great qi exploded, the rank seven Immortal Gu House split into pieces, exploding into countless fragments. Immortal Gu were all destroyed, the Gu Immortals inside also met with calamity, none survived and only bones, blood, and meat pulp were left behind.

The three regions' Gu Immortals were horrified and stupefied.

Heavenly Court's side cheered loudly.

"This is Heavenly Court's power!" Inside Demon Judgment Board, Qin Ding Ling's eyes shined brightly. Fang Zheng, however, was silent as he was shaken mentally.

The shock was not only to Duke Long's strength, there was also a kind of turbulence going on in his mind.

At this moment, Fang Zheng began to understand the spirit of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals!

"Yes." Fang Zheng thought inwardly: "If there were no Heavenly Court in history, could there be the current human race? Generations of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals cleared away obstacles with their blood, making countless sacrifices to bring about the rule of humanity. Comparatively, Fang Yuan and these people disregard the big picture, destroying fate Gu is giving the variant humans a chance to rise up. They are indeed traitors to humanity."

Swish!

Right at this time, a sword light pierced through the battlefield, bringing forth a soft sound and a bloody figure.

Zhu Que Er slowly fell to the ground like a sparrow whose wings were cut, her body was directly slashed into two halves.

Immortal killer move — Five Finger Fist Heart Sword!

It was Fang Yuan! He was sinisterly roaming at the edge of the battlefield in his immemorial sword dragon form.

"Fang Yuan!" Heavenly Court's immortals were furious.

Fang Yuan sneered: "I am here for my own interests! I don't give a damn about what you are, you can be noble or insignificant for all I care. Today, I will destroy fate Gu, I will kill whoever dares to stop me, if an immortal blocks me, I will slay the immortal, if a demon comes, I will slaughter the demon in my way! Heavenly Court? Since you obstruct my path, you will meet with the same outcome!"

"Hmph, demon! You need to be executed!"

"Kill him!"

"Murderer, I will crush you to pieces!!"

Heavenly Court's immortals cursed.

Roar—!

Di Zang Sheng recovered and collided into the defensive line again.

Dragon Palace cooperated and used dreamy light smoke.

Wherever the dream path killer move went, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals evaded. Feng Jiu Ge gave a light sigh, activating a killer move and turning it into a song warrior.

The song warrior threw itself into the dreamy light smoke. Dreamy light smoke thus had no more offensive ability and returned like a python that had eaten its fill.

Feng Jiu Ge could not directly break the dream path killer move, but he was able to block it by using this method.

Destiny song resounded once again, Di Zang Sheng roared discontentedly but was without options, and was once again suppressed by Feng Jiu Ge.

Far away, Spectral Soul and his servants had already arrived in front of a treasury.

Looking back at the battlefield, Fairy Zi Wei sighed: "I did not think triple qi retraction still had this use. Duke Long's battle strength has risen to an astonishing level. Adding on Feng Jiu Ge's assistance, Heavenly Court's defensive line looks to be on the verge of collapse but is actually able to keep on lasting."

According to overall strength, Heavenly Court was naturally stronger.

But they had to defend Heaven Overseeing Tower and were thus extremely passive, even Duke Long was shackled by this.

Duke Long could easily kill rank eight Gu Immortals or rank seven Immortal Gu Houses, and Fang Yuan could similarly kill Heavenly Court members easily by using five finger fist heart sword. Duke Long had to leave the defensive line and choose to fight Fang Yuan far away.

If these two were allowed to attack the other side's Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan would not feel even a little heartache, but Heavenly Court needed enough manpower to defend the place. Duke Long would never let Fang Yuan continue his slaughter.

On the contrary, if Fang Yuan endured Duke Long's attacks, wholeheartedly attacking Heavenly Court's main force was also an option. But if he chose to do this, he would have to bear Duke Long's heavy attacks. Fang Yuan was not willing to do this, after all, he and the other three regions' Gu Immortals allied only because of the situation. Sacrificing himself for them was too stupid and too risky.

Thus, Fang Yuan and Duke Long pinned down each other.

Feng Jiu Ge instead became the core of the battle, he took charge of Heaven Overseeing Tower's defense while blocking Dragon Palace and Di Zang Sheng. His battle strength surpassed both enemies and allies' expectations time and again.

Old Man Zheng Yuan narrowed his eyes: "Now, we just have to see who can break the stalemate. The crucial point is fate Gu. Heavenly Court has already harvested the success dao marks, but the refinement path Gu formation is destroyed, can Yuan Qiong Du alone be able to restore fate Gu in time? Master, if we interfere now, can't we seize fate Gu?"

Spectral Soul laughed: "What will we gain by snatching it? Don't think that they are fighting with all they have got, they are still holding back. There is more to this situation than meets the eye! The past venerables have gotten involved in this battle. We will talk after plundering this treasury and getting back the Door of Life and Death."

"Yes, master!"

Chapter 1952: Responsibility and Sacrifice

On the side of a sect's mountain, the landscape was green, clear water flowed by it and birds' chirping could be heard.

"Little Du, what are you lying on the ground for?" A gentle and soft voice could be heard.

"Senior sister." The young Yuan Qiong Du opened his eyes and saw a girl bending over to look at him with her bright and smiling eyes.

The girl's gaze moved to Little Du's hand and let out a gasp: "Wha, Little Du, you refined a rank three Gu again. You are really amazing."

"But I am not happy, you know I don't like cultivating refinement path." Yuan Qiong Du stood up while mumbling.

"Don't be so dispirited, your talent is envied by so many people." The girl patted his shoulder and consoled.

But Yuan Qiong Du was still dispirited and his head slumped forward.

"Haha, how about this, I will share a secret with you. Few days ago, I found clues to a Gu Master inheritance in my father's study room, it is hidden at some corner of the mountain. What do you think, do you want to search for it?" Senior sister's beautiful gaze turned towards Yuan Qiong Du.

As expected, teenage Yuan Qiong Du could not endure boredom, his eyes brightened when he heard what was said: "There is such a fun thing? Wonderful, our sect's mountain has inheritances left behind by predecessors after all. Gu Immortal inheritances are extremely rare but Gu Master inheritances are plentiful. Tell me the clues quickly, senior sister."

"Okay. The clue is a line of a poem, I have been pondering about it these few days, I will read it to you." Senior sister did not conceal it, and this was only a Gu Master inheritance. Her father was also Yuan Qiong Du's master, a Gu Immortal existence.

Yuan Qiong Du clapped his hands after hearing it just once: "I understand. The clue is solved like this, match the first and last characters, then match second and the second last characters; it gives us a location."

Senior sister pondered for a bit and jumped with joy: "So it is there! Little Du, you are really smart, you guessed it immediately."

"Let's go find it quickly." Yuan Qiong Du moved ahead.

"Wait for me." Senior sister quickly followed.

"Don't worry, senior sister, I will give this inheritance to you, I won't snatch it from you, haha." Yuan Qiong Du's figure disappeared into the depths of the mountain forest.

Finally, the two found the inheritance inside a mountain cave.

"This is a fire path inheritance." Yuan Qiong Du and his senior sister inspected the inheritance carefully: "Will flame? A fire that uses will as the fuel. This method is quite original and stunning. How did the Gu Master who created it think of this? Interesting. Eh, this name, how could it be master?"

Yuan Qiong Du was extremely surprised.

Senior sister also felt surprised, saying uncertainly: "They might just have the same name?"

Yuan Qiong Du, however, pondered and his eyes shone: "Maybe not! Senior sister, I remember you saying that you found this clue in master's study room."

"Yes, I was tidying up father's bamboo scrolls, you know my father's hobby is to collect these antiques. And by chance, a bamboo stick slipped from an aged scroll, and on it was the inheritance clue." Senior sister recalled her memory.

"This inheritance was set up by me when I was young." Right at this time, Yuan Qiong Du's master slowly walked into the cave and appeared before Yuan Qiong Du.

Walking alongside him was Yuan Qiong Du's sect uncle, who was short in stature, had a round face, and looked amiable.

Yuan Qiong Du and his senior sister quickly bowed and greeted at the same time: "We pay respects to master (father) and sect uncle."

Yuan Qiong Du curled up his lips: "Master, are you making fun of your disciples?"

"Of course not." His master shook his head, looking at the inheritance in Yuan Qiong Du's hand with a trace of reminiscence.

"Hahaha, you clever brat." The fat sect uncle pointed at Yuan Qiong Du: "Your master and I just returned from Spirit Resonance Peak, we were just chatting along the way when we discovered your traces. I can guarantee that this inheritance was indeed left by your master during his youth. He wholeheartedly liked fire path back then and used five years to painstakingly gather primeval stones and purchase a rank three fire path Gu."

"But master clearly cultivates water path." Yuan Qiong Du's eyes were wide open, having not expected his master also liked fire path, like him, when he was young.

"There was no other choice." The fat sect uncle sighed: "Our sect's water path inheritance required an inheritor. How could an individual's preference compare to the sect's situation? Every Gu Immortal inheritance needs to be inherited from generation to generation. Every inheritor will improve the inheritance on the foundation of their predecessor, making the inheritance keep up with the times and not be eliminated. This is our responsibility. When your master gave up fire path, he personally arranged this inheritance. I was there at that time and saw him crying his eyes out."

"Cough cough." Yuan Qiong Du's master interrupted: "Since you two discovered this inheritance, then it shall belong to you. Let's go."

The two seniors left, leaving behind Yuan Qiong Du and his senior sister in the cave.

"Junior brother, I cultivate wood path, I don't need this, so I will give it to you." Senior sister also said goodbye to Yuan Qiong Du.

Yuan Qiong Du gazed at the inheritance in his hand, slight waves undulated in his heart as he mumbled: "Master..."

He opened his eyes again.

Yuan Qiong Du saw that he was still inside Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"Damn it! I suffered a backlash during the refinement and fainted!" Yuan Qiong Du's heart pounded madly as he recalled the scene.

The biggest taboo in Gu refinement was to be disturbed. It did not matter how heavy his injuries were, the main thing was whether fate Gu was alright or not. This was related to the plan that Heavenly Court had been executing for millions of years!

Yuan Qiong Du was almost already without hope.

As the only Gu Immortal to refine Gu, he had actually fainted. Could fate Gu, that was the target of the refinement, be unharmed?

Fate Gu would not be destroyed because of this, but it was very likely that most of the previous restoration results would disappear, it might even return to the original damaged state.

Right now, Yuan Qiong Du could only hope fate Gu's situation was slightly better, his and Heavenly Court's countless years of efforts must not go to waste.

But when Yuan Qiong Du raised his head to look at fate Gu, he was stunned.

"What?!"

A lump of fire had taken his place in the Gu refinement, fate Gu was quietly lying in the fire and was just half a step away from complete recovery.

After the shock, warmth surged in Yuan Qiong Du's heart.

This was his will flame!

A fire which used will as fuel, he had obtained it from his master's inheritance when he was young. Later on, he cultivated refinement path but did not forget fire path as well, he continued to improve the will flame and developed it to immortal level.

"Will flame has already become my most familiar and most skilled Gu refinement method. I probably activated will flame unconsciously when I fainted!" Yuan Qiong Du guessed.

This was not the first time this happened. In fact, throughout his life, in his countless Gu refinement experiences, there were many times when will flame took his place in emergencies. Every time he was unable to hold on, he would activate will flame to temporarily replace him and stabilize the situation.

After countless times, using will flame at the crucial times had already become his subconscious habit.

Yuan Qiong Du let out a breath of air.

He looked at the burning will flame quietly while thinking: "Rather than calling it a habit, more accurately, this is a type of responsibility."

He thought of his master and smiled: "Responsibility... Master, looks like I haven't disappointed you."

Yuan Qiong Du knew his condition, his injuries were too heavy and he was not able to continue the Gu refinement. But hope was in front of him, he used his last bit of life and willpower to reinforce this lump of will flame.

"Burn, burn more." Yuan Qiong Du mumbled, he used his own life to light the will flame!

The will flame burned quietly, the fire brightened and became extremely stable.

Inside the fire, fate Gu finally moved past the final step, it achieved complete recovery!

While Yuan Qiong Du was already lifeless.

Like his master, like his senior sister, and like the countless Heavenly Court's seniors, they had given their blood and sweat for the cause of Heavenly Court, using their own lives to build the foundation of Heavenly Court!

He was a true hero even in death!

Heavenly Court's foundation, the large Central Continent was paved with blood and sacrifices.

The will flame dissipated.

"Hehehe." Cong Yan's weak laughter resounded in the quiet top floor of Heaven Overseeing Tower: "Yuan Qiong Du has already accomplished his task, it is our turn now."

"But with our state, even transmitting our voices is troublesome, let alone activating Heaven Overseeing Tower." Che Wei said, his tone was quiet and deep.

Cong Yan replied back almost as if he was not worried: "There is still a way. The immortal essence remaining in my aperture is enough for me to activate my trump card, isn't it so coincidental?"

Che Wei and Cong Yan were close friends, Che Wei immediately realized Cong Yan's meaning: "Don't do this, if you absorb my injuries, you will die immediately."

"What is there to fear about death? Right now, our companions are fighting outside, the defensive line is on the verge of collapsing, they probably don't have the chance to send anyone else. Brother Che Wei, we have known each other for many years, your abilities are stronger than mine. But your journey has not been completed yet, you will soon create your own path, I really look forward to it... but it is such a pity that I won't be able to witness it."

As Cong Yan spoke lightly, a light blue radiance spread from his body and covered Che Wei.

The two Gu Immortals had wounds everywhere, even their bones and flesh were smashed in. But following the blue light's effect, Che Wei's body began to recover while Cong Yan's became more severe.

"My friend..." Che Wei closed his eyes before opening them, two trails of tears flowed down quietly.

Cong Yan was dead, Che Wei's injuries were still severe but he used all his strength to barely crawl towards fate Gu.

"Activate, activate... I beg of you." Che Wei's vision turned dark, he poured in all his immortal essence and could only pray quietly at this point.

Chapter 1953: Fang Yuan Falls

A long time seemed to have passed, but it was only an instant.

The grand Heaven Overseeing Tower began to slowly let out a pure-white light, the light gradually grew brighter and began to rise.

Several breaths later, the light shot to the sky and illuminated the whole battlefield like an emperor had descended!

The chaotic and violent battlefield paused immediately.

Almost all Gu Immortals raised their heads and looked towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

The three regions' Gu Immortals were pale and ashen, while tears and snot flowed down the faces of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals.

"Rank nine fate Gu has been restored!"

"Yuan Qiong Du did not fail us! He did it! This is too amazing."

"Heaven Overseeing Tower has returned to its peak state, we have won!"

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals cheered, their morale rose to the peak at once.

"Retreat, retreat!" Be it Wu Yong, Yao Huang, or Shen Cong Sheng and others, they all shouted to retreat with no intent to battle.

Bing Sai Chuan was still controlling Calamity Luck Altar, he transmitted his voice to Fang Yuan with an unresigned expression: "Do something quickly!"

Fang Yuan's immemorial sword dragon transformation, however, began to retreat rapidly.

Duke Long gave up on Fang Yuan and used dragon gate to rapidly travel to Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"Fate Gu, fate Gu..." When he saw the completely intact fate Gu, he could not restrain his intense emotions anymore, tears flowed down as if he was released from a heavy burden.

The one who had injured fate Gu back then was his disciple Red Lotus, to make up for this mistake, Duke Long resolved himself and took on the heavy responsibility of restoring fate Gu.

"Hong Ting, master has atoned for your mistake. I did not let down Heavenly Court, I did not let down humanity!" Duke Long took deep breaths before he regained his cool. He looked outside the tower with a sharp gaze.

"Now, it is time for you all to die!" Duke Long shouted and activated Heaven Overseeing Tower's strongest offensive method.

Immortal killer move — Fate Vanquish!

Light, light that filled heaven and earth, it was omnipresent, illuminating the universe and people's hearts.

In just an instance, all the rank seven Immortal Gu Houses in the battlefield crumbled, the Gu Immortals inside fortunately survived.

Even Calamity Luck Altar and Dragon Palace were in miserable states. Bing Sai Chuan, Wu Shuai, Zhan Bu Du and others immediately used all their efforts in repairing the Immortal Gu Houses.

The surviving historical rank eight experts of Northern Plains dissipated after the light shone on them.

Countless year beasts and swordsmen of Fang Yuan that caused disaster to Heavenly Court were mostly destroyed, blood flowed like a river.

Mao Li Qiu's perfect pair killer move was forcefully broken, Di Zang Sheng was suppressed to the ground and was actually unable to get up immediately!

Only Fang Yuan's immemorial sword dragon form was completely safe.

He was a complete otherworldly demon who could not be targeted by the killer move fate vanquish and had a natural immunity towards it!

"Only you remain now, Fang Yuan!" Duke Long stared at the immemorial sword dragon with an intense killing intent and hatred.

It was this otherworldly demon that destroyed the immortal graveyard, destroying the largest portion of the millions of years of foundation of Heavenly Court!

This sin could not be forgiven, he must suffer a cruel death!

Boom—!

Duke Long flew out of Heaven Overseeing Tower and pierced through the sky towards Fang Yuan.

"Block him, stop Fang Yuan!" Duke Long roared, his voice resonated throughout the whole Heavenly Court.

Destiny song started in time as Fang Yuan's retreating speed fell sharply.

Immortal killer move — Qi Current Scissors!

Duke Long neared and opened his palm; countless sharp qi currents formed extremely sharp qi blades that shrouded Fang Yuan like a storm.

Fang Yuan canceled reverse flow protection seal and charged through the qi blades' encirclement, leaving behind a bloody trail in the sky.

Myriad Year Flying Warship quickly flew over and reunited with Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan stepped on the deck and transformed into the immemorial year monkey, he then turned around and waved his arm. Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Wild winds surged, scattering all of the qi current scissors.

Fang Yuan stomped on the deck, Myriad Year Flying Warship gave off a buzzing sound and let out dazzling radiance as it activated a time path killer move — Myriad Year Hunting.

Splash splash splash.

The River of Time phantom under Myriad Year Flying Warship continued to bubble, countless year beasts were summoned once again and participated in the battle, spreading out everywhere.

At this time, Feng Jiu Ge moved ahead of Duke Long.

Immortal killer move — Submission Song!

Immortal killer move — Song Warrior!

Submission song's power condensed into human form as it ran amok through the army of countless year beasts. Wherever it went, the year beasts, regardless of strong or weak, betrayed Fang Yuan and submitted to Feng Jiu Ge.

"Great job!" Even Duke Long felt surprised and joyous at this sight.

Previously, Feng Jiu Ge had been using destiny song mainly to maintain the battlefield and was unable to use other methods. Now that there was a chance, he immediately showed his abundant methods.

Duke Long once again neared Myriad Year Flying Warship and used killer moves like world shaking dragon hammer alternately, destroying daybreak swords. Cracks spread in Myriad Year Flying Warship and large numbers of Gu worms died instantly.

Fang Yuan was forced to retreat again and again, he had to use all his strength to repair Myriad Year Flying Warship while also blocking Duke Long and Feng Jiu Ge's joint attacks.

"It is our turn to counterattack!" Prince Feng Xian led the wave of counterattack.

A sharp phoenix cry resounded, his whole body transformed into a phoenix. He spread his wings and flew, fire burned everywhere he went and turned into a sea of fire.

Bai Cang Shui attacked almost at the same time from the other end of the defensive line, pale towering waves shot out.

Jun Shen Guang was like a meteor as he moved across the battlefield.

Zhou Xiong Xin was accompanied by fierce information path tigers. Vortex Space Boy and Ye Qiao Zi attacked together. Zhao Shan He and Yu Zhu Zi once again used sitting and eating the mountain empty against the enemy Immortal Gu Houses.

Previously, because of Duke Long's might, the three regions' Gu Immortals were all withdrawn inside the Immortal Gu Houses.

Facing Heavenly Court's wave of counterattacks, Calamity Luck Altar, Dragon Palace, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, and other Immortal Gu Houses were unable to resist and retreated while fighting.

Heavenly Court's side continued to push with Heaven Overseeing Tower and Demon Judgment Board as the cores, continuously reducing the movement area of the three regions' Gu Immortals.

Qin Ding Ling also flew out of Demon Judgment Board and used all kinds of luck path methods to amplify her side's offenses to the maximum degree. After all, the enemy Gu Immortals were hiding inside Immortal Gu Houses, they could not attack casually and had to use the Immortal Gu Houses' methods.

The three regions' Gu Immortals were forced to retreat again and again, their conditions were already bad because of fate vanquish. Most of the Gu Immortals had to concentrate on repairing the Immortal Gu Houses, they could only endure the beating passively.

With no alternatives, Mao Li Qiu, Wu Yong, and some others took the risk to fly out of the Immortal Gu Houses and fought Heavenly Court's side to strive for precious time for the repair of the Immortal Gu Houses.

"Hold on! If we can't hold on now, leaving Heavenly Court will only be wishful thinking."

"Be careful of Heaven Overseeing Tower, especially fate vanquish!"

"How is Fang Yuan's situation? Only he can resist fate vanquish."

Like in the previous life, the immortals entrusted their hopes to Fang Yuan once again.

Despite many of the Gu Immortals hating Fang Yuan, the current situation forced them to rely on him.

But what disappointed the immortals was that Fang Yuan's situation was also similarly bad.

He was being pincer-attacked by Feng Jiu Ge and Duke Long, he was barely resisting the attacks with the help of Myriad Year Flying Warship.

The killer move fate vanquish with fate Gu as the core had no effect on Fang Yuan. But Feng Jiu Ge's destiny song that was only rank eight was of an even higher plane, it not only included fate but also contained luck.

Luck was naturally effective against Fang Yuan. Before this, Fang Yuan had used luck path methods many times to help in his cultivation.

Destiny song was effective against Fang Yuan, greatly weakening him, almost offsetting the amplification from heroes among people.

On the contrary, Duke Long could not enjoy heroes among people but he was empowered by heavenly dragon's last stand, triple qi retraction, and destiny song, increasing his battle strength to an unimaginably shocking level.

With Duke Long attacking and Feng Jiu Ge supporting him, Fang Yuan was unable to take them head-on and had to retreat again and again.

"Heavenly Court cannot be defeated!" Duke Long's punches and kicks exploded the air as they landed on Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was like a small raft in a storm, it was sent flying and crashed on the ground.

"Fang Yuan, here's another move for you." Duke Long charged down like a meteor, wanting to collide directly.

Fang Yuan looked at the sky and snorted, golden lights shone around Myriad Year Flying Warship as the Twelve Zodiac battle formation separated and transformed into a grey stone giant.

The giant stood on Heavenly Court's ground and waved its hands, attacking Duke Long head-on.

Boom!

An explosion rang, Duke Long collided with the giant. Killer moves clashed, creating a powerful explosion.

The terrifying heat wave inflated like a giant balloon before bursting on the spot.

Tornadoes and shock waves engulfed everything, Fang Yuan and the almost crumbling Myriad Year Flying Warship retreated smoothly using this propulsion force.

Whoosh.

Wind roared as Duke Long's monstrously tall figure suddenly appeared behind Fang Yuan.

Immortal killer move — World Shaking Dragon Hammer!

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk rapidly, he did not have the time to even turn around as he activated reverse flow protection seal.

Rumble!

Reverse flow protection seal finally reached its limits and broke apart.

Fang Yuan suffered Duke Long's attack, although he had transformed into the immemorial year monkey, his back was almost pierced.

The enormous force sent Fang Yuan flying. After he fell to the ground, his body was dragged along the ground, leaving behind a long trail of blood and only stopping after crashing through three Immortal Gu Houses.

Duke Long gave a muffled groan, his body was shaking. Reverse flow protection seal reflected external attacks, the strength he struck Fang Yuan was also reflected to him in full, he had to suffer an even more serious impact than Fang Yuan. After all, Fang Yuan had reverse flow protection seal to weaken the strength of the attack as well as the powerful body of the immemorial year monkey.

Duke Long panted heavily, he was not able to move immediately and concentrated on healing his wounds quickly.

At the edge of the battlefield, the immortal treasury was already looted clean by Spectral Soul and his servants, but they had yet to find the Door of Life and Death.

"Strange, the Door of Life and Death was clearly placed here." Fairy Zi Wei frowned.

"Looks like Duke Long has hidden many things from you." Spectral Soul said coldly. The Door of Life and Death was a secluded domain of heaven and earth and contained countless souls. Its importance to Spectral Soul was huge, but unfortunately, they could not find it.

"Master, Fang Yuan is not able to hold on, do we give him a hand to maintain the stalemate and get more time for ourselves?" Old Man Zheng Yuan asked.

Spectral Soul gazed at the battlefield and when he saw Fang Yuan's position, he suddenly smiled: "There is no hurry, there is still a venerable who has not made a move yet."

Fang Yuan was collapsed in his own pool of blood in front of Embroidered Tower.

Three blood skins of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable were sewn in the air. Blown by the violent winds of the battlefield, these three blood skins actually loosened and waved around like banners.

In an instant, Fang Yuan sniffed a dense, fishy stench of blood!

Chapter 1954: Pursue — Freedom!

Fang Yuan's whole body was bathed in blood and filled with injuries. He snorted coldly and stood up, looking at Embroidered Tower in front of him.

Embroidered Tower was originally a mortal object that was left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable to his disciple Star Constellation as her dowry. But according to the customs back then, its symbolic meaning was much greater. Later, when Star Constellation became Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, she turned Embroidered Tower into an Immortal Gu House that had extremely mystical powers.

Over a million years ago, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable invaded Heavenly Court. He stormed through Heavenly Court, passing Immortal Emperor Court, Hidden Space Pavilion, Sumeru Lake, Eternal Sand Cave, Million Heavenly King Gallery, Embroidered Tower, Central Great Hall, and finally stopping at Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable suffered some loss when he reached Embroidered Tower, Embroidered Tower used its trump card method — Dao Embroidery. Seven embroidery needles flew out elegantly. Reckless Savage Demon Venerable was forced to discard three pieces of his skin before he was able to go past it.

These three bloody skins were sewn into the air by countless dao mark threads.

After that, Embroidered Tower's damage could not be repaired. And later, it was used to attack Spectral Soul in Yi Tian Mountain, the new damage added to the previous ones. This damage ruined Embroidered Tower and it could not be of any use right now.

Not only Fang Yuan, even Duke Long and other Gu Immortals saw the movement of the three bloody skins in the air above Embroidered Tower!

They looked like three bloody banners, fluttering savagely in the wind.

The left banner had a bird drawn on it, the bird had six legs but no wings.

The middle bloody banner had a drawing of a beast which was getting increasingly clearer. It opened its mouth but had no teeth.

The right bloody skin had a fish, it grew increasingly vivid and lifelike but it was clear that it had no gills.

Blood skins made wild sounds like an ancient gale that crossed a million years and roared in people's ears. Or like a grand army that went to battle, clashes and collisions of steel and horses resounded!

The blood banners' fluttering continued to amplify in commotion, they were like volcanoes that had been suppressed for countless years or like wild beasts that had accumulated their energy and was about to strike their prey!

Roar—!

The wild beasts roared.

They violently broke the dao mark threads that bound them, and turned into three blood red lights that landed around Fang Yuan.

Three beastly bizarre and resounding roars sounded and the blood red light dissipated, revealing three enormous beasts.

A glowing monstrous yellow bird that was like a small mountain, its six legs were thick and rough, its beak was hard and long, but it had no wings.

An azure-blue leopard with a big belly was sprawled on the ground, it kept on yawning and one could see it did not have even a single tooth.

And a fish with dark green scales was floating in the air, its head was raised high and its mouth was closed tightly. There was no trace of gills next to its eyes. The huge fish was motionless like a jade statue.

The immortals were shaken, even Duke Long's expression turned solemn as he halted his attacks.

"There is an abnormality in the three bloody skins left by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable!"

"These three monsters have such shocking auras."

"Did Fang Yuan trigger a venerable's method?"

"Wait a second, these three monsters, why do they resemble those three recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?"

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter four states —

Ren Zu wandered alone on the vast land, his hair was disheveled and he seemed to have lost his mind: at times, he wailed, at times, he sat down in a daze, and at times, he laughed like a fool.

Fate Gu's manipulation had separated him from his children, he also lost wealth Gu, Ren Zu was forced into a state of madness.

"Who am I? Where am I? What am I doing?" Ren Zu was at a loss and went crazy again.

One morning, a group of birds ran past Ren Zu.

These birds did not have wings, their six legs moved alternately as they ran on the ground, raising clouds of dust in their path.

Ren Zu jumped with joy when he saw these birds.

"So I am a bird!" He also spread his legs and ran wildly, joining the bird group.

The birds growled strangely towards Ren Zu: "You are a human, you use two legs to walk, you are not a bird. Leave, don't disturb us, we are pursuing freedom Gu, we want to retrieve our freedom."

Ren Zu asked: "Why are you all searching for freedom Gu?"

The birds said with a heavy tone: "We once possessed freedom Gu, but we did not realize that. Only after losing it, we found that we no longer had wings and could not fly anymore. When we regain freedom, we will be able to spread our wings and soar to the sky again."

Ren Zu realized: "I understand, humans also need freedom. If humans don't have freedom, they will be like birds who have lost their wings."

"Right! I remember now!" Ren Zu clapped and laughed madly: "I also need to search for freedom to get rid of fate's shackles. After that, I can go wherever I want to go, and be with whomever I want to be forever."

The birds casted a strange look at Ren Zu: "Oh human, how can you have such preposterous thoughts?"

"Look at us, how can birds not have wings? So, chasing after freedom is part of our duty."

"But you humans are destined to be alone, all gatherings will end up in separation. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies."

Ren Zu scratched his head, puzzled: "Is that how it works?"

The birds left behind their last words: "Oh human, let us give you some sincere advice. If you obtain freedom in the future, you must cherish it, don't be like us and let go. Don't let freedom Gu fly away, otherwise you will regret it."

After Ren Zu parted ways with the birds, he slowly forgot his identity and goals once again.

One afternoon, a leap of blue leopards passed by him.

The insane Ren Zu saw the group of leopards and shouted in joy: "So I am a leopard."

Ren Zu rushed into the group.

But the leopards pushed him away and shouted: "You are a human, not a leopard. You use two legs to walk, while we have four legs. Leave, don't disturb us. We are pursuing freedom Gu, we want to retrieve our freedom."

Ren Zu asked: "Why are you searching for freedom Gu?"

The blue leopards looked depressed: "Sigh, we once possessed freedom Gu, but we did not realize it. Only after losing it, we found that we no longer had teeth and could not bite and tear apart our prey. When we regain freedom, we will be able to eat happily again."

Ren Zu realized: "I understand, humans also need freedom. If humans don't have freedom, they will be like beasts with no teeth."

"Right!" Ren Zu clapped and laughed madly: "I need to search for freedom to get rid of fate's shackles. I will possess countless delicacies and wines, endless wealth, and all kinds of comfortable and beautiful clothes."

The blue leopards were stunned before laughing loudly as they mocked Ren Zu: "Oh human, how can you have such preposterous thoughts?"

"Look at us, how can beasts not have fangs or claws? So, chasing after freedom is part of our duty."

"But you humans were born with empty hands and will pass away with nothing. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies."

Ren Zu scratched his head, unsatisfied: "Is that how it works?"

The leopards left behind their final words: "Oh human, let us give you some sincere advice. If you obtain freedom in the future, you must cherish it, don't be like us and let go. Don't let freedom Gu fly away, otherwise you will regret it."

After Ren Zu parted ways with the leopards, he slowly forgot his identity and goals once again.

One evening, a school of fish swam past him.

Ren Zu saw the fish and shouted in joy: "So I am a fish."

Ren Zu joined the fish group and tried to swim like them.

There was a commotion in the fish group as they pushed Ren Zu away and shouted: "You are a human, not a fish. You use two legs to walk, while we have no legs. Leave, don't disturb us. We are pursuing freedom Gu, we want to retrieve our freedom."

Ren Zu asked: "Why are you searching for freedom Gu?"

The fish sighed: "We once possessed freedom Gu, but we did not realize that. Only after losing it, we found that we no longer had gills and could not breathe in the water again. When we regain freedom, we will be able to swim in the water again."

Ren Zu realized: "I understand, humans also need freedom. If humans don't have freedom, they will be like fish with no gills and cannot breathe."

"Right!" Ren Zu clapped and laughed madly: "I need to search for freedom to get rid of fate's shackles. I will breathe freely and live on forever, I want eternal life!"

The fish sneered: "Oh human, how can you have such preposterous thoughts?"

"Look at us, a fish must have gills, so chasing after freedom is part of our duty."

"But you humans are destined to have no relation with eternal life, you will die of old age and illnesses. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies."

Ren Zu frowned, feeling irritated: "Is that how it works?"

The fishes left behind their final words: "Oh human, let us give you some sincere advice. If you obtain freedom in the future, you must cherish it, don't be like us and let go. Don't let freedom Gu fly away, otherwise you will regret it."

After Ren Zu parted ways with the fishes, he slowly forgot the advice of the birds, leopards, and the fish.

"I am a human, I need to pursue freedom!"

"I need to get rid of the shackles of fate, I want to live forever with my loved ones, I want to enjoy life with enough wealth, I want to live on forever."

Many beings that walked past Ren Zu heard him, they shook their heads and stayed away from him.

"Let's quickly leave, he is Ren Zu and he is talking nonsense again."

"He has already gone mad completely."

"How could he dare to have such thoughts?"

One day, freedom Gu flew towards Ren Zu on its own accord.

Ren Zu was joyous as he grabbed it.

"Oh freedom, I finally obtained freedom." Ren Zu was extremely happy but also felt puzzled as he asked freedom Gu: "This is really strange, the wingless birds are pursuing you, the toothless beasts are pursuing you, the gill-less fish are pursuing you, but you flew to me, what is going on here?"

Freedom Gu replied: "I didn't fly to you, human, you once used attitude Gu to bully me, used love to bind me, and used wealth to bribe me. I loathe and hate you! I flew over because I was attracted by the cognition Gu on you."

Cognition Gu floated out of Ren Zu's body and explained with a smile: "Ren Zu, because you have gone mad, you are thinking deliriously all the time. A human that desires companionship forever, a human who has an extravagant hope of living a life with no worries, a human who pursues eternal life; what else can this be other than a lunatic?"

Freedom Gu sighed: "Freedom of cognition is the greatest freedom. These delirious thoughts can strengthen me. Ren Zu, although you captured me, I will never work for you. Release me now!"

Ren Zu shook his head and grasped even tighter: "Freedom Gu, I will not let you go."

Freedom Gu sneered: "Then prepare yourself, don't collapse from the pressure."

The moment it finished speaking, responsibility Gu flew over, pressing on Ren Zu's shoulder.

"Heavy, so heavy!" Ren Zu almost bent over from the pressure.

Cognition Gu sighed: "Freedom and responsibility coexist, oh Ren Zu, you want to obtain freedom so you need to shoulder the responsibility. At least, you need to be responsible for yourself."

Ren Zu clenched his teeth and persevered, sweat flowed down his body like a river, soon, he knelt down on the ground.

He saw spider webs again.

Fate Gu's spider silk wrapped around his whole body. Ren Zu was barely shouldering the heavy responsibility and had no strength to break free from the spider silk's bindings.

Fate Gu's spider silk constricted tightly, forming blood wounds everywhere on Ren Zu's body.

Ren Zu shouted: "What is going on?"

Cognition Gu explained: "Oh human, the more freedom you experience, the more you will feel the restriction around you."

Freedom Gu laughed: "Just let me go, the longer you hold on to me, the more spider silk will bind you, the binding will become tighter and will even constrict you to death!"

Ren Zu shook his head: "No, I won't let go, oh freedom Gu, I must have you!"

Countless spider silk pierced into Ren Zu's flesh, Ren Zu howled in pain and rolled on the ground but did not let go.

"Hahaha!" Ren Zu began laughing foolishly again: "I can sense a Gu far away. Just this feeling alone makes me happy and satisfied."

Cognition Gu admitted frankly: "That is natural. Whoever obtains freedom Gu will also be able to sense the location of happiness Gu."

Ren Zu continued to persevere, he cried in pain at times and laughed happily at other times. The spider silk constricted tightly, tearing into his bones and leaving deep marks on them, but Ren Zu still did not loosen his hands.

In the end, he fainted from the pain.

After a long time, he slowly woke up.

Fate Gu's spider silk was no longer constricting him, responsibility Gu also did not exert heavy pressure, while cognition Gu had disappeared.

"Wait, what about freedom Gu?" Ren Zu did not sense freedom Gu's existence, and in his moment of panic, he opened his hands.

The moment a gap appeared, freedom Gu flew away and left Ren Zu behind.

Humans often did not understand freedom when they possessed it, only after losing it, they would come to a sudden realization.

Ren Zu was stunned when he saw freedom Gu flying away, he remembered the advice of the birds, leopards, and fish, he felt extremely regretful.

He tore out his hair painfully and rolled on the ground.

"I am better off dead." Ren Zu was overwhelmed with grief: "I would rather lose love, I would rather lose my life, I don't want to lose freedom!"

Chapter 1955: Crucial Person at the Crucial Time

In Heavenly Court's battlefield, be they enemies or allies, everyone's gazes were gathered at one place!

Fang Yuan looked around him, he was surrounded by the three giant monsters. But the three giant monsters did not do anything to him, they were instead guarding him and looking at the surroundings with hostility, their affiliation could be seen with one glance.

"Reckless Savage Demon Venerable..." Fang Yuan's expression was one of shock.

"Even if Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method is helping you, you will still be defeated!!" Duke Long shouted, his voice resounding throughout the surroundings. He swooped down from the air like a red meteor, his determination did not waver even in front of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method — He was going to exterminate all demons, he would quell all opposition in the world!

Immortal killer move — Qi Breath Mountain.

Duke Long's palms aimed at Fang Yuan from afar and pushed.

Rumble!

With a loud sound, a giant qi mountain pressed down towards Fang Yuan and the three monsters.

Through triple qi retraction, Duke Long had a massive amount of qi path dao marks. Right now, all his qi path killer moves like qi breath mountain had their power amplified by countless times.

This qi mountain was much larger than before, its composition was also extremely solid. Be it in quality or quantity, both had a breakthrough!

Seeing this scene, whether it was Wu Yong, Bing Sai Chuan or others, they all revealed solemn expressions.

Just this qi breath mountain was difficult to resist, the best method was to dodge. But after qi breath mountain, there was a monstrous expert like Duke Long who could block all escape routes!

Fang Yuan clenched his teeth and was about to move.

But right at this moment, one of the three monsters transformed from the blood skins, the giant blue leopard, suddenly opened its mouth and took a deep breath.

Boom.

The whole qi breath mountain shrank rapidly and was absorbed by some formless force into the blue leopard's belly!

The immortals were given a great shock, food path cultivator Zhao Shan He's pupils shrank as he saw signs of food path from the blue leopard's body.

Even Duke Long was stunned.

This powerful qi breath mountain was actually broken this directly.

After the blue leopard swallowed the qi breath mountain, its shriveled belly bulged by ten percent. Its eyes glistened as it stared at Duke Long with a chilling gaze like it was looking at a luxurious dinner!

Duke Long was utterly fearless, the three monsters might be unfathomable, but he still charged towards Fang Yuan. His speed even increased, bursting the air and producing sonic booms.

Fang Yuan was fully prepared for combat when one of the three monsters, the green fish, moved.

It only waved its tail slightly when it appeared before Duke Long all of a sudden. Its speed was so fast that it looked like instant teleportation, but it did not feel abrupt at all, everything happened smoothly and fluidly!

Duke Long's field of vision had been wide a second ago, but now, his whole sight was filled with the enormous body of the fish monster.

The fish monster slammed its head fiercely.

Boom!

The monster's head directly sent Duke Long flying with speed that was faster than earlier when he arrived.

He possessed transformation path and qi path dao marks, he was unprecedentedly strong. After using triple qi retraction several times, he did not even need nine dragons protection to guard against ordinary rank eight attacks! But when he knocked into the fish monster's head, he felt like he had used his bare fist to strike a boulder!

In an instant, all the bones in Duke Long's body shattered, his internal organs almost burst from the force, there were massive amounts of internal and external bleeding.

"Triple qi retraction!" Duke Long shouted, his sharply declining qi surged immediately.

Duke Long immediately activated qi path healing methods, and with shocking speed, his injuries recovered in a few breaths of time.

But because he chose to heal himself, he let himself crash through all the way, directly crashing into the boundary of Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court was a shared grotto-heaven, its limits were the aperture walls. Duke Long crashed into the aperture walls, the enormous force that still remained in his body poured into the aperture walls in the sky.

The immortals heard a loud collision, then they saw several cracks suddenly appearing in the sky behind Duke Long before quickly spreading like a spider web.

The immortals could not help but draw in sharp breaths.

The strength of the fish monster's attack was simply unimaginable! Even Duke Long seemed to be unable to resist it.

And the fish monster was only an arrangement left behind by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, it had already existed for over a million years but it still had such might.

If so, how much strength did Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, who left this method, have?

Simply unimaginable!

The immortals recalled the evaluation about Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, he was publicly recognized as the venerable with the highest physical strength.

And now they saw this sight, it was truly so!

"This is Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method!"

"We have not lost yet, we can still fight."

"Lord Duke Long has returned, his injuries have recovered and his aura has become even stronger!"

"What are you afraid of? We have the fully repaired fate Gu, the heavenly fate sides with us!"

The three regions' Gu Immortals felt shocked and exulted at the unexpected reinforcements of three powerful beings, and their morale soared. Heavenly Court's immortals similarly had a high morale, they had complete confidence in fate Gu and Duke Long.

Duke Long once again swooped in and fought with the three monsters. But he learned his lesson this time and prioritized using qi path's long range attacks, avoiding close combat.

These three giant monsters' strength was truly horrifying, even Duke Long did not want to be sent flying so miserably again.

His battle tactic was wise, the three giant monsters had terrifying strength but they had almost no methods.

After exchanging a dozen or so moves, Duke Long got a clearer understanding of them.

The six legged yellow bird's speed was extremely fast and could shoot out yellow lightning from its mouth, but it was unable to fly. Its beak was extremely hard and sharp, even able to pierce through Immortal Gu Houses.

The green fish monster could float around with speed that was akin to teleportation of space path, it appeared extremely seamlessly and caught enemies off-guard. It could recover from any attacks almost instantaneously. Its strongest aspect was this — a horrifying regeneration rate that was much stronger than Duke Long using his qi path healing methods. But it had a weakness, its attack was fierce but the tempo was slow, the frequency of attacks was also quite low. After attacking once, it would be still for a while before it could attack again.

As for the toothless blue leopard, it could fly by stepping on air. Its strongest method was to devour all attacks. Not only this, it could even devour the heroes among people killer move from Gu Immortals' bodies. This sight made Zhao Shan He feel dazzled. His food path methods were far from being able to devour amplifications, this contained food path profundities that he did not possess. If he could comprehend this, his enlightenment of food path would definitely progress one step further!

At the same time, the toothless blue leopard's greatest weakness was also this almost innate devouring ability. Every time it devoured, its belly would bulge. After Duke Long and others intentionally fed it various attacks, the toothless blue leopard's belly had become round and full, it started having trouble moving.

However, even though Heavenly Court's side had probed the three monsters' details, they still could not defend against them and were gradually falling into a disadvantage.

The three monsters had flaws, their strengths and weaknesses were extremely conspicuous. But no one dared to block their brutish rampage.

Adding in Fang Yuan, Wu Yong, Bing Sai Chuan, Shen Cong Sheng, Song Qi Yuan, and the rest supporting from the side, as well as restraining and getting rid of Heavenly Court's various methods, Heavenly Court's side was in a passive situation.

The three monsters' target was Heaven Overseeing Tower, they seemed to have an enormous hatred towards fate Gu.

Heaven Overseeing Tower did not dare to confront the three monsters' power, it could only retreat constantly. To defend Heaven Overseeing Tower, Duke Long shouldered huge pressure and was heavily injured time and time again, retreating to heal his injuries before joining the battle again. His purple hair was swaying wildly, his eyes were bloodshot, his whole body was bathed in blood that dyed his scales completely! His fighting spirit kept on rising, it had not fallen once.

Both sides fought around the three monsters and Heaven Overseeing Tower. The attacks went back and forth, it was highly intense. The battle kept on moving, wherever it went, the aftermath of the terrifying killer moves destroyed everything, creating countless ruins. The great Heavenly Court that was managed meticulously by Gu Immortals was heavily damaged from this battle.

Just as the three regions' Gu Immortals were firmly holding onto the upper hand, Heaven Overseeing Tower suddenly stopped.

At the next moment, immortal killer move fate vanquish burst out again.

"Careful!" Wu Yong shouted. The three regions' Gu Immortals were already on guard and reacted quickly.

After the white light dissipated, explosions resounded in Heavenly Court battlefield once again as the battle resumed.

But this time, Heavenly Court held the momentum. The three regions' Gu Immortals could only defend while repairing the Immortal Gu Houses' and their own injuries.

The three regions' Gu Immortals gradually found their footing. Compared to the first fate vanquish attack, their situation was much better. The reason was that they had three giant monsters to rely on.

The giant monsters rampaged around the battlefield, under their attacks, Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were gradually dragged into a stalemate before being suppressed by the three regions' Gu Immortals again.

At this time, Heaven Overseeing Tower activated fate vanquish again.

After this happened over and over again, the whole of Heavenly Court was filled with ruins.

The three monsters' aura had clearly fallen, the Gu Immortals' offense was also not as fierce as before. They were at a point where they had to consider the issue of immortal essence expenditure.

"Damn it, the situation is becoming increasingly bad." Wu Yong's face was solemn, the three monsters were weakening from the repeated devastation of fate vanquish

"Back then, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable failed in his invasion of Heavenly Court, these three giant monsters are only arrangements left by him, they naturally won't be able to resist the power of fate vanquish!" Bing Sai Chuan's heart was turning cold.

If the three regions' Gu Immortals failed to obtain a breakthrough when the three monsters were still active, they would definitely suffer a miserable and disastrous defeat after that.

This was something extremely obvious!

But Heavenly Court's side used the wisest battle tactic. They moved continuously while avoiding the enemy's attacks, making the enemy expend more energy. Especially, when fate vanquish activated, the advantage the three regions' Gu Immortals obtained with difficulty turned into nothing, everything went back to square one.

And because they had Demon Judgment Board and Heaven Overseeing Tower, there was always a base camp around the front lines. The moment the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals faced danger, they could hide inside, thus there were no casualties. Naturally, this was also because the offense had weakened as both sides were beginning to conserve immortal essence.

"Master, the situation does not look good. Even Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method cannot change the outcome. The current Heavenly Court has an intact fate Gu after all." Far away, Fairy Zi Wei was analyzing coolly.

Spectral Soul had already recovered his human form but his body was translucent. He held his hands behind his back as he observed the battlefield before glancing at the far away Imperfection Regret Pavilion.

Inside Imperfection Regret Pavilion, the two venerables' silhouettes were still playing chess.

The chessboard was already filled with chess pieces, but the mysterious thing was whenever the venerable silhouette put down a piece, there would always be another free spot.

However, compared to before, the frequency of the two venerables placing the chess pieces had reduced by a lot.

Star Constellation's silhouette held a chess piece and looked at the chessboard before glancing towards Spectral Soul's direction.

"Are you okay with this? Spectral Soul stole a portion of the results of our game." Star Constellation's silhouette said.

Limitless' silhouette laughed: "Since he could get free and even steal our results, this is his own capability. These gains will help him, I am looking forward to the day when he can reach the realm that we were unable to reach."

Star Constellation's silhouette was silent for a while before sighing: "You are truly a pure Dao pursuer."

"Unfortunately, heaven and earth is a cage that stopped me from pursuing my Dao." Limitless' silhouette said: "Which is why I want to pursue freedom."

Star Constellation's silhouette immediately refuted: "Your freedom, however, will break this cage. And we both know what kind of scenery exists outside this cage!"

Limitless' silhouette shook his head: "Our positions are different, saying anything else is of no benefit."

His silhouette was becoming increasingly illusory right now, only his eyes were still bright and letting out sharp lights. Limitless' silhouette held a chess piece and looked at the chessboard for a long while, but he did not place the piece.

This match had already reached the most crucial point.

On the chessboard, Limitless' silhouette's situation was very bad, he was greatly disadvantaged. His pieces were surrounded from every direction by Star Constellation's silhouette's chess pieces, she had an obvious superiority.

Even though it was because of Heavenly Court's accumulations, it was enough for Limitless' silhouette to see the strength of his opponent, Star Constellation.

Star Constellation's will was resisting heaven's will on one hand, while also making arrangements throughout the five regions, she thought of countless aspects, her plans spanned across the past and present, throughout the universe. Forget about the arrangements that made three venerables' invasions fail, just look at the current situation, Spectral Soul had regained freedom but did not obtain the Door of Life and Death.

This was probably Star Constellation's ploy, even Fairy Zi Wei was in the dark, which was not likely to happen with just Duke Long's scheming ability.

Indeed, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was worthy of being the only wisdom path venerable in history!

However, Limitless' silhouette had not lost yet. His main chess pieces were all gathered together, the opponent could hardly defeat them. A forceful attack would definitely result in heavy losses, and it would also give the initiative to Limitless' silhouette instead.

But for Limitless' silhouette to counterattack and break through by himself, he was still lacking some strength. The whole encirclement was a dense congregation of the plans of Star Constellation's silhouette, if Limitless' silhouette attacked rashly, he would fall into a trap.

Thus, Limitless' silhouette could only choose to defend while waiting for reinforcement.

This game between two venerables that had started in the Olden Antiquity Era and continued for a million years, it had finally welcomed the most crucial moment!

Indeed, Limitless' silhouette still had reinforcements.

He had waited for a million years for this aid, both sides were aware of it.

"Now, we have to see the quality of our pieces." Star Constellation's silhouette swept her gaze through the battlefield, when it stopped at Fang Yuan's body, her gaze revealed complicated expressions.

Limitless' silhouette was similarly looking in the same direction, mumbling: "Oh Fang Yuan, you have been like this since the start. You... how long are you planning to conceal your abilities?"

Chapter 1956: A Man Must Be Cool!

Fang Yuan had all along been fighting on the front lines.

On one hand, he had been fighting with Duke Long and the rest, on the other hand, he kept on maintaining a cold and indifferent expression while pondering about the overall situation.

But ever since Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method activated, he had an extra voice resounding in his ears.

"Have a good look, junior! The three monsters in front of you were transformed from my three immortal moves. These three immortal moves were created from the insights I gained after reading 'Pursuing Freedom' in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, they were all created to pursue freedom."

"First move — Thunder Rush Yellow Bird Transformation, it uses attitude Gu as the core. Have you ever envied birds and wanted to fly freely in the sky? However, we humans are restricted since birth, we don't have wings, why even talk about flying? But an even crueler situation is like the wingless birds, they already experienced the wonderful feeling of flying but they lost their wings. No matter who you are, where you are, you will face all sorts of limitations. If we are unable to change, unable to break away from all these, we will be like wingless birds, pursuing freedom but unable to catch it, what should we do then?"

"This is the core concept of this move, remember it, junior. Even if we face the strictest restrictions and are unable to pursue freedom, we still have a kind of freedom, we can freely choose what kind of attitude we use to face the cruel reality. Remember, your attitude is very important!"

"Second move — Devouring Blue Leopard Transformation, it uses mutation Gu as the core. Freedom is not a bad thing, but it is also not a good thing either. It can make you better and can also make you worse, just like the effect of mutation Gu. The fierce beast lacks teeth, but does that mean it can't live on? If it does not have the freedom to bite, what's the harm in devouring the food? Maybe it can even train your digestive system to become stronger."

"Third move — Internal Breathing Green Fish Transformation, it uses adaptation Gu as the core. Compared to it, how ugly does the world seem? We are assaulted by cruel facts, we are tormented by pain and hopelessness. When we are walking our respective paths, we will be covered in bruises sometimes, even being exposed with nowhere to escape. Humans change, the world is also going through countless changes, if we cannot keep up with the changes of time, we will be left behind by the whole world. Therefore, adaptation is key. If you don't have gills, use your mouth to breath; if you don't even have a mouth, then create a self-circulating internal respiratory system. Even if that means you have to walk slowly, even if you become nothing like a human in the end."

The voice was powerful and forceful as it explained the origins and details of the three monsters. These monsters were transformed from three transformation path killer moves left behind by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable.

After Fang Yuan triggered Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's method, this voice had peculiarly accompanied Fang Yuan, but no one else could detect it.

"Is this Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's voice?" Just as Fang Yuan was guessing, the voice changed.

From the stable and serious voice to a lively and flippant tone.

"Hey, you have already spoken so much, it's my turn, it's my turn!"

"Haha, kid, no matter who you are, you are definitely an otherworldly demon. Because only an otherworldly demon has hope of destroying fate Gu. So, when I left behind this true inheritance back then, I made it so that only an otherworldly demon can inherit it."

"But besides this, you still need to possess at least one of three Gu worms - attitude Gu, mutation Gu, and adaptation Gu. These three Gu worms correspond to three killer moves that can trigger my killer moves. When you arrive in the sky above Embroidered Tower, you can summon the giant monsters transformed by the killer moves and they shall be your strongest helping hand."

"Use them however you please, kill or loot if you like, or help people if you wish to. Of course, the best use would be to destroy fate Gu because seeing it really annoys me. Hahaha!"

"Of course, if you can trigger all three moves, then you can merge them into one move! This is a super, super, super powerful killer move that I created with great effort!"

"Once you grasp this move, you can use your human form to possess all the advantages of the three moves, moreover, there is no weakness in any aspect. That means, you will be like the wingless bird, moving as fast as lightning and shooting out lightning. You will also be like the gill-less fish, possessing extremely powerful regeneration ability. You will be like the toothless beast as well, devouring everything and storing them into your stomach."

"Are you stupefied? Isn't it super amazing? Hahaha, come, bow before me!"

The flippant male voice spoke until here, when it seemed like it was kicked out and was replaced by the previous solemn male voice.

"The final combination move is called incomplete freedom transformation, it has three cores - Attitude, Mutation, and Adaptation. It has numerous steps and is highly complicated. Although you can use the three monsters to merge them into one, which is much easier than you using them independently, I still ask you to not attempt it lightly. Because this move's effect works on your body, if it fails, you will be heavily injured at best, or even die in severe cases. Bear this in mind, bear this in mind!"

The heavy and solemn voice spoke earnestly, but soon, the previous flippant voice replaced it.

"Please, what you said is not important at all! Kid, let me tell you the important point! Once you activate this move successfully, you will have the strength to suppress all immemorial desolate plants and immemorial desolate beasts, the three monsters' methods will become your innate abilities. You will become a human shaped beast that can battle through heaven and earth, rampaging around all over the world unhindered! You will immediately possess quasi venerable battle strength!"

"Of course, if you meet an old venerable like me, you will still kneel in the end."

"But these are not the most important points. There is one most crucial point, you must remember it."

Fang Yuan could not help but concentrate as he heard this.

He then heard that flippant and lively voice continue: "The most important part of the most important thing is once you activate this move, the three monsters will combine into a bloody cape and will hang on your back. This cape is truly... super cool! Junior, you must try it, it is really too stunning, you absolutely won't regret it!"

Fang Yuan was speechless.

Following the voice, all kinds of information flowed in his mind, allowing him to understand all the contents of the three killer moves clearly.

Different from what the voice described, these three killer moves and the combination move were not complex at all and their steps were also not numerous.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable lived in the Olden Antiquity Era after all, Gu cultivation styles were not overwhelming and were crude back then, unlike the present age's delicate complexity.

It was not difficult to master these killer moves, especially for Fang Yuan who possessed deep wisdom path attainment.

"So, I should combine it like this..." Fang Yuan's thoughts finished as he suddenly retreated and activated a killer move.

In an instant, the three monsters that were fighting at the front lines turned into three light rays - yellow, blue, green - and entered Fang Yuan's body.

Such a strange change caught both sides unprepared.

The three lights covered Fang Yuan, emitting a majestic aura that spread in all directions and repelled all beings and objects.

The three lights merged quickly and turned blood red.

The blood red light suddenly condensed into one and covered Fang Yuan's back, turning into a large blood red cape.

The cape fluttered with the wind like a war banner; the fluttering sounds echoed in every person's ears.

"What change occurred again?"

"It seems like Fang Yuan inherited Reckless Savage true inheritance?!"

Both allies and enemies were shocked once again.

Looking at this familiar cape, inside Imperfection Regret Pavilion, Star Constellation's silhouette recalled past memories.

A million years ago, a man charged into Heavenly Court.

He walked step by step, the ordinary steps, however, shook the land and sky of Heavenly Court.

He was clothed in beast skin, his body was extremely robust with muscles bursting out. Tattoos covered all the skin on his body, portraying countless beasts and plants of all shapes and sizes, some were vicious beasts, some were smart and exquisite life forms.

The aura he released was as lofty as mountains and as vast as oceans. The Heavenly Court immortals only took one look at him and felt a suffocating pressure.

He was wearing a cape. This beast skin cape was extremely wide and was sewn using human skins. It suited a large physique like Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's, if this were an ordinary person, a large portion of the cape would be dragging on the ground.

Every time Reckless Savage Demon Venerable killed a rank eight enemy, he would peel their skin and sew onto the beast skin cape. This was the custom of the beastman race, but Reckless Savage had learned and imitated it in his youth, before he became a venerable.

An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth!

Halfway through Heavenly Court, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable stopped in front of Embroidered Tower.

In the air, Star Constellation's will manifested: "Reckless Savage, you cannot destroy fate Gu. Your strength originates from your fate. It is like how you cannot lift yourself up without relying on other methods."

"Of course I know this." Reckless Savage Demon Venerable laughed.

"Then what did you come for?"

"To fight!" Reckless Savage Demon Venerable raised his head and said it as a matter of fact with a flippant voice.

Star Constellation's will: "..."

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable continued to laugh: "After becoming venerable and being invincible in the world, I felt an intense loneliness! No one could fight with me, I have killed almost all those variant human rank eights, the old and weak ones that are still alive have all hidden themselves. I also don't have the interest to find them. Looking at the five regions, only Heavenly Court is somewhat interesting. To protect fate Gu, you guys must have left behind many methods. Even Limitless was stopped by you back then. Come, use all your methods, let us have a match."

Star Constellation's will was silent for a long while before entering Embroidered Tower: "This Immortal Gu House in front of you is one of the methods my main body left behind."

"Roar!" Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's eyes brightened: "If so, I am attacking!"

The battle ended quickly.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable clenched his fists and licked his lips, mumbling unsatisfied: "What is this, after just two or three moves, your Embroidered Tower is almost on the verge of collapse. But the start was pretty good. Relax, I won't destroy your tower, we are all humans after all."

"Also, I will leave behind these three bloody skins. This is my inheritance!"

"No matter who, even if it is someone from your Heavenly Court, if they can inherit my inheritance, then it shall belong to them."

"Treat it as a memento of my visit to Heavenly Court. Don't dismantle it, hehehe."

"I am really looking forward to it. I wonder which junior will obtain my inheritance, will they be shaken by my grand strength, or be bowled over by my incredible thinking?"

"Haha, it naturally is best for this junior to destroy fate Gu. If they can't do this, I will truly be displeased!"

Star Constellation's will was silent for a long while before speaking: "So your intention is to destroy fate Gu."

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable shrugged his shoulders: "That goes without saying. I have left my bloody skins here, if you have the skill, then destroy them! But I will leave you some kind advice, these three bloody skins are already connected with Heavenly Court's dao marks. If you attack them recklessly, it will be the most direct attack towards Heavenly Court. Unless there is someone who has transformation path attainment rivaling mine, no one will be able to safely dismantle it."

Star Constellation's will spoke: "There is a better way for you to destroy fate Gu, be an Immortal Venerable, become the Lord of Heavenly Court and be in contact with fate Gu all the time. I think with your wisdom, you will definitely think of a way to destroy fate Gu."

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable directly shook his head without even thinking: "I don't want to!"

Star Constellation's will frowned: "Why?"

"Because the title of Demon Venerable sounds much cooler than Immortal Venerable!"

Star Constellation's will: "..."

It was strange, when Reckless Savage Demon Venerable said this reason, it actually gave off a feeling of being a natural fact.

Reckless Savage Demon Venerable turned around and looked at himself before waving his arms: "Take a good look!"

"Look at my thighs, they are so sturdy. Look at my arms, they are so muscular and well-defined."

"This is beauty, this is coolness!"

"And this cape, it is so bloody, it is also created from human skins, how domineering is it!"

Star Constellation's will was unable to think properly for a moment, it could only respond after a good while: "So, you created this cape not for payback and revenge against variant humans?"

"Of course, there is the secondary reason, but the important thing is still its coolness!"

Star Constellation's will: "..."

"Oh oh, right. These three bloody skins can combine into one move and its form is a bloody cape. It is quite similar to the one I use now. If there is a junior who wears it in the future, they will definitely be extremely cool beyond belief!"

"Men!" Reckless Savage Demon Venerable raised his arms and bent his elbows, showing his bulging muscles and praising himself: "Must be this cool."

Chapter 1957: Final Showdown

Because of the change in Fang Yuan's body, the fight in the battlefield had paused temporarily.

Duke Long was the first to react.

Immortal killer move — Spiraling Dragon Fang!

Fang Yuan's condition was unknown, the three monsters actually transformed into a blood-soaked cape that hung on his back. Duke Long did not dare to be overconfident, he still had apprehension from the attacks of the three monsters, so he used a long range attack, spiraling dragon fangs, to probe.

Dragon fangs, sharp as blades, danced in the air. Fang Yuan did not dodge, he wanted to test his current defensive strength.

Chink chink chink!

Dragon fangs slashed his body, producing a series of sparks. After wearing the bloody cape, Fang Yuan's defensive strength had increased to an outrageous level.

Duke Long's pupils shrank at this sight.

Fang Yuan's current defensive strength was already much higher than his, there were at least white marks left behind on Duke Long's dragon scales if he let the dragon fangs strike him. But there was no damage to Fang Yuan, not even a trace of marks or wounds could be seen.

"The defensive strength is so astonishing, other aspects should also be similar." Looking at how Fang Yuan dealt with the dragon fang killer move, the immortals had such thoughts.

Heavenly Court's side was very wary, while the three regions' Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan with eager anticipation.

These Gu Immortals did not know that Fang Yuan's ears were ringing with criticism at this moment: "Kid, you are the junior who inherited my true inheritance? Damn it, you look really ugly! Look at yourself, your face is like a woman's, your arms and legs are so thin. How can your skin be so white and smooth? Where is your toughness as a man? Heavens! My inheritance is wasted in your hands."

Fang Yuan: "..."

During the process of combining the three monsters into incomplete freedom transformation, Fang Yuan needed to transfer his own will. However, after the bloody cape formed, Fang Yuan's will transformed into Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's image, turning into Reckless Savage's will!

This method was truly inconceivable! This showed that Reckless Savage might be a transformation path Gu Immortal but he also had an astonishing attainment in wisdom path.

However, Fang Yuan soon discovered that the source of the will transformation were the three monsters. As far as he was concerned, the so-called 'Reckless Savage's will' possessed no harm to him but had many benefits instead.

Reckless Savage's will could attend to the bloody cape and help maintain the killer move, he could even quicken Fang Yuan's understanding of the true meaning behind incomplete freedom transformation!

"Kid, make a move quickly. After so many years, there is not much left of the strength left behind by my main body. Quick, quick, charge, destroy fate Gu!" Reckless Savage's will laughed loudly as he clamored in impatience.

"You talk too much, can you shut up?" Fang Yuan replied indifferently.

"Eh!" Reckless Savage's will was stunned, he placed his hands on his cheeks and shouted in disbelief: "I was scorned upon! I, the great Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, was actually scorned by a junior! And by such an ugly guy at that!!"

Reckless Savage's will kept on mumbling. Who could have expected the domineering Reckless Savage Demon Venerable to be such a chatterbox?!

Even without his reminder, Fang Yuan could sense that although incomplete freedom transformation was terrifyingly powerful, it consumed the foundation of the three monsters very quickly.

This move had a time limit.

"Since that is the case..." Fang Yuan squinted, looking at Heaven Overseeing Tower wickedly.

At that instant, every Heavenly Court Gu Immortal controlling Heaven Overseeing Tower felt a chill in their hearts!

"Be careful of Fang Yuan!"

"He is attacking!!"

"Steady, steady!"

Heavenly Court's side was tense, their nerves stretched to the limits.

Boom!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan attacked. His figure crossed the sky like a bloody ray, he was directly charging towards the area with the most enemies — Heaven Overseeing Tower!

Fang Yuan's speed was so astonishing that even Duke Long, who was already fully prepared, felt a great shock.

"Fang Yuan, stop!" Duke Long reacted and chased with all his strength.

"Hehehe, it is finally getting interesting." On the edge of the battlefield, Spectral Soul laughed loudly and commanded: "Old Man Zheng Yuan, start, activate everybody's vision. I want everyone in the world to see this interesting sight."

"Yes, master." Old Man Zheng Yuan was a key that held the authority to activate Heavenly Court's venerable human path methods.

And this move, everybody's vision, was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable. Its unique power had been shown in Fang Yuan's previous life.

It used people's united hearts as the foundation and could let Central Continent's mortals, Gu Masters, and Gu Immortals share their vision. As such, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals could observe all the enemy activities in Central Continent and could even stimulate the hatred of Central Continent's people, gathering even more human will.

The more human will they accumulated, the more power the other human path killer moves like heroes among people would possess. In such a feedback loop, their strength would keep on growing stronger, this was the style that Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's killer moves had.

Immortal killer move — Everybody's Vision!

In an instant, Central Continent was in an uproar, the five regions were in an uproar.

"What in the world is going on?"

"My eyes, my eyes have a problem!"

Mortals were shocked.

"It is the scene in Heavenly Court, what kind of method is this, it can allow everyone to witness the current situation!"

"Which side has the upper hand?"

Almost all the Gu Immortals of the five regions knew the inside story.

In the previous life, Central Continent's people enjoyed the effects of everybody's vision, but in this life, because of Shen Shang's interference, human wills of the five regions were gathered together.

Because of this, everybody's vision allowed everyone in the five regions to observe the battle in Heavenly Court.

The first scene the five regions' mortals saw was Fang Yuan fighting his way to Heaven Overseeing Tower!

"Who is that person?" Even ordinary mortals felt intense suffocation when they saw Fang Yuan's overbearing aura.

"Fang Yuan, you won't succeed!" At the crucial moment, Gu Yue Fang Zheng and Qin Ding Ling controlled Demon Judgment Board to defend in front of Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"That is the rank eight Immortal Gu House — Demon Judgment Board!" The Gu Immortals who saw this scene, no matter which region they belonged to, cried out in shock.

"Fang Yuan is not stopping, he is charging right into Demon Judgment Board!"

"Has he gone crazy?"

"This is a rank eight Immortal Gu House."

However, at the next moment, the mouths of the five regions' Gu Immortals opened wide in shock.

Fang Yuan directly collided into Demon Judgment Board.

The enormous collision force sent Demon Judgment Board flying, even though Gu Yue Fang Zheng and Qin Ding Ling were already controlling the Immortal Gu House with all their strength.

"Get lost!" Fang Yuan shouted as he punched with great force.

A huge dent appeared on Demon Judgment Board, countless fragments scattered and turned into Gu worm corpses.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng coughed out a large mouthful of blood and fell on the ground with a horrified expression on his face. Fang Yuan's punch had almost pierced Demon Judgment Board!

After Demon Judgment Board was knocked down, Fang Yuan stomped it fiercely, an enormous and irresistible force pressed down on Demon Judgment Board like a mountain and it rapidly fell to the ground.

Fang Yuan jumped, his speed increasing as he continued charging towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

But the next moment, Duke Long had already caught up to Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan!" He shouted wildly, his voice shaking the skies.

Fang Yuan turned around, his bloody cape swung and he started punching, creating a storm of fist shadows!

Duke Long had come prepared with a killer move, his palm pressed, it was qi breath mountain.

His left hand then formed into a claw shape as he activated immortal killer move dragon claw strike, while his right hand clenched into fist and activated chaotic dragon fist. At the same time, he spat his fangs, they turned into countless spiraling dragon fangs which moved around his body. The dragon images of nine dragons protection on his body floated out on their own initiative.

Bam Bam Bam Bam...

Fang Yuan and Duke Long fought fiercely, exchanging blows with each fist hitting raw flesh.

On one side was an inheritor of various venerables, an otherworldly demon, on the other side was a Dao Guardian, master of an Immortal Venerable. Their fight had broken the record of intensity in this battle so far!

Just the aftermath of their moves resulted in wild winds that pushed away all the people and objects. The terrifying collisions could directly destroy Immortal Gu Houses. Even rank eight Immortal Gu Houses like Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and Calamity Luck Altar stopped fighting. Those rank eight Immortal Gu Houses even retreated far away.

"Are these two monsters?"

"What kind of terrifying fight is this!"

The five regions' Gu Immortals saw this scene through everybody's vision, they gulped as their hearts pounded wildly.

In the absence of a venerable, Fang Yuan and Duke Long's fight could be considered to be at the peak level of the current world!

Mortals gradually began to realize something.

"This is incredible! We are looking at immortals!"

"This world really has immortals!"

"Fights of immortals really are too terrifying. Look quickly, even the heavens seem to have been broken by them."

Mortals exclaimed in shock, the scene had far surpassed the limits of their imagination.

The storm of attacks did not stop, both sides were in a deadlock.

Duke Long could not receive amplification from heroes among people, but he had heavenly dragon's last stand and destiny song's help, as well as triple qi retraction. This method was an arrangement left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, Duke Long was only a key to activating it.

At the edge of the battlefield, Spectral Soul smiled as he looked at Fang Yuan and Duke Long's battle: "Since it has already reached this stage, then let me push it further. Zheng Yuan, release all the human wills."

Old Man Zheng Yuan was dazed, weren't the human wills already released completely, were there any remaining? If there were, wouldn't Old Man Zheng Yuan have used them before?

However, Spectral Soul pointed towards a direction, Old Man Zheng Yuan astonishingly discovered there truly was a portion of human will stored in a corner of Heavenly Court.

Spectral Soul's understanding of Heavenly Court was actually clearer than Old Man Zheng Yuan himself!

'How many secrets of Heavenly Court does he grasp? Also, why would the past venerables retain a portion of the human will so secretly?' Old Man Zheng Yuan was filled with questions.

"You don't need to guess, just release them. What happens next will give you your answer." Spectral Soul chuckled.

Old Man Zheng Yuan had already submitted to Spectral Soul completely, he immediately nodded and activated his methods with no hesitation.

The human wills were released completely!

At the next moment, the power of heroes among people soared.

Chapter 1958: Complete Human Will

The moment the human wills were released, both sides' Gu Immortals seemed to hear whispers of countless people.

"You must grow up healthily, my children."

"Lovers being able to be married is truly a great thing."

"May peace last for generations and generations. I'd rather be a dog living in peace than a person living in chaotic times!"

"Kill these lawless people, place judgment upon these atrocious evil-doers!"

"The righteous path will definitely be victorious."

"I believe that fairness and justice might come late sometimes, but they will never be absent."

"You must win, Heavenly Court. I can't do anything, but I can pray for you."

The morale of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals soared, but soon, doubts surfaced on their faces.

Their enemies similarly received amplifications, moreover, it seemed like the three regions' Gu Immortals received a slightly stronger amplification than them?

"Kill those righteous path hypocrites!"

"Destroy Heavenly Court, it sits in an ivory tower, who knows how many generations of Central Continent's people it has exploited!!"

"Although I respect Heavenly Court's spirit, I will never be able to achieve it. I am a Central Continent Gu Immortal, I admit my selfishness, I am only an ordinary Gu cultivator. However, Central Continent's resources are plundered and occupied by the ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court. Join Heavenly Court? That is too difficult. They even want me to offer my immortal aperture! How can I be willing to do that?"

"Bring down Heavenly Court, the more losses Heavenly Court suffers, the less the pressure on our four regions when the five regions merge."

"Heavenly Court has occupied the throne of the number one force for far too long. If it is overthrown, hehe, this will be interesting!"

...

Both sides fought once again, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were astonished to discover that heroes among people's effect on the enemies was indeed stronger than themselves.

Why?

Heroes among people is clearly our Heavenly Court's method!

Why was heroes among people helping the enemies more?!

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were bewildered as they began to fall into a disadvantage.

Wu Yong led his alliance once again, he was the first to charge out of Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and began to valiantly pave a way through battle. At this moment, he fully displayed the prestige and courage of Southern Border's Wu clan!

His face was solemn and his eyes flickered with cold lights. The determination to destroy fate Gu had always been so intense and overwhelming!

In the past...

He stood in front of his mother Wu Du Xiu's coffin, mourning in silence.

While he felt pain, he found there was a feeling of release and delight in the depths of his heart.

"Does this mean I am not filial?" Wu Yong questioned himself and slowly understood his true feelings: "No, it is not so. I am full of filial piety and respect towards my mother. But she was truly too strong, I could only choose to curl up and hide under her shadow. Now that she is gone, I finally have space to stretch myself."

Returning to the present.

Wu Yong's determination was firm and his gaze was cold, he revealed the heated emotions inside his heart!

"Therefore, be destroyed, fate Gu!"

"I will mourn for you just like I mourned for my mother."

"Only with you gone can I, Wu Yong, have the freedom to chase after my ambition!"

On the other side, Calamity Luck Altar suppressed Demon Judgment Board.

Bing Sai Chuan had never felt such power!

Blood flowed wildly inside his body.

"You still don't realize it, Qin Ding Ling! Despite the fact that you were the person sleeping beside Lord Giant Sun."

"Fate is fixed while luck is a variable. Why do you think Lord Giant Sun created luck path, why could he create luck path?"

"From a certain perspective, this is the wish of countless beings for luck path to appear! When your life is fixed, when every encounter you have is already determined, is there still any meaning in living? What difference is this from puppets or mindless zombies?"

"This is not my speculation, Lord Giant Sun said this to me personally!"

"And I inherited his will, after three hundred thousand years, I am still staking my life to fight, I am an old man who is willing to fight for such an aspiration!!"

Immortal killer move — Grand Collision!

Shen Cong Sheng actually took the initiative to attack Feng Jiu Ge.

Under Shen Cong Sheng's attacks, Feng Jiu Ge had to retreat constantly, but he kept on maintaining destiny song, prioritizing on supporting his allies.

Shen Cong Sheng roared: "Feng Jiu Ge! We are both sound path Gu Immortals, even if you can't see it, can't you hear it?"

"Listen!"

"These are the innermost voices of almost all the world's people!"

"They don't want to be shackled any more, they thirst for freedom, even if this freedom is beyond impractical! Sometimes, people are like lunatics, they have foolish thoughts."

"I will be honest with you." Shen Cong Sheng actually cried tears of deep emotions: "I have never felt such feelings. It is as if there are countless people standing behind me, cheering and encouraging me. Perhaps this is how Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals felt when they fought for humanity back then."

"It was really the right decision for me to come to this battlefield!"

Bam Bam Bam Bam...

Close combat continued, moves after moves were exchanged as Fang Yuan and Duke Long fought head-on.

After the stalemate lasted for a while, Duke Long began to fall into a disadvantaged position.

Despite Duke Long gritting his teeth and wanting to endure, it was to no avail. Right now, he started to feel a sense of weakness and helplessness despite his overwhelming determination!

Among all the people present, heroes among people's amplification on Fang Yuan was actually the strongest.

"Why? Why!? You are clearly a demon who brings disaster to the world, you are an atrocious demon who commits countless sins! Why would you receive the greatest help from the human wills?" Duke Long roared in shock and fury.

"Do you still not understand it? Duke Long! The current era is no longer the same, the hearts of the people have already changed!"

"In the Olden Antiquity Era, humanity sought for survival space. Thus, the three Demon Venerables held back when they invaded Heavenly Court."

"And now, it has already been over a million years since the Olden Antiquity Era has ended! Your Heavenly Court is unable to represent the will of all the humans in the world by now!"

Fang Yuan's words were very vicious, they seemed to be sharper than dragon fangs as they pierced into Duke Long's inner heart.

Fang Yuan used more than just his fists, every joint of his body turned into weapons as he attacked Duke Long.

Qi breath mountain was destroyed by him, spiraling dragon fangs were broken, Duke Long's dragon claw strike and chaotic dragon fist were suppressed again and again by Fang Yuan!

Bam Bam Bam Bam!

Fang Yuan's every attack produced sonic booms.

The blood cape let out a dark red radiance that covered Fang Yuan's whole body, empowering his strength in all aspects to a terrifying degree.

Duke Long's fingers were snapped by Fang Yuan, his fist fractured as he struck Fang Yuan's fist directly! The nine dragon tattoos were howling in misery! They were already destroyed to a huge degree by Fang Yuan!

...

Countless years ago, there was a couple.

The male was called Tu Ji, the female was Ruo Li.

Tu Ji was a rockman and Ruo Li was a human immortal.

"I cultivate rule path, I have to believe in the rules of this world. All things have their own ordained path of which is fate. I believe I was able to meet you because I followed my fate, falling in love with you is the kindness of fate towards me." Tu Ji replied.

Ruo Li said: "What if I told you fate decreed that I would die at Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's hands?"

"What?!" Tu Ji was shocked: "Ruo Li, how many times have you checked this prophecy?"

Ruo Li gave a bitter smile: "Only once is enough, but I checked it many times indeed, every result was the same. Do you know why a wisdom path Gu Immortal's prophecy is so accurate? That is because fate is always fixed. I will die at Reckless Savage's hands, that is my fate."

Tu Ji was silent for a long while before he said with an almost decisive tone: "Then I... do not believe in fate!"

On what basis must she die at Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's hands?

On what basis must my lover not live a happy life?

If this is fate's arrangement, then — I won't accept it!

...

Duke Long was beaten back again and again by Fang Yuan. First, blood flowed out of his mouth, then all of his seven orifices started bleeding, this was because Fang Yuan's punches had landed on his body and caused internal bleeding of his organs.

"Great! This feels really refreshing!" Reckless Savage's will shouted from inside the cape, waving his hands in excitement: "Kid, although you look ugly, your style resembles me! I have to say, my opinion of you has changed. But I wonder why I feel that there is something lacking?"

Reckless Savage's will thought for a while before clapping: "I know! You should roar in excitement, shout happily, this is the excitement of a man during battles!"

However, Fang Yuan's face was cold as ice, his eyes were dark as the abyss with no trace of needless emotions.

As far as he was concerned, he was using this style of fighting to maximize the advantage of incomplete freedom transformation, there was nothing else to it.

With the powerful strength of the three monsters, Duke Long was already in a huge disadvantage when fighting him in close combat. But Fang Yuan maintained the attitude of attacking Heaven Overseeing Tower, which forced Duke Long to fight him in close combat.

Duke Long's situation became increasingly grim, he was clearly defending more and attacking less.

He howled, he roared, but he was still forced back over and over again by Fang Yuan.

...

In Southern Border, there was a Gu Immortal called Tao Zhu.

"He is Tao Zhu?"

"Is he stupid? In order to research the pointless secret of the five regions, he gave up on that marriage!"

"He is a lunatic. I've often seen him heading to the regional walls for his research, he often ends up injured and in a sorry state."

He sacrificed almost everything to research the five regions' regional walls, he endured countless people's ridicule and even had to resist the secret oppression of many people.

The most fatal blow to him was the biggest joke that fate played on him!

Not long in the future, the five regions' regional walls would disappear completely.

Even if Tao Zhu's research made progress, it seemed to lose its meaning.

"But so what?"

"If this is fate, and I, Tao Zhu, am unable to resist or change it, so what?"

"I will still continue researching! Even if I fail in the end and obtain nothing, even if my life becomes a complete failure!"

"I will never resign myself to fate! Even if I understand there is a wall called fate in front of me, I will charge into it!"

"Even if I die from the collision, I will die with a smile and my head held high."

On what basis must I accept my fate?

Who gives a crap!

That is what I want to do!

This is how I want to live!

Chapter 1959: People's Hearts Have Changed

"Quick, reinforce Duke Long!" Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals moved, they did not dare to continue watching.

Duke Long and Feng Jiu Ge were two pillars of Heavenly Court, once Duke Long was defeated, the whole situation would again turn precarious.

Boom!

Fang Yuan suddenly kicked Duke Long's hand.

Duke Long's defense was wide open, Fang Yuan used the chance to approach closer and grabbed Duke Long's purple hair with his left hand.

Then, he raised his right fist and punched. Punches after punches landed on Duke Long's face and chest like cannonball strikes.

Duke Long was unable to free himself, he could only shout in desperation: "Triple qi retraction!"

Qi surged once again and gathered in Duke Long's body, Duke Long's condition strengthened by three times.

Bam bam bam! Fang Yuan continued to rain punches on Duke Long.

He kept on punching!

...

Over a million years ago, when Genesis Lotus became a venerable, he wandered the world disguised as a mortal.

One day, he arrived at a poor oasis village in Western Desert.

There, he helped the villagers solve some issues using a Gu Master identity, he was welcomed warmly by the young and old in the village.

A child was the most excited, even revering Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable to the point of prostrating himself.

Because he saw new hope in his life.

"Lord Gu Master, Lord Gu Master. I beg you, I beg you!" The child knelt on the ground and grabbed the hem of Genesis Lotus's cloth as he looked up towards Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, his pure eyes were filled with tears and pleading.

"Speak, child, don't kneel. I will definitely help you if I can." Genesis Lotus lifted the child warmly.

The child revealed a joyous expression: "It would be really great if you can help! Please resurrect my mother, she is my most important person and also the person who loves me the most in this world. My father abandoned us long ago. I could grow up all because she worked hard to raise me."

"But my mother died a few days ago, she died from exhaustion and illness. Even on her deathbed, she used her trembling hands to put the last half remaining biscuit in my hands, she saved it for me!"

"I cannot be without my mother!"

"I cannot be without my mother!"

"I beg you, Lord Gu Master. You could dig such a deep well and precisely find a water source. You can definitely resurrect my mother, right?!"

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was silent.

The child was innocent, he did not know resurrecting the dead was far more difficult than digging a well. But Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was the current venerable, the things that were impossible for others were possible for him.

But he could not!

He was an Immortal Venerable, he was Heavenly Court's Immortal Venerable.

Thereupon, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable rubbed the child's head and sighed: "This is not possible. No matter who it is, they will experience life and death. Your mother's death is just her reaching her final destination, isn't it a kind of release? Cheer up and live on bravely and happily , I believe your mother will definitely want you to live like that."

"No! I don't want to!" The child shook his head rapidly: "I want my mother to revive!"

Genesis Lotus shook his head and sighed again: "I cannot resurrect your mother."

"Why? You can clearly do it!" The child opened his eyes, looking at Genesis Lotus with fury.

Genesis Lotus shook his head, not speaking anymore.

The child pointed at Genesis Lotus and shouted: "I hate you, I hate you, Gu Master! You can clearly resurrect my mother, but you don't want to do it! You are too cold-blooded, you are really cruel. Is it because she is not your mother? If it were your mother, would you refuse so indifferently?"

Genesis Lotus sank into silence, he put himself in the child's place and thought, then came to a conclusion as he said with extreme sincerity: "Yes, I will still do this. Everyone needs to accept death, no matter who they are. Because I know, this is all fate's arrangements."

"To hell with your fate!" The child roared: "Do I care about your damned fate, I need my mother, I want my mother back!"

The child was quickly stopped by the nearby villagers, the villagers repeatedly apologized to Genesis Lotus.

Genesis Lotus waved his head, expressing he did not mind it.

He looked at the villagers stopping the madly struggling child when he suddenly went into a daze and his body shuddered!

At this moment, he suddenly understood.

The reason why he felt a vague unease when he traveled around the world.

Human hearts have changed, their greed is insatiable!

When humans became the rulers of the world, their desire was no longer about resisting the rule and suppression of variant humans, they had become increasingly insane and delusional.

Genesis Lotus looked at the child in front of him dazedly as he came to a realization: Weren't the humans of the present age like the child in front of him? He was struggling wildly under the shackles of fate for an impractical wish. But was it truly impractical? Was resurrecting a dead person impossible?

Genesis Lotus was aware that this was possible. But... he could not do it.

This was not allowed.

However, does not being allowed mean that there won't be anyone doing it?

Genesis Lotus suddenly felt loss and hesitation, a deep helplessness shrouded him. Even though he was a rank nine venerable, the number one person in his era!

He could stop the people from doing this with all his strength, but what about after his death?

Even if he used all his strength and energy in this life, and no one attempted to revive the dead, could he, Genesis Lotus, stop the people from having such thoughts?

The most terrifying thing were these types of thoughts!

How could he stop everyone's wishful thinking?

He could not stop the desires that emerged in people's hearts!

...

Duke Long was beaten to a pulp by Fang Yuan!

At the start, he counterattacked with all his strength, but Fang Yuan endured Duke Long's counterattacks head-on with an unchanging expression.

Duke Long's appearance was completely different now, his chest had caved in, his scales were scattered everywhere, and his aura had fallen sharply.

"Triple qi retraction!" Duke Long roared again, his aura rose and his injuries recovered immediately.

Bam bam bam! Fang Yuan still rained punches on Duke Long.

Duke Long had just recovered his features when his face was messed up by Fang Yuan once again. Soon, his bones fractured and blood flowed out from everywhere.

Duke Long did not retreat, he defended with all his strength while shouting: "Triple qi retraction!"

His condition recovered once again.

Reckless Savage's will cheered from the cape: "Beat him, beat him! Beat him hard, squeeze him dry! I want to see how much accumulation Heavenly Court has to be able to let him expend it like this! Hahaha."

But Fang Yuan was calm all along, calculating the remaining strength of the three monsters' combination.

His strength was weakening constantly.

Back when the three monsters had first appeared, the green fish was able to destroy all the bones in Duke Long's body with just one headbutt. But after many fierce battles and being struck by fate vanquish several times, the three monsters did not have much strength remaining.

Fang Yuan activated incomplete freedom transformation and combined the strength of the three monsters, but all aspects of strength like defense, movement, and healing were being expended intensely.

Comparing accumulation, it truly could not match Heavenly Court!

Endless fist shadows converged, Fang Yuan suddenly raised his fist and struck with all his strength!

Boom!!

A loud sound was heard as Fang Yuan's right fist lodged into Duke Long's face. The horrifying strength burst forth, Duke Long instantly lost consciousness and crossed the sky in a blink of an eye like a meteor before crashing heavily on the ground.

He continued to fall deeper, his strong body pierced into Heavenly Court's ground and created an unprecedentedly deep crater!

Duke Long was lying in the depths of the crater without moving. But triple qi retraction was activated once again, another round of endless qi converged into him.

Fang Yuan snorted and loosened his hand, a large handful of purple hair scattered with the wind, they were ripped out when he punched Duke Long.

Fang Yuan analyzed calmly.

Triple qi retraction was not activated by Duke Long, it was essentially a method left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable. Even if Duke Long lost his consciousness for the moment, triple qi retraction still continued to support Duke Long.

Incomplete freedom transformation did not have much strength remaining. If this killer move was stopped midway, he could not use Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's strength to activate it again. Next time he used it, Fang Yuan would have to rely on his own strength.

Duke Long had stopped temporarily, Fang Yuan immediately turned around and charged towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heaven Overseeing Tower had been continuing to move, but because of the interference from the three regions' Gu Immortals, it was not able to go too far away from Fang Yuan.

"Stop him, stop him!"

"Stop Fang Yuan!!"

"No matter the cost, we must stop him!"

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals charged towards Fang Yuan like moths flying towards fire.

Ye Qiao Zi blocked the path.

Fang Yuan's punch pierced through his wooden armor and killed him.

Zhao Shan He pounced at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan kicked, directly bursting his body!

Vortex Space Boy screamed as he appeared behind Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan grabbed the tiny head with his fingers, he then clenched his fingers into a fist, forcibly turning Vortex Space Boy's head into a mush of blood and brain matter.

"Hahaha, this is the way!"

"Kill them, rip them to shreds!"

"Then, charge through the entire way!!"

Inside the bloody cape, Reckless Savage's will laughed loudly while waving his hands as he cheered on Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan, don't even think about it!" Duke Long flew once again, trying to stop Fang Yuan.

A palace suddenly appeared above him.

Dragon Palace!

...

The former Lord of Dragon Palace — Wu Shuai's life seemed to be filled with tragedies.

Dragonman extermination was like an executioner's blade that was always hanging above his and the dragonman race's head.

Dream revelations came time and time again, in order to settle the matter of dragonman extermination, he had to use rank eight Dragon Palace while doing experiments on the dragonman body.

But to do that, Wu Shuai alone was not enough, he gathered all of the dragonman Gu Immortals and told them the truth, he begged them for help.

In the huge Dragon Palace, there was an unprecedented meeting, almost all of the dragonman Gu Immortals had gathered together.

"To do experiments, we need a vast number of dragonmen, almost all these people will die, even if they survive, they will wish they were dead. Thus, I cannot make this decision alone, if anyone objects, speak up now."

"I object!" Immediately, someone stood out.

Everyone turned to look, it was Wu Shuai's cousin, the beloved seventh young master that Duke Long doted on the most.

Seventh young master pointed at Wu Shuai who was on his throne as he scolded: "You scoundrel, you are insane!!!"

"In order to gain Heavenly Court's trust, you killed your most loyal sworn brother!"

"To conceal the secret of dragonmen reign supreme, you caused the death of your own father!"

"To refine dream token Immortal Gu, you actually used your most beloved wife as the Gu material!"

"Now, to deal with dragonman extermination, you even want to sacrifice all of your innocent dragonmen and do experiments on them?"

"Why is your heart so wicked, why are you so cold-hearted?!"

"You think that this so-called evidence will make us believe you? Hehe, you are too laughable, do you think we are all fools?!"

"Hehehe, no, you are not laughable, you are pitiful and sad!"

"You wanted to give your wife happiness, and in the end? You sacrifice her to refine a Gu. Hehehe."

"You wanted to make your father proud, and in the end? You killed him! You killed him with your own two hands!!"

"You promised Huang Wei a bright future, you gave him hope. But in the end you killed him. And now, what future is there?"

"Hehehe, hahaha!" Seventh young master laughed maniacally, his tears were almost falling out: "You tried so hard to lead the dragonman race to rise up, and in the end? In the end, the dragonman race is about to be wiped out, we are going to be extinct!"

"It was you, it was you! If you were not ambitious and took over South Flower Island, relocating our people, developing rapidly and causing conflict with the humans, why would all this happen? If the dragonman race lived quietly and peacefully, ancestor would not have the intention of wiping us out!"

"Wu Shuai, oh Wu Shuai, you are the strongest person in the dragonman race besides our ancestor, but what you gave us was not glory or hope, it was neither equality nor dignity. It was... destruction!"

"You are a real tragedy! Your whole life is a tragedy!!"

The entire hall was silent.

Wu Shuai sat on his dragon throne, expressionless.

At this time, a dragonman Gu Immortal slowly walked out from the crowd and stood in front of Wu Shuai, he then turned to face the crowd. This dragonman Gu Immortal said in a deep voice: "I support Lord Wu Shuai."

Seventh young master was astonished: "Third... third uncle, you?"

A second dragonman Gu Immortal walked out of the crowd and stood in front of Wu Shuai and faced the dragonman Gu Immortals. This dragonman Gu Immortal said in a loud voice: "I agree greatly with Lord Wu Shuai's plan!"

Seventh young master was shocked: "Fifth uncle?!"

Then, the third, fourth, fifth person... all the dragonman Gu Immortals stood in front of Wu Shuai.

In the blink of an eye, seventh young master was left all alone.

He shouted in disbelief: "Have you all gone insane?!"

"If this is insanity, then we are all lunatics!"

"Hehehe, to become a lunatic like Ren Zu, I have no objections."

"Little Seventh, do you still not understand? How big of a tragedy is it for our lives and deaths to be in the hands of others! Even if this person is our ancestor, our progenitor, he cannot do this!!"

Wu Shuai slowly stood up from his dragon throne, his face was covered in tears.

"Everyone... I, Wu Shuai, hereby swear!" Wu Shuai's voice was extremely hoarse: "I will stand with the dragonman race regardless of survival or extermination, I will contribute my heart, my blood, and all the spirit and determination that I have!"

"Even if I were to fail in the end, I will fight to the final moment of my life."

"Even if I die in the end, my spirit and determination will be inherited by others."

"Even if my spirit and determination are no longer in existence... even if only my name is left, I will continue to fight, I will never stop resisting!!"

Chapter 1960: Destroying Fate!

Boom!

Under the amplification of heroes among people, Dragon Palace was barely able to ward off Duke Long.

"Get lost." At the next moment, Duke Long sent Dragon Palace flying with dragon claw strike.

Duke Long's field of vision became broad again, but he was not happy at all because Fang Yuan had already gotten close to Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Not only him, Wu Yong, Bing Sai Chuan, Shen Cong Sheng, and others had also moved in like a fierce tide. This wave of offense was terrifying.

Duke Long was already unable to block them in time and looked at this sight with overwhelming anger.

Right now, at this moment, even if Heaven Overseeing Tower turned phantom, it could not avoid this danger. Because Fang Yuan possessed dream path methods!

Feng Jin Huang could restrain his methods, but she was only a mortal Gu Master. Her strength was insufficient to go against the current Fang Yuan.

"Use fate vanquish quickly!" Duke Long shouted.

The Gu Immortals inside Heaven Overseeing Tower shuddered and did not care about enemies or allies, they activated fate vanquish again with desperation and anxiety.

The sky turned white!

Light was everywhere.

White light.

It filled the entire world, all the space in this world was filled with white light.

This was Heaven Overseeing Tower's strongest method, it used rank nine fate Gu as the core to activate a supreme killer move!

Be they Heavenly Court or the three regions' Gu Immortals, both sides were extremely familiar with this killer move.

White light filled the whole battlefield ruthlessly, not differentiating enemies or allies!

In an instant, regardless of which Immortal Gu House it was, they were all heavily injured or damaged!

"Damn it, damn it!" Wu Yong gritted his teeth as blood flowed out of the corners of his lips. He felt his ambition melting like snow in the white light: "This again, it is this move again! Whenever there is some breakthrough, fate vanquish will turn around the situation for Heavenly Court!"

"Huh?" Wu Yong's gaze suddenly focused before revealing a complex expression.

There was still a blood red trace remaining in the empty battlefield!

What was that?

It was a cape, fluttering like a war banner!

"Oh oh oh oh oh!" Inside the cape, Reckless Savage's will clenched his fists and beat his chest like an ape in heat.

He was extremely excited, shouting wildly: "This is it! This is it! Within heaven and earth, who else is there but me? At the crucial moment, you still need to rely on me! Cool, I am damn cool!!"

If it were just the three monsters, they naturally would not be able to resist the power of fate vanquish easily.

However, when they combined into one move and became connected to Fang Yuan as the core, using Fang Yuan's complete otherworldly demon identity, fate vanquish was no longer able to harm them.

In the endless light, Fang Yuan's white robe, black hair, and bloody cape were fluttering wildly with the wind.

He charged!

He pushed forward!

He did not stop at all!

"We still have... hope." From within the retreating Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan opened his eyes wide and stared at that bright red image moving in the white space.

Shen Cong Sheng coughed out blood repeatedly as he fell from the sky. He was also looking at Fang Yuan, using all his strength to fix his gaze on him!

He shouted inwardly: "Fang Yuan, you damned demon! Everything depends on you now!!"

Fang Yuan shot forward like a sharp arrow, he was like a star of calamity that rose to the sky from the ground, bringing chaos to the world and defying heaven itself!

"Charge, charge! The grandeur of men can be seen when they charge ahead, oh yeah!" Reckless Savage's will continued to shout as his voice rang in Fang Yuan's ears.

Be they Duke Long, Feng Jiu Ge, Heavenly Court's immortals, or the three regions' immortals, they forced their eyes open and fixed their gazes on Fang Yuan.

Heaven and earth was a scene of pure white, and in this whiteness, the path seemed to be exceptionally long and endless.

As if it spanned across history, from the past until now!

...

Over three million years ago, when variant humans were in prosperity, there was an inconspicuous human slave.

He was called Wei Yu Shu.

He heard of Heavenly Court's location, he was not willing to be a slave anymore, he escaped and was chased after.

His master berated him coldly.

"Wei Yu Shu, when I bought you back then, you were only a child who did not even know about cultivation!"

"I taught you step by step and raised you into a Gu Immortal. Was it my protection and indulgence that allowed you to have such guts?"

"Tell me, why did you betray me?"

"Have I, Princess Ye Tong, mistreated you?! You lived in luxury and peace, you only needed to serve me and I have never treated you cruelly."

Wei Yu Shu smiled sadly: "But, even if I lived a much better life, I was still only your slave!"

The female inkman immortal was furious: "What is bad about becoming my slave? Many inkmen want to live your life but don't get such a chance!"

Wei Yu Shu was dazed for a moment before he spoke slowly: "I did not think it was bad before, but when I heard there was a Heavenly Court in this world where humans live... I realized why I was always in low spirits and felt unhappiness. It was because I lacked one thing."

"Hehehe, I have read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, I am truly too stupid. I am even more stupid than those wingless birds, toothless beasts, gill-less fish! At least, they know they lost their freedom and are staking their lives to chase after freedom. But what about me? I did not even know I lost my freedom!"

"So, you want to escape, you want to reach Heavenly Court?" The female inkman immortal sneered: "You are too naive, you actually believe in the temptation of these devils?!"

Wei Yu Shu closed his eyes, his voice was hoarse: "It is not that I believe it, but I want to believe it."

"Heavenly Court was never the important point!"

"Without Heavenly Court, there can be Earthly Court, or even Human Court!"

"There will always be a place where a group of humans gather and pursue freedom!!"

...

A million years ago.

Duke Long snorted coldly: "Tell me, Hong Ting, who can do as they please in this world? Your thoughts are too childish, you think becoming an Immortal Venerable and leading the righteous path would not need sacrifices? What is there in this world that has no price to pay for? How shallow do you think the words 'righteous path' are? Wrong! Maintaining Heavenly Court's righteous path requires you to pay a price, it requires sacrifices. If you don't even have this sacrificial mentality, then I will tell you, you don't have the qualifications to enter Heavenly Court!"

Duke Long's brows raised, his face cold as ice: "Who do you want to revive?"

"Every person who sacrificed themselves for me. My parents, Liu Shu Xian, and many others."

"Even if there are crueler tragedies, I will accept them! Master, disciple always had a question. Why? Why must we accept fate's arrangements? If there was no fate, would the world truly fall into chaos? Is it not possible that the world will become a better place?" Hong Ting asked in an anxious tone.

...

The current era.

Duke Long looked at Feng Jin Huang and said solemnly: "Huang Er, you need to understand that you are the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable who will surpass all the past venerables! You will create dream path and be invincible in the whole world. Your glory will shine and spread for ages, becoming the eternal symbol and support of humanity. Don't fear, don't hesitate, take each success to press forward indomitably until you reach the supreme peak of this world!"

Feng Jin Huang's eyes got brighter and brighter as she listened. She smiled with unparalleled beauty.

Duke Long also smiled.

Feng Jin Huang said: "If all this is predestined by fate, then... I do not believe in fate!"

...

Boom!

Fang Yuan directly broke through the roof of Heaven Overseeing Tower and entered inside.

A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal inside stood up to stop him.

Fang Yuan directly pierced his hands into his chest and pulled fiercely, ripping the Heavenly Court Gu Immortal into two halves!

Blood splashed on Fang Yuan's face; his skin was white like snow, cold like ice.

Blood splashed on Fang Yuan's black hair; the hair was like the night sky, letting out profound eerie light.

Blood splashed on Fang Yuan's blood cape; the cape was touching the ground like it was paving a bloody path for the tyrant's domination.

Fang Yuan took large strides and reached the center of the top floor. Fate Gu was right in front of him, it had always been there, as if it were constantly receiving offerings, offerings that it had been receiving for millions of years!

Fang Yuan grabbed fate Gu!

At this instance, even Reckless Savage's will inside the cape was quiet, closing his mouth as he stared at Fang Yuan blankly.

Because he realized: This was the moment of truth for the whole of humanity, no, for the whole world.

At this time, Fang Yuan held fate Gu in his hands, his gaze was flickering with complex emotions.

He had finally caught fate Gu, this was a scene which he had imagined countless times.

His goal was achieved at this moment, but he did not think of himself and instead thought of \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Ren Zu said: He wanted freedom and to get rid of fate's shackles. After that, he could go wherever he wanted to go, and be with whoever he wanted to with forever.

The birds berated him: You humans are destined to be alone, all gatherings will end up in separation. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies.

Ren Zu said: I want freedom and to get rid of fate's shackles. I will possess countless delicacies and wines, endless wealth, and all kinds of comfortable and beautiful clothes.

The beasts ridiculed him: But you humans were born with empty hands and will pass away with nothing. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies.

Ren Zu said: I want freedom and to get rid of fate's shackles. I will breathe freely and live on forever, I want eternal life!

The fishes rebutted: But you humans are destined to have no relation with eternal life, you will die of old age and illnesses. Oh human, you want to pursue freedom but you also need to abide by your nature, you should not indulge in wild fantasies.

Ren Zu was puzzled.

Ren Zu was disgruntled.

Ren Zu was irritated.

Ren Zu became insane!

How can you have such thoughts?

Why can't I have the same thoughts?

Why can't a human be together forever with their loved ones?

Why can't a human live life without worries and have endless wealth?

Why can't a human have eternal life?

Because fate does not allow it?

Because it does not allow, therefore I cannot do it?! I cannot even think about it?!

On what basis?

On what damned basis?

On what basis am I not allowed to think about it?!

On what basis is eternal life forbidden?!

If such thoughts turn me insane.

Then let me become a lunatic!

If such pursuit makes me demonic.

Then let me become a demon!!

Fang Yuan looked at fate Gu and sneered coldly.

He clenched his fist lightly.

Crack.

A soft sound echoed.

Fate Gu was directly crushed into pieces.

Rank nine fate Gu —

Destroyed!

Chapter 1961: So What If It Was Destroyed?

The moment fate Gu was destroyed, the whole battlefield returned to its previous state.

The white light formed by fate vanquish killer move disappeared completely.

Crack crack.

A series of crisp sounds echoed as countless cracks spread throughout Heaven Overseeing Tower. At the next moment, the whole of Heaven Overseeing Tower crumbled into pieces!

The grand Heavenly Court fell into deathly silence.

There was no trace of wind in the battlefield, but the immortals felt a hurricane blowing in their hearts!

Heaven Overseeing Tower turned into countless fragments that fell down along with Gu Immortal corpses. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's painting path method turned into a ray of light that crossed the sky and flew far away.

Fang Yuan ignored it and quietly floated in the air, looking at Duke Long, Feng Jiu Ge, and the rest.

He had no expression and did not say anything, he only opened his palm slowly. Under everybody's vision killer move, everyone in the five regions saw — the fragments of the destroyed fate Gu!

"Fate Gu has been... destroyed?"

"We won?!"

The three regions' Gu Immortals looked at each other, seeing the astonishment and daze on each other's faces.

"Unbelievable, we really did it!"

"This battle will definitely be remembered by later generations."

After coming to their senses, the three regions' Gu Immortals cheered wildly!

On the contrary, Heavenly Court's remaining Gu Immortals had ashen expressions and were dazed like puppets.

Fate Gu was Heavenly Court's banner, their spiritual pillar.

It was more than a rank nine Gu worm, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable had relied on this Gu to create the rule of humanity, it gave humans the hope of freedom and courage to revolt.

After over three million years of inheritance and development, the significance of fate Gu was much greater to Heavenly Court. It was Heavenly Court's foundation, a symbol, and also an eternally fluttering banner.

But now, this banner was taken down and torn by Fang Yuan!

Heavenly Court's immortals felt that the pillar in their mind was taken away, their world had collapsed!

Even without the three regions' Gu Immortals attacking or any external stimulation, they were dazed and did not know what they should do.

Even Feng Jiu Ge was silent, his destiny song that had kept on resounding throughout the battlefield stopped at this moment.

Far away, Feng Jin Huang was hiding in a secret underground Immortal Gu House, she was weeping silently: "Fate Gu... has been destroyed! How did this happen? Everyone clearly put in so much effort, not even hesitating to sacrifice themselves!"

Qin Ding Ling's gaze was blank, she was like a lifeless statue.

The greatly damaged Demon Judgment Board rose to the sky, Fang Zheng who was inside looked at Fang Yuan with a highly complicated expression: "Fang Yuan, you actually accomplished it. In Heavenly Court, in front of the venerable methods, you destroyed fate Gu! So the gap between you and I is simply this big."

This gap made Fang Zheng feel despair, but a strange thing was Fang Zheng did not feel bitterness at this moment, instead he felt a trace of relief.

It was time to give up.

A person like Fang Yuan was different from everyone from the start. Thinking of rivaling him was wishful thinking from the start, a delirious thought even.

"Damn it, damn it..."

"We failed, fate Gu has been destroyed."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals cried. They had used all their strength, given their everything, some crawled out of their graves to fight, some held on till the end, but they still failed.

"We have really failed our comrades who sacrificed themselves!"

"I am too ashamed to face my seniors!"

Shame surfaced on the Heavenly Court immortals' faces, many even had the impulse to kill themselves.

"Don't panic!" At this moment, Duke Long suddenly spoke, his voice spreading throughout the battlefield, shaking every Gu Immortal's mind.

Duke Long flew to the sky, his expression was solemn as he knew this was the crucial moment.

Fate Gu had been destroyed, Duke Long could not afford to be upset or blame himself. He was the leader of Heavenly Court, he needed to try his hardest to deal with this issue!

What made him anxious was that even the deeply experienced Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were shaken like this. What would the people all over the world think about this sight?

If Fang Yuan scheming and defeating Heavenly Court time and again earlier was like a heavy slap to Heavenly Court's face, then Fang Yuan destroying fate Gu was like shaking Heavenly Court's foundation completely, destroying the status and reputation Heavenly Court had accumulated for over three million years!

Duke Long had to restore their morale and fighting spirit.

"Fang Yuan, you really think you destroyed fate Gu?" Duke Long suddenly laughed with no trace of listlessness, one could not sense any form of wavering in his tone.

Fang Yuan did not reply and only slightly raised his hand as he looked at Duke Long.

Immediately, the three regions' Gu Immortals ridiculed: "Duke Long, have you gone blind? You can't see the fragments of fate Gu?"

Some of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals looked with bright gazes, a spark of hope rising in their hearts: "Is the fate Gu that Fang Yuan destroyed a replica?"

But Duke Long shook his head, still laughing: "Hehehe, the destroyed fate Gu is the real one. But Fang Yuan, even though fate Gu is destroyed, has it really been destroyed forever, can we not refine it once again?"

"Huh?" The immortals were stupefied.

Immortal Gu were unique, this was an irrefutable truth of the world. If I had an Immortal Gu, others could not possess the same one.

But when this Immortal Gu was destroyed, others would have the chance to possess it.

Fate Gu was destroyed by Fang Yuan now, this was an ironclad truth. But this was not a genuine ending because Heavenly Court could refine it again!

"Does Heavenly Court have fate Gu's recipe?" Shen Cong Sheng's expression was grim as he asked.

"Heavenly Court has held fate Gu for over three million years, we had countless refinement path great experts and three Immortal Venerables in this period. Take a guess if our Heavenly Court has fate Gu's recipe or not?" Duke Long smiled, his entire body letting out confidence and calmness.

"Damn it!" The three regions' Gu Immortals were exasperated.

Duke Long laughed: "However, even if Heavenly Court did not have fate Gu's Immortal Gu recipe, so what? Everyone, let me ask you, was the fate Gu in the Immemorial Antiquity Era refined by Ren Zu?"

"Of course not." Qin Ding Ling replied, she understood Duke Long's intention and her eyes shone with life again: "Fate Gu was born from heaven and earth itself."

Duke Long nodded: "That's right, Immortal Gu are born from nature which is why there are many wild Immortal Gu. Even if we cannot refine it, heaven and earth will refine fate Gu. The new fate Gu might be rank six or even rank nine directly. Who can say for sure?"

This time, the three regions' Gu Immortals looked at each other.

After Duke Long mentioned this point, they suddenly realized that destroying fate Gu might not be a big deal!

If fate Gu was destroyed, so be it, it could be refined again.

"Even if it is refined, we can destroy it again!" A Gu Immortal shouted angrily, but even he himself did not have much confidence.

To destroy fate Gu this time, they had paid a huge price! Could such success really be replicated? Forget about anything else, just the point that only an otherworldly demon could destroy fate Gu blocked the path of many heroes and conquerors. Didn't even three Demon Venerables fail?

"Damn it, how could we have failed to notice this?" A Gu Immortal was vexed, but thinking about it, he could blame himself for not considering everything properly.

After all, invading Heavenly Court and destroying fate Gu was already an enormous goal and could even be said to be wishful thinking. To realize this goal, the Gu Immortals had already exhausted their minds and energy. This was an impossible mission akin to a mortal ascending to heaven, even if they used all their strength and had inexhaustible will, it was still difficult to achieve.

Under such circumstances, who could afford to think of the matter after ascending to heaven?

In fact, when Central Continent held the Refinement Path Convention and four regions' Gu Immortals invaded, who could say for sure that they could destroy fate Gu?

No one!

Even Fang Yuan, even venerables did not have such confidence.

Everyone was giving it a try.

After the attempt succeeded, the Gu Immortals were exulted. But what happens after realizing this goal?

Duke Long's words were also the truth. The three regions' Gu Immortals suddenly discovered that the price they paid, the battles and the effort they invested were all in vain, was it just an empty victory?

The three regions' Gu Immortals were silent, their expressions gradually turning unsightly.

Wu Yong was sharp and sensed the change in people's hearts and the fallen morale, he immediately refuted coldly: "Lord Duke Long, you have a sharp tongue. However, Heavenly Court's failure is still a failure, you took great pain to defend and even hide fate Gu in Heavenly Court, yet we were still able to destroy it. In the future, even if you obtain fate Gu again, so what?"

"Hehehe, in fact, you need to be careful. Otherwise, when heaven and earth gives birth to the new fate Gu, you won't be able to refine it yourselves. At that time, fate Gu will become a wild Immortal Gu, anyone will be able to possess it, it might not necessarily be obtained by your Heavenly Court anymore."

The three regions' immortals' eyes brightened and their morale soared.

Duke Long was smiling calmly: "Wu Yong, you are not wrong about it at all. Let's say fate Gu becomes a wild Immortal Gu and is obtained by one of you, so what? Can you all... use it? Do you know how to use it?"

Even Wu Yong could not reply to this question.

Duke Long smiled proudly: "Fate Gu can never be used by Gu Immortals! Before the Remote Antiquity Era, it was held by variant humans but they could not use it. Over three million years, my Heavenly Court had several Immortal Venerables, but no one could directly use this Gu. Countless geniuses racked their minds and then conceptualized Heaven Overseeing Tower, it took three million years for us to research a killer move that could make use of fate Gu, and that is fate vanquish!"

"Do you understand the killer move fate vanquish? Do you know how to construct Heaven Overseeing Tower?"

The three regions' Gu Immortals fell into silence.

Duke Long continued: "Only heaven's will can use fate Gu. Back then, for the sake of humanity, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable did not hesitate to sacrifice herself and merged with heaven's will, disturbing and influencing heaven's will. Which is why, humanity that rose three million years ago is still flourishing now, we remained as the rulers of the world."

"And my Heavenly Court built the immortal graveyard to support Star Constellation's will. Heavenly Court members all chose to hibernate in the immortal graveyard to provide constant help for Star Constellation's will. Only then are we able to influence fate Gu and thus influence the position of humanity in the whole world!"

"Among you, who can achieve this?"

Duke Long swept his gaze throughout the battlefield, the three regions' Gu Immortals were silent while Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals stood proudly, someone even added arrogantly: "No one! In the vast five regions, only Heavenly Court can accomplish this!"

"No, you are wrong, Duke Long." Bing Sai Chuan's retort came from inside Calamity Luck Altar: "Even if we are unable to use fate Gu, we can use it as a Gu refinement material to refine destiny Gu! Fate Gu cannot be controlled by others, but destiny Gu can. This is the plan of our Lord Giant Sun Immortal Venerable."

Duke Long looked towards Calamity Luck Altar and gave a disdainful smile: "Even if you refine destiny Gu, does it mean fate Gu won't exist?"

Bing Sai Chuan was unable to reply.

If fate Gu was used as a Gu material, when Longevity Heaven refined destiny Gu, fate Gu would be used up. In the future, there could still be a new fate Gu.

Duke Long sighed: "No matter what you do, fate Gu will still exist. Even if it destroyed now, it will appear again in the future. As long as it appears, will your efforts today have any meaning?"

The three regions' Gu Immortals were silent.

"Of course there is meaning!" Duke Long answered himself with solemness and hatred: "The meaning of this is to give a chance for variant humans to rise up, for them to create an unimaginably bad influence on humanity."

"You cannot use fate Gu and how long will it take for you to refine destiny Gu? You don't even have an incomplete Gu recipe of fate Gu! Once fate Gu reappears, it will be controlled by heaven's will. Humanity will decline and variant humans will rise."

"And the one who led to this is all of you!" Duke Long berated and suddenly pointed towards Fang Yuan: "Especially you! You are the greatest evil! You destroyed the immortal graveyard, Star Constellation's will won't be able to interfere with heaven's will like before. If humanity is exterminated in the future, you will be the main culprit behind everything!!"

"Fang Yuan, oh Fang Yuan, you think you obtained victory by destroying fate Gu?"

"Hehehe, at best, this is only a giant joke."

"My Heavenly Court thinks for humanity in all aspects, we offered our blood and sweat for the benefits of humanity, even sacrificing ourselves. And you people, for your own selfish interests, destroyed the great position that my Heavenly Court had maintained meticulously for millions of years."

"My Heavenly Court can refine fate Gu again in the future, we can refine it secretly! We won't let the five regions know of fate Gu's refinement, will you find out about it?"

"Can you all stop us in time?"

"Even if you stop us the second or the third time. What about after that? Who can guarantee you can stop us from refining it again and again?"

"We will only refine rank six fate Gu, it is far easier than restoring it to rank nine!"

"Also, every time we fight because of fate Gu, humanity will suffer heavy losses and greatly expend its foundation. This will give variant humans the opportunity to rise up against us!"

Duke Long lamented with deep emotions as he said this.

"Who is this old man? I did not know that Heavenly Court did so many things in consideration for our entire human race!"

"Why did they invade Heavenly Court, what were these Gu Immortals thinking?"

"These people are all demons, they disregarded the big picture for their own interests! They are accursed sinners!"

The five regions' mortals resonated with Duke Long.

Most of the mortals had extremely little understanding of the Gu Immortal world.

And the Gu Immortals scattered in the five regions were also silent when they heard Duke Long.

Heavenly Court was powerful, Heavenly Court was domineering, Heavenly Court occupied almost all the cultivation resources of Central Continent, Heavenly Court's ambition stretched extremely far and actively interfered in major events of the other four regions.

But no one was able to deny Heavenly Court's contribution in protecting humanity.

This was a fact!

"Ahhh, this is somewhat troublesome. Although it felt extremely satisfying to destroy fate Gu, there is some emptiness after the adrenaline rush, this is a bit of a problem." Inside the blood cape, Reckless Savage's will mumbled while holding his head.

"Hehe, Duke Long, are you done?" Fang Yuan's expression was indifferent, after destroying fate Gu, this was the first time he spoke and broke the silence.

Duke Long looked at Fang Yuan, his brows furrowed as he started feeling uneasy.

Fang Yuan was too calm! According to Fang Yuan's intelligence, how could he not see the crucial point? Duke Long tried to think from another perspective, if he were Fang Yuan, he would definitely use all his strength to attack and not give the enemies the chance to speak.

Because once Duke Long spoke, he would create this current situation.

Indeed.

Duke Long's words restored Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals' morale and also suppressed the enemies' spirit, he also raised Heavenly Court's prestige and it was simply turning the situation around!

Duke Long was worthy of being the leader of Heavenly Court, he not only possessed terrifying strength worthy of the main pillar, at the crucial time, he could even lead and boost morale, changing people's hearts.

How could Fang Yuan not see this?

But he did not stop Duke Long, Duke Long could even vaguely see a trace of anticipation in his eyes.

So what was Fang Yuan anticipating?

At the next moment, Fang Yuan chuckled: "Oh Duke Long, who told you that destroying fate Gu meant the end of this battle? You seem to have forgotten someone."

Duke Long's pupils shrank as he realized something.

He followed Fang Yuan's gaze and saw a river.

That was a phantom silhouette of the River of Time!

Calamity Luck Altar carried Red Lotus Demon Venerable's method — Call of the Ancient. From the start of the battle, this killer move's power had condensed into a phantom River of Time in Heavenly Court.

Northern Plains' past Gu Immortal experts walked out from this phantom river and created an extremely huge threat to Heavenly Court.

But as the battle continued, the phantom River of Time seemed to have gradually grown powerless as fewer and fewer of Northern Plains' experts were summoned.

At the late stage of the battle, this phantom River of Time seemed to be motionless and showed no traces of new figures emerging.

However, when Fang Yuan destroyed fate Gu, this phantom River of Time seemed like a beast that had broken free of its shackles, it started surging wildly and turbulently.

Swish swish swish...

The river water surged, raising astonishing waves.

A figure walked out slowly and naturally from the giant waves.

All the immortals present heard his voice:

"In my youth I shined in the light of spring, horses trampled on flowers as fragrance of wine spread.

Love and hatred came with the waves, summer cicadas sang as I woke up in the middle of the night.

Planting red lotuses in the River of Time, going back in time with my tears run dry.

Through the vicissitudes of life I return to this stage, the myriad beings anticipate a life unbound by fate!"

He had the appearance of a young man, his gaze seemed to have experienced countless vicissitudes, he wore a red robe, his face was pure as jade, his eyes were bright like stars, and his skin was white as snow.

He walked out from the phantom River of Time and stepped into Heavenly Court's battlefield.

Everyone watched, there was complete silence all around.

His gaze moved around before fixing on Duke Long's body.

Duke Long shook, his expression was extremely complicated as he opened his mouth, his lips moved but no words came out.

The young man smiled: "Master, have you been well?"

Chapter 1962: I Have Destiny Immortal Gu's Recipe!

"Wow, this person came out of the river!"

"Why is there a river in the sky?"

"The young man who walked out is really handsome!"

"I still think that the fairy in the red cape looks nicer."

Because of the killer move everybody's vision, the mortals of the five regions saw this scene, they discussed enthusiastically and rowdily.

Mortals and Gu Masters might not understand the severity of the situation, but most of the Gu Immortals knew who this mysterious young man was.

At once, Gu Immortals of the five regions were shaken, it was as if a world destroying tornado was rampaging in their hearts.

"This Gu Immortal, it can't be?"

"Is he Red Lotus Demon Venerable?!"

Among the generations of venerables, Red Lotus Demon Venerable was the most mysterious one. Back then, Heavenly Court used everything to nurture him but their efforts were in vain. Not only did Red Lotus not become an Immortal Venerable, he even became a Demon Venerable, betraying the righteous path and damaging fate Gu. There was also the problem of the dragonman race mixed within this, Heavenly Court had to disregard costs and make information path great experts use their most profound methods to eliminate the influence of this event.

Moreover, Red Lotus Demon Venerable had constantly been reborn, he changed his style of action and wanted to preserve Heavenly Court's reputation for the sake of his master, he started to act secretly in the dark.

Thus, most Gu Immortals did not know the true appearance of Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

But they all heard the mysterious young looking Gu Immortal call Duke Long his master. He had also walked out of the phantom River of Time...

Everyone knew that Duke Long was the master of Red Lotus.

"But why did this happen? Didn't Red Lotus Demon Venerable die?"

"He might be a new disciple of Duke Long."

The Gu Immortals of the five regions were uncertain, but Heavenly Court's battlefield was full of experienced experts, there were many super forces behind them that had secretive information regarding Red Lotus Demon Venerable, they knew quite a lot of things.

Thus, be they Heavenly Court or the three regions' Gu Immortals, they looked at the young Gu Immortal while dazed like rocks, they were numb from shock.

They recognized the young Gu Immortal's identity.

It was really Red Lotus Demon Venerable!

The three regions' Gu Immortals were shaken, Red Lotus Demon Venerable was the disciple of Duke Long, seeing his attitude towards Duke Long, it still carried concern and respect.

Heavenly Court did not dare to act rashly. After all, Red Lotus Demon Venerable had invaded Heavenly Court in the past, damaging fate Gu. After that, in order to repair fate Gu, Heavenly Court spent over a million years, countless resources and manpower. They managed to repair it in the end, but it was a pity that Red Lotus' inheritor, Fang Yuan, destroyed it! It was truly infuriating!

And most importantly, there was Red Lotus Demon Venerable's cultivation level!

He was a venerable with rank nine battle strength, once he appeared, who could face him in combat?

Even the powerful Duke Long, even the colossal Di Zang Sheng, even Fang Yuan who wore the blood battle cape, were no match for the rank nine Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

Nobody held any doubt regarding this.

The young looking Red Lotus guessed everyone's thoughts, he walked on thin air as he got to the center of the battlefield, he smiled: "Everyone, no need to worry, I have already died. Now that fate Gu is destroyed while call of the ancient has barely any power left, I am merely Red Lotus' will."

Red Lotus' will was vivid and solid like it was the real person.

But upon close inspection, one would realize that there were differences between it and an actual Gu Immortal.

The immortals managed to discern this as they let out sighs of relief.

Red Lotus did not lie, this was his will, not his main body.

His reputation was too great, he appeared in a shocking manner, everyone could not help but think of it as the worst case situation. After Red Lotus informed them, they realized the truth.

The bad feeling in Duke Long's heart was getting heavier.

Duke Long snorted coldly, shouting: "Red Lotus, even though you have died, you are still not willing to give up that heretical thought? You won this time, thanks to you, fate Gu has been destroyed by your chosen pawn."

Red Lotus shook his head: "Master, this is not a win, precisely so, I had to show up."

"What are you trying to do?" Duke Long frowned, the bad feeling in his heart intensified.

Red Lotus replied with action, his body flickered as he appeared before Fang Yuan instantly.

Fang Yuan looked at Red Lotus' will with a calm expression, his gaze was dark like the night sky.

He had very deep ties with this venerable. The Spring Autumn Cicada that he had used to turn situations around many times was the time path Immortal Gu created by this person.

"You did very well. I am sure you've guessed what I am going to do now?" Red Lotus' will smiled at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan replied: "Somewhat."

"Even though fate Gu is destroyed, the truth is that to use it as a Gu material to refine destiny Gu, we will need an otherworldly demon like you. Thanks to someone's help, you finally became a complete otherworldly demon." Red Lotus' will said this as he looked far away, towards the periphery of the battlefield where Spectral Soul and his servants were hiding.

Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan were perspiring profusely. Even though this was just Red Lotus' will, he was simply too terrifying, finding out their hiding spot with one glance.

At the hiding spot, Spectral Soul had already returned to human form, he looked at Red Lotus' will with a complex expression.

This was not the first time he had met Red Lotus' will, his memories surfaced from the depths of his mind.

Back then, he became a soul path venerable, he entered the River of Time to explore its secrets. Even though Spectral Soul Demon Venerable cultivated soul path, with his foundation, he could freely enter and exit the River of Time.

As the mysterious fog appeared, a stone lotus island appeared in front of him of its own initiative.

He stepped onto the stone lotus island as Red Lotus' will smiled and invited him: "I have been waiting, Spectral Soul. Let us make a deal?"

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable agreed to the transaction. Therefore, he learned of fate Gu, and also the truth behind the historical invasion of Heavenly Court by the three Demon Venerables. He gave up on the plan to attack Heavenly Court, he went to design and create sovereign immortal fetus Gu instead.

Red Lotus' will looked at Spectral Soul, using his gaze as an indication — it is time to carry out our transaction.

Spectral Soul chuckled as he ordered Old Man Zheng Yuan: "Gather all of the human will, send it all to Fang Yuan."

Old Man Zheng Yuan immediately moved.

At once, the vast amount of human will from Heavenly Court surged. These wills were of all varieties and colors, they were filled with ugly desires or beautiful dreams, one could indulge in them and lose their way, they were beautiful and ugly at the same time. People wanted them but also hated them.

Red Lotus' will looked at the vast amount of will that resembled a rainbow sea.

He turned around and smiled at Fang Yuan, before entering the ocean of human will personally.

The human wills engulfed him instantly, next, fire started burning out of nowhere, resembling blazing red lotuses that burned the sea of wills.

Duke Long saw this and became enraged, this was not something a mere will could achieve: "Red Lotus, back then when you attacked Heavenly Court, you actually left this arrangement behind!"

Before he finished speaking, Duke Long flew up, wanting to destroy the human wills.

"Don't even think about it!" Wu Shuai was prepared for this, he manipulated Dragon Palace to stop him.

Both sides fought, Dragon Palace was soon forced to retreat.

"What are you all waiting for?" Duke Long shouted at all the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals jolted, they started to approach Fang Yuan and the vast sea of wills.

The three regions' Gu Immortals were not going to watch, a huge battle erupted again!

"No matter what Red Lotus is doing, it must be disadvantageous to Heavenly Court, this is something we want to see." Wu Yong's eyes shined with bright light, he shot out countless wind blades around him.

Di Zang Sheng roared angrily, it coiled his body around Fang Yuan and the human wills, resisting killer moves using its body as a shield, growling in pain but refusing to retreat.

Bing Sai Chuan rode in Calamity Luck Altar as he resisted Demon Judgment Board. He had a complex gaze, it looked like Red Lotus Demon Venerable was going to refine destiny Gu as well. This went against Longevity Heaven's goal but he could not stop it or retreat now, he had to fight first.

The flames burned the human wills, emitting a dense, sharp fragrance.

After Red Lotus' will fused into the human wills, the vast sea of wills cooperated with Fang Yuan, entering the flames.

Lumps of flames spread out, quickly expanding into a sea of fire.

The surrounding temperature rose, if rank six Gu Immortals were not putting up a defense, they would instantly melt due to the flames.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, the bloody cape protected him, he stood in the sea of fire but he did not make a move.

A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal could not help but laugh: "Fang Yuan is not making a move, he looks like he does not have destiny Immortal Gu's recipe!"

Fang Yuan looked at the person who was speaking from within the flames, he smiled coldly as he tone carried a hint of pity: "I do not have it, but here in this battlefield, somebody does."

"Who?!" The fighting immortals all had this question in their heads.

"Find them and kill them!" The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals subconsciously had such thoughts.

"Find them and protect them!" The three regions' Gu Immortals instantly made their decision.

Fang Yuan silently shifted his gaze towards Feng Jiu Ge.

Feng Jiu Ge also looked at him.

The two looked at each other through the sea of fire, they stared at each other as if the surrounding fights in the battlefield were far away from them.

Feng Jiu Ge breathed in deeply, he slowly shut his eyes.

Next, he opened his mouth and started to sing, the tune of destiny song spread throughout the battlefield.

"Feng Jiu Ge has attacked again!"

"Let's kill Fang Yuan, let's exterminate the human will!"

"Exterminate the human will first, Fang Yuan is secondary."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals were energized, but at the next moment, they screamed in shock.

They were not powered up by destiny song, instead, the three regions' Gu Immortals gained a boost in strength.

"Feng Jiu Ge, what are you doing?!" Duke Long was furious and shocked, he turned around and looked at Feng Jiu Ge like a furious blood dragon.

"Father!" Feng Jin Huang's voice was filled with utter shock, it could be heard clearly as well.

"Feng Jiu Ge, why are you doing this? You betrayed Heavenly Court! How dare you, how can you do this!!" Qin Ding Ling screamed in a shrill voice, she was extremely furious. In order to nurture Feng Jiu Ge, she had even given him her responsive luck Immortal Gu.

But Feng Jiu Ge actually 'repaid' her like this!

Feng Jiu Ge had a calm expression, he did not stop singing.

At this very moment, he betrayed Heavenly Court unhesitantly, joining Fang Yuan and the three regions' allied forces!

Chapter 1963: Feng Jiu Ge's Red Lotus True Inheritance

The tune of destiny song filled the battlefield, but at this moment, Feng Jiu Ge's opponent was Heavenly Court.

Regardless of the shock and perplexity of both sides, Feng Jiu Ge was immersed in his own singing, at the same time, memories surfaced in his mind.

During the second invasion of Lang Ya blessed land...

Fang Yuan set up a formation in the blessed land, Feng Jiu Ge and Chen Yi were isolated.

Feng Jiu Ge faced Fang Yuan alone.

"My Gu worms are vanishing mysteriously! How can this be? This should be a theft path method. Is it Fang Yuan's method or this formation's?" Feng Jiu Ge was shocked.

Because Fang Yuan had theft path methods, Feng Jiu Ge was at a disadvantage.

As time passed, his Gu worms got stolen one by one, among them were several sound path Immortal Gu.

Feng Jiu Ge's battle strength fell greatly, he had to choose to use fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu to escape for now.

Suppress space Immortal Gu!

But Fang Yuan suddenly used his prepared method, Feng Jiu Ge failed to escape.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

Next, Fang Yuan even stole the Fixed Immortal Travel that he was after.

Feng Jiu Ge's heart turned icy cold, he knew that he was in a desperate situation!

But at this moment, he received Fang Yuan's secret transmission: "Oh Feng Jiu Ge, I will not kill you, I will not steal fate armor Immortal Gu either. You and I are not on the same side, but you and Heavenly Court are not aligned in beliefs either. Face your true inner self, what do you truly want? Let me ask you, have you started comprehending destiny song already?"

Feng Jiu Ge initially thought that this was a trap by Fang Yuan to affect his fighting spirit and determination, but soon he became very perplexed.

Fang Yuan actually slowed down his attacks, he stopped forcing him.

This made Feng Jiu Ge think involuntarily —

"What does Fang Yuan mean by this?"

"He knows I have fate armor Immortal Gu? He reacted so perfectly when we attacked Lang Ya blessed land this time, he made ample preparations, does this mean he used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth?"

"If he really is reborn, what happened in the previous life? From his words, why does it seem like I will diverge from Heavenly Court?"

At this time, Fang Yuan transmitted again: "Oh Feng Jiu Ge, I know you are full of questions and suspicions. Don't worry, as time passes, you will understand what I mean. Next, I will open the formation and give Chen Yi the false impression that he broke it. I am sure he will teleport you away, hehehe, we will meet again, Feng Jiu Ge."

"Fang Yuan, explain yourself clearly!" Feng Jiu Ge transmitted.

But at the next moment, an explosion occurred as the formation space that was isolated became connected.

Chen Yi saw Feng Jiu Ge in danger and quickly shouted loudly: "Hang on, I'm coming!"

"Be careful, the enemy has a way to steal Gu worms." Feng Jiu Ge hesitated briefly before immediately giving Chen Yi critical information.

During the fight, Fang Yuan attacked ferociously, he critically injured Feng Jiu Ge, fate armor Immortal Gu was activated.

In order to save Feng Jiu Ge, Chen Yi used karma relocation.

Feng Jiu Ge was shocked: "Fang Yuan was right, Chen Yi really had a way to send me out!"

"Feng Jiu Ge, you managed to escape this time, but next time will be different." Fang Yuan had a plain expression.

This sentence had a different meaning when it was heard by Feng Jiu Ge.

...

In the battle of Lang Ya blessed land, Heavenly Court lost.

After the battle, Feng Jiu Ge considered Fang Yuan's words.

"He could have killed me but he did not take my life. Why?"

"Fang Yuan is a demon with a ruthless and vicious personality, he only cares about benefits! He let me go, there is only one reason, I will be a big help to him in the future."

"But I am a Central Continent member, a prospective member of Heavenly Court, the Dao Guardian of my daughter Feng Jin Huang! Don't tell me... there will be conflict between me and Heavenly Court?"

"If Fang Yuan is reborn from the future, does that mean that in his previous life, I opposed Heavenly Court, I was his natural ally?"

As he held such concerns, Feng Jiu Ge did not inform Fairy Zi Wei of this situation.

The thing that moved him the most was the destiny song that Fang Yuan mentioned.

"Destiny song..." Feng Jiu Ge had a vague sensation and inspiration, but his inspiration was too faint and far away, he could not grab onto it.

But he knew that this was a direction.

He continued to explore it, soon gaining some fragmented comprehension.

Until one day, when he was stationed at Embroidered Tower, he looked at the three bloody skins left behind by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable.

All of the comprehension that he had during this period underwent a qualitative transformation.

Feng Jiu Ge's soul was deeply stirred, he could not help but smile: "It seems that my next song will be — Destiny Song!"

...

In the battle of the River of Time.

Fang Yuan and Feng Jiu Ge met again.

"How is the creation of destiny song going?" They fought intensely on the surface but Fang Yuan was secretly transmitting to him.

Feng Jiu Ge: "Fang Yuan, what is it that you know?"

"Hehehe. Come to the River of Time more often, you should have realized that being here greatly helps your comprehension and creation of destiny song. But the most helpful thing is still the Red Lotus true inheritance on the stone lotus island." Fang Yuan said.

"What do you mean?" Feng Jiu Ge asked.

"According to my estimations, that should be a true inheritance that Red Lotus Demon Venerable specially left behind for you, it will help you greatly." Fang Yuan said.

Feng Jiu Ge hesitated for a moment before answering: "I will not owe you this favor without repaying it. Let me tell you this, in Heavenly Court's Embroidered Tower, there are three true inheritances left behind by Reckless Savage Demon Venerable. Each one requires a key, they are attitude Gu, mutation Gu, and adaptation Gu."

"Oh?!" A sharp light flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes.

He did not think that Feng Jiu Ge was lying, the items were inside Heavenly Court, there was no need to lie. Back then, to repay the favor of saving him in the winds of assimilation, Feng Jiu Ge blocked Wu Yong's assault. Now, it also fitted Feng Jiu Ge's nature to expose this secret true inheritance to him.

In this battle, Fang Yuan still let him go, causing Feng Jiu Ge to survive again.

...

Central Continent's Refinement Path Convention started, multiple battlefields were created as Gu Immortals fought intensely.

At such a crucial timing, Feng Jiu Ge was instead inside the River of Time.

"That... really is a stone lotus island?" Feng Jiu Ge was shook internally, the stone lotus island within the mist appeared in front of him, as Fang Yuan had predicted.

He saw Red Lotus' will on the island.

Red Lotus' will smiled: "You are finally here, Feng Jiu Ge. This is the true inheritance that I left specially for you."

Feng Jiu Ge frowned: "No matter how much you give me, it will not change my stance."

Red Lotus' will shook his head: "I had never thought of bribing you, your choice is your own decision. I just feel that this true inheritance should be left to you. Of course, you can refuse to take it. Even if you destroy it, I am not going to stop you."

Feng Jiu Ge believed in himself, after considering it, he decided to accept the true inheritance, he immersed himself in a certain segment of the memories of Red Lotus' life.

Red Lotus was undergoing tribulation, trying to get to rank nine venerable realm.

The terrifying might of the calamities and tribulations made Feng Jiu Ge extremely shocked and fearful!

After the tribulation was over, only half of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals who helped Red Lotus were alive. The most painful thing to Red Lotus was that his wife Liu Shu Xian had died.

This was his most beloved woman.

"Don't leave me, Shu Xian!" Red Lotus hugged Liu Shu Xian as tears poured down his face.

Liu Shu Xian smiled: "It's no use, I have been struck by the tribulation. Having a trace of my soul left to take a final look at you is already an enormous fortune. How could I possibly ask for more?"

"I am useless, I am useless! I underwent tribulation but implicated you!" Hong Ting's head was lowered with tears rolling down his eyes.

"No, Hong Ting. That tribulation could only have been blocked by my special physique. Even if you all sacrificed your lives, you would only have failed. I was born with one of the ten extreme physiques and encountered you, it was all fate's arrangement. In your fatal moment, I suddenly understood the greatest meaning of my life, it was to protect you, to block the tribulation for you and help you ascend to the position of an Immortal Venerable! Now... I have accomplished it."

"No, No! Xian Er, I would rather not be an Immortal Venerable, I only want you to live, I only want you to live!" Hong Ting roared helplessly, his body was shaking and his tears were falling.

"Everything and everyone in this world has its own respective fate, it is fixed. Hong Ting, you cannot have such thoughts, you need to live on properly, your fate is to become an Immortal Venerable, lead Heavenly Court and spread the glory of the righteous path throughout the five regions... Do you know? I had always been wanting to see that scene, standing by your side and accompanying you as you bring fortune to the world with invincible might. Unfortunately, I won't be able to see it..."

Liu Shu Xian's life force gradually fell, until she died.

Hong Ting's head was lowered and his back was bent deeply like an old man, a heavy shadow shrouded his face.

At this moment, he seemed to have lost all signs of life.

Incomparable grief, it was as if his heart had died!

Regret Gu formed in Red Lotus' immortal aperture, he decided to change everything. For the sake of this, he turned on Duke Long and Heavenly Court.

He went on the opposite path!

Red Lotus used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth tens or hundreds of times.

The tribulation faded, this time, even though Liu Shu Xian was heavily injured, she still had one breath left.

"Xian Er, you are still alive, you are still alive, this is great!" Red Lotus was overjoyed.

Guh.

Liu Shu Xian suddenly spat out a mouthful of blood, her last breath was used up.

"Xian Er!!" Red Lotus was shocked, he looked at Liu Shu Xian's corpse in a daze as his eyes turned red.

"I can still do it, I can see hope. As long as I continue working hard, I will definitely become strong enough to save Xian Er's life!" A fierce light flashed in Red Lotus' eyes, he muttered to himself as if he had gone into a demonic trance.

Rebirth after rebirth, he continued to be reborn.

Using the advantage of rebirth, he got stronger and stronger, he became more capable of handling different situations. He had abundant experience, he made use of every portion of resources and elevated his strength to his greatest limit.

However, like an endless loop, each time, he had to face the tribulation of becoming a venerable.

The scale and might of the tribulation was adjusted according to the changes that happened to Red Lotus! This made sure that the result of the tribulation had never changed.

Those Gu Immortals that should have died still died, including Liu Shu Xian.

Red Lotus continued to try without giving up. Ten times, a hundred times, a thousand times, ten thousand times!

He analyzed, he calculated, he maximized the value of every single resource he had, he asked for all the help he needed from Heavenly Court to the best of their ability.

...

"Xian Er!" Red Lotus hugged Liu Shu Xian.

Liu Shu Xian gave him a final glance: "It is great that you are safe." After saying that, she died.

...

"Xian Er!" Red Lotus hugged Liu Shu Xian again.

Liu Shu Xian did not have the strength to talk, she exerted her strength and wanted to raise her hand to touch Red Lotus' face but she did not succeed. Midway, her arms fell to the ground.

...

"Xian Er!" Red Lotus shouted furiously, he watched as Liu Shu Xian was reduced to ashes within the lightning tribulation.

...

"Shu Xian." Red Lotus looked at Liu Shu Xian who was badly poisoned, his footsteps slowed down.

Liu Shu Xian's entire body was black-purple, poisonous blood flowed out of her seven orifices, she smiled pitifully: "Hong Ting, don't be sad because of me. All the sacrifices are worth it, you must become a venerable, you will lead Heavenly Court and the whole of humanity."

These were her final words.

Red Lotus stopped walking, he stared at the pool of poisonous water formed from Liu Shu Xian's corpse, he held his fist as he gritted his teeth: "She died again! I need to continue working harder!!"

...

"Shu Xian!" After the tribulation, Red Lotus flew towards Liu Shu Xian again.

Liu Shu Xian shook her head, she was pale: "I am going to die, I can no longer accompany you, my most beloved."

"It will depend on the situation to see if you die. Let me check!" Red Lotus had not given up.

"I know my own condition, listen to me, at the final moment of my life, I want to tell you..." Liu Shu Xian's aura got weaker as she spoke weakly with pauses in the middle.

Red Lotus did not listen to her, he was focused on inspecting her body condition.

The result was that there was no way to save her, by the time he reacted, Liu Shu Xian who was in his arms had already died.

"There must be some way, I can definitely improve further!" Red Lotus reminded himself.

...

Attempts after attempts, failure after failure.

It was as if Hong Ting was trapped, no matter what method he used, even if he avoided the tribulation, Liu Shu Xian still died.

Feng Jiu Ge watched Red Lotus fail time and time again, he repeated attempts after attempts, an intense feeling of sadness and grief accumulated in his heart.

He watched as Red Lotus screamed, he watched as Red Lotus got agitated, he watched as Red Lotus gritted his teeth, he watched as Red Lotus left in hatred, as he went through another cycle of rebirth.

Each time, Red Lotus carried hope, but he gained disappointment instead.

The tribulation to become venerable was unavoidable, he could not give up on it, but he could not control it either.

Liu Shu Xian was a wall that could not be avoided. Each time Red Lotus was reborn, he would need to accept this cruel fact. Each time he tried, he would see his beloved woman die in the end. Each time he got injured, the pain in his heart would be the same as physical pain on his body, but Red Lotus still continued to rebirth, it was as if he were holding a knife to his heart, stabbing at it continuously.

Even though Feng Jiu Ge held deep admiration and sympathy for Red Lotus, he alerted himself to control his emotions, this might be a venerable method after all.

As an observer, Feng Jiu Ge kept a cool perspective, he gradually realized: In the initial stages, Red Lotus would still scream at heaven in great agony whenever she died.

But towards the later stages, Red Lotus stubbornly analyzed the situation with a rational mind, his expression was dark.

At the final stage, Red Lotus' efficiency got higher and higher, whenever he saw that Liu Shu Xian could not be saved, he would instantly rebirth without any hesitation.

Finally, there was one attempt.

Liu Shu Xian fell on the ground, the bones in her entire body were broken, she laid in a pool of blood with her final breath left.

Red Lotus descended rapidly, quickly approaching her.

"Hong Ting... I am going to die, you must..." Liu Shu Xian smiled, watching as Red Lotus rapidly approached her.

Red Lotus had a cold expression, he looked at her impassively: "There is no saving you. I failed again but it is alright, I will never give up, I am going to try once more."

Liu Shu Xian was shocked: "Hong Ting, what are you saying?"

Red Lotus turned around and left as Liu Shu Xian who was behind him called out with her dying breath: "Hong Ting..."

Red Lotus moved quickly initially but when he heard Liu Shu Xian's desperate cry, his footsteps slowed down as he came to a halt.

He looked down at his two hands.

In the deathly silence, Red Lotus stared with wide eyes, his body started to shake.

Suddenly, he felt like he could see himself, at this moment, he felt utter shock, there was a sense of immense fear in him.

Chapter 1964: Red Lotus' Death

"Why? Why did I become such a scary person?"

In the past, Hong Ting would feel grief at Liu Shu Xian's death, he would feel regret and hatred. He would hug Liu Shu Xian's corpse as he knelt on the ground, crying his heart out.

But now?

Facing Liu Shu Xian's death, seeing the final moment of Liu Shu Xian's life, towards the lover who only wanted to spend her final breath talking to her most beloved, Red Lotus turned around and left!

Was this Liu Shu Xian not the real Liu Shu Xian?

Of course she was real!

Red Lotus was clear about this.

She was still her, that same Liu Shu Xian, regardless of how many times Red Lotus was reborn, her determination and actions had never changed. She was willing to sacrifice herself to protect her lover, she used her life to block his venerable tribulation!

But...

Liu Shu Xian was still Liu Shu Xian, but Hong Ting was no longer the same Hong Ting.

"Since when did it start? Since when did I turn into this?" Red Lotus asked his inner self.

This question was not hard at all, he soon found the answer.

His countless rebirths, his countless attempts, the countless times Liu Shu Xian died, and the countless times he received disappointment!

His heart was hurt time and again, he bled each time, before the scab formed, Hong Ting tore open his wounds once more.

He was hurt too many times, he felt pain too many times, he regretted too many times.

Too many times indeed, eventually, he got used to it, he became... gradually numb.

Thus, he started to calculate with precision.

Thus, he started to analyze rationally.

He used every resource he had to strengthen himself and equip himself. He tried different methods in search of the strongest and most likely solution to preserve Liu Shu Xian's life when he underwent his tribulation.

When he started to think rationally, when he started to feel rational about Liu Shu Xian's death, even though he forced himself to be rational at the start, he changed.

Next, slowly, step by step, he turned into someone that he did not recognize.

This person made him feel extremely shocked and fearful.

Followed by a deep sense of helplessness!

This scene left an extremely deep impression in Feng Jiu Ge —

Red Lotus stood on the spot, lowering his arms, he was young but his back was hunched, like an old man about to die.

Silently, two trails of tears flowed down his cheeks.

Silently weeping.

Behind Red Lotus, there was Liu Shu Xian who called him with her dying breath, hoping that he would turn around, so that she could see her most beloved person at the final moment of her life.

But Red Lotus did not turn around to look at her.

Red Lotus no longer loved her.

After all, if he really loved this person in his heart and she was about to die, would he coldly turn around to leave?

Of course he would not!

Even though his goal was to use rebirth to save Liu Shu Xian, that was only a deeply rooted objective that he had.

The reason behind it was no longer love.

It was truly laughable.

He wanted to save the most beloved person in his life, but along the way, Red Lotus lost his love.

No matter how many times Liu Shu Xian died, she did not betray him, she sacrificed herself for him.

But Red Lotus himself had changed.

He betrayed his past self, he betrayed Liu Shu Xian.

He wanted to rebirth and change the past, but to think that it was rebirth that changed him.

From now what, what should he do?

Since he no longer loved Liu Shu Xian, why should he continue to rebirth and try to save her?

Of course, he had other regrets, he loved his parents deeply.

But did Red Lotus dare to attempt this?

He could almost tell the results already. After witnessing the death of his parents time and again, he would get used to it, he would get numb, he would accept this result that was decreed by fate.

Red Lotus did not dare!

Then, should he accept this result? After rebirth, should he pretend to be unaware of everything, to follow the path set by Fate and become a venerable, before becoming the Heavenly Court Immortal Venerable that everyone including his master wanted to see?

Red Lotus did not want that!

He still had love in his heart, towards his parents and master. Because there was love, there was also regret.

He also had hatred in his heart, he hated Fate, because he no longer loved Liu Shu Xian, he also hated himself. He had all sorts of complex emotions in his heart, Red Lotus was unsure about them himself.

Red Lotus asked himself truthfully, he inspected his inner self.

He still wanted to destroy fate Gu.

But the intention was already different.

He started to research and found more of the hidden profundities within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. When he comprehended the crucial factor, love Gu, he successfully used it to save Liu Shu Xian's life!

Of course, the price was that Red Lotus succeeded in the tribulation but did not become venerable.

As an observer, Feng Jiu Ge understood clearly: This was definitely a major breakthrough!

The venerable tribulation could not be controlled by man.

No matter how Red Lotus stalled it, he had to undergo tribulation eventually.

But using love Immortal Gu, he finally changed a fixed result! Instead of dying, Liu Shu Xian managed to survive.

Of course, there was a backlash of Red Lotus not becoming venerable, that was also a result.

Both results changed!

"Shu Xian, Shu Xian, you are still alive! You finally survived!" Red Lotus who succeeded was very excited, he hugged Liu Shu Xian.

Liu Shu Xian was in low spirits: "What is going on? Hong Ting, you did not become venerable?!"

Red Lotus laughed loudly: "That is because I used love Gu. Do you know how many times I was reborn while trying to save you? You should have died during the tribulation, but because of my countless attempts, I researched the human path methods contained within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>..."

Red Lotus was incredibly excited, he talked about his difficult journey, his experiences and hard work, the trials and ordeals that he went through each time in his experimentation.

"But I finally succeeded, I finally succeeded!" Red Lotus raised his arms and cheered: "Even though this is a minor change, this is the proper direction. One day, I will succeed completely!"

Slap.

A crisp sound was heard as Liu Shu Xian gave Red Lotus a slap.

Red Lotus instantly froze, his cheering came to a stop as he stared at Liu Shu Xian.

Liu Shu Xian's eyes had tears: "Hong Ting, are you still yourself? You actually had such heretical thoughts? You actually wanted to change the past! You defied fate, no wonder you failed to become venerable after the tribulation! You did all these just so I could survive?"

"All those people who helped you in the tribulation, what about the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals who were sacrificed? You said that you are doing all this for me, but have you ever considered my feelings?!"

"I, Liu Shu Xian, was born with one of the ten extreme physiques and encountered you, it was all fate's arrangement. In your fatal moment, I understood the greatest meaning of my life, it was to protect you, to block the tribulation for you and help you ascend to the position of an Immortal Venerable!"

"But you actually did this! For me, you abandoned the most precious chance to become venerable!"

"If you cannot become venerable, what will happen to Heavenly Court? What will happen to the world? What about humanity?"

"You forgot your master's teachings, you let down the expectations of your deceased parents! I am truly hurt, my heart really hurts!"

"I would rather sacrifice myself!"

"Your love towards me is just a small love. Greater love is for humanity, for the myriad living beings in this world!"

"Hong Ting, I am truly disappointed in you."

Liu Shu Xian cried profusely.

Red Lotus stared at Liu Shu Xian in a daze, after a long while, he let out a breath of air.

"So that was it." Red Lotus had a calm expression, his gaze became eerie and dark.

Liu Shu Xian grabbed his arms: "Quickly think of a method, you must have some way, right? Let everything return to its original path as decreed by Fate, even if I have to be sacrificed. How can our love compare to the greater love of heaven and earth, how can it compare to the grand ambitions of Heavenly Court?"

"Guh!" Liu Shu Xian's body suddenly shook, she lowered her head as she looked at her chest.

Red Lotus's hand directly stabbed into her heart, it was a fatal blow!

Liu Shu Xian looked at her lover in disbelief.

"Maybe killing you will return everything to its original path." Red Lotus looked at Liu Shu Xian in the eye as he said plainly.

Liu Shu Xian showed a blissful smile as he said: "Hong Ting, I was not wrong about you. Please... please become a venerable."

At the next moment, she died again.

Similar to the countless times Red Lotus had experienced, Liu Shu Xian died again.

But compared to the countless times Red Lotus had experienced, there was a difference.

Liu Shu Xian was truly dead!

In Red Lotus's heart, she was completely dead!

From then on, she never lived again.

Red Lotus looked at her corpse with calm emotions, there was not even any ripple in his heart.

The woman he had once loved deeply, he was willing to give up anything for her, he was reborn time and time again, working hard to save this woman who he had never given up on.

But now, he killed her.

He personally killed her!

Red Lotus felt no regret in his heart, he even gained some insight.

The cause of this tragedy was in Heavenly Court, it was fate Gu.

At this moment, his determination to destroy fate Gu could not be any firmer!

Feng Jiu Ge felt the scene in front of him change.

Heavenly Court.

The battle was over, the entire area was in ruins.

On the damaged top floor of Heaven Overseeing Tower, Duke Long and Red Lotus faced each other.

Duke Long had evidently undergone a tough battle, he was covered in blood and injuries.

He looked at Red Lotus as he sighed deeply: "Oh Hong Ting, one mistake leads to countless mistakes, to think that you have already reached this point. You want to destroy fate Gu? Go ahead."

Saying this, Duke Long took the initiative to give way!

Red Lotus was slightly shocked, he walked towards fate Gu. Most Gu worms had fragile bodies, but no matter how much force he used, fate Gu was like the strongest object in the world, he could not destroy it.

"Regardless of what method you use, you cannot destroy fate Gu. Hong Ting, you are not the only one, be they Limitless Demon Venerable or Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, they came here in the past, but their methods were all useless against fate Gu."

"In this world, only a complete otherworldly demon can destroy fate Gu! But otherworldly demons are not complete when they come into our world. Thus, nobody in this world can destroy fate Gu."

Duke Long said this as he showed intense fatigue: "Hong Ting, come back! It is not too late to turn over a new leaf! Even though you have sinned greatly and made many mistakes, Heavenly Court and I are willing to give you a chance to redeem yourself, we can start over again!"

Even at this point, Duke Long was still urging Red Lotus, he was unwilling to give up.

Red Lotus was silent for a long time, he turned around to face Duke Long, smiling: "Oh master, since the two Demon Venerables could not destroy fate Gu, why did you not place fate Gu in front of me from the start, to let me try doing so and give up?"

Duke Long was silent.

Red Lotus continued as he smiled: "That means you are afraid too, right? You are afraid that I might have a brand new method that is able to destroy fate Gu."

Duke Long smiled bitterly: "Of course. Times are changing, Gu cultivation paths are emerging endlessly. Many theories in the past are no longer appropriate now, even I am unsure if there is really a way to destroy fate Gu. But at this time, I can no longer stop you, I can only take a risk and try. But you've seen the result yourself, too?"

Red Lotus pondered: "Fate Gu arranged the lives of everyone and everything in this world, you and I, even a rock or a ripple in a lake is part of this. But master, have you ever thought about it?"

"A human is not a rock nor a ripple, we have cognition. If a person is not happy with the life arranged by fate, what should this person do?"

Duke Long looked at Red Lotus: "You've read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> too, when Ren Zu met fate Gu, he tried to escape from its restraints and pursue freedom Gu. What happened to him? He did not manage to grasp freedom, he lost himself and became insane, he sank into madness!"

"This is the outcome, this is the warning! A person has to accept their fate and live their life, they have to shoulder the responsibilities given to them by fate, they need to do what they are tasked to do!!"

Red Lotus laughed loudly: "I understand, thank you master for the teaching."

Duke Long saw that his expression was strange, he felt something amiss.

At the next moment, extreme fear and shock appeared on Duke Long's face.

He found that as Red Lotus exerted strength in his fingers, the fate Gu in his hand was actually shaking lightly, cracks appeared all over its body.

"Red Lotus!!" Duke Long was furious, he attacked.

He went all out!

Red Lotus did not dodge at all, he was hit by Duke Long.

This was a fatal injury!

"You?!" Duke Long was shocked, he suddenly realized that Red Lotus had purposely angered him so that he would deal a fatal blow.

At the final moment of his life, Red Lotus still smiled as he faced Duke Long: "Master, I've always admired and cared for you, even after countless rebirths, my admiration towards you have never decreased."

"But now, I need you to understand something. Look at me."

"Fate has given such preferential treatment to me, arranging such high status and accomplishments. But I was not happy, I wanted to rebel. Then let me ask you, in this world, there are countless others who lead worse lives than me, what do they think of Fate?"

"People are not rocks or ripples, we have cognition. The truth is, cognitive madness is the most scary thing, it is the most powerful!"

Saying so, Red Lotus handed fate Gu to Duke Long.

"This is all I can do."

"Love Gu is able to damage Fate. Hehehe, master, are you shocked?"

"It is a pity that I am not an otherworldly demon."

"But I tried my best to make arrangements, I did everything that I could. I left hope for the future! Other than that, there is nothing to look forward to in my life, I might as well die like this now."

"But I believe that one day, one day in the future, fate Gu will be destroyed! Even if it is not me, someone else will do it."

"I want to believe that in the future, I will not be alone, a group of people will attempt to destroy Fate."

"Master, you cannot stop it, Heavenly Court cannot stop it, because you cannot stop people from thinking with their free will!"

Chapter 1965: He Was Still Feng Jiu Ge

On stone lotus island, Feng Jiu Ge browsed through the memories left behind by Red Lotus.

He returned to reality.

Red Lotus' will was like a real person, extremely vivid: "Other than my memories, I have two things for you. One is rank eight future self killer move, the other is the Immortal Gu recipe of destiny Gu."

Next, Red Lotus' will explained in detail: "Rank eight future self killer move will allow you to instantly gain pseudo venerable battle strength. After all, you are the Dao Guardian of the predestined Great Dream Immortal Venerable. In history, as long as Dao Guardians matured, they would have such a cultivation level. Future self will also allow you to utilize your strongest state in the future at this moment."

"As for destiny Gu's Immortal Gu recipe, even though it is just an incomplete Gu recipe, it was created according to the destiny song that you will create in the future. It has the same origin as your destiny song."

"A thousand years later, you will create the complete destiny song. But I cannot give it to you directly, because fate Gu is not destroyed completely yet, it will not allow this."

"Thus, I used another method, converting it into a rank nine destiny Gu recipe, it will be a huge help to you, you will comprehend destiny song in its initial form."

Feng Jiu Ge was moved.

The true inheritance from Red Lotus' will was completely suited for his needs, he could not refuse.

But he did not lose his cool, he acutely sensed the meaning behind Red Lotus' will's words.

"The initial form of destiny song?" Feng Jiu Ge asked.

Red Lotus's will nodded: "Indeed. For the following thousand years, you will modify destiny song many times. Eventually, you will make this killer move extremely profound, at the last modification, this killer move will actually possess the ability to grow on its own. The more Gu Immortals hit by it, the more it can extract the power of destiny from them to grow further. This is an excellent killer move."

"However, I need to remind you something. As long as fate Gu still exists, your destiny song will be suppressed and sealed."

Feng Jiu Ge shook his head: "Red Lotus Demon Venerable, thank you for the true inheritance. I understand what you mean, in fact, before now, Fang Yuan had already reminded me many times. But I will not destroy Fate or resist Heavenly Court just because of your true inheritance."

Red Lotus' will smiled lightly: "I am not asking for anything. I am only sharing my experience with you, I placed this crucial strength to break free from fate in your hands, as for your choice, that is up to you. The decision will be made by you in the end, won't it?"

Feng Jiu Ge left the stone lotus island with a heavy heart.

Fate showed preferential treatment for Red Lotus Demon Venerable, even though it took his parents and lover, he was given unparalleled talent and aptitude, he had supreme strength and status. But Red Lotus was not willing to accept this.

People were not puppets, they had their own thoughts.

"Even the venerable Red Lotus was like this, what about me, a Dao Guardian?" Feng Jiu Ge thought about himself.

Seeing the growth of Feng Jin Huang could truly bring joy and happiness to her parents.

Let alone his Dao Guardian status, even without it, why would Feng Jiu Ge not defend his own daughter?

"But, is this Dao Guardian status something I like and truly desire?" Feng Jiu Ge asked himself in his heart.

The truth was, nobody had ever asked him about it.

Be they Duke Long, Qin Ding Ling, or even the supreme elders of Spirit Affinity House, nobody asked him.

It was as if this status was glory, it was something natural to accept, Feng Jiu Ge should have been overjoyed to receive it, there was no need to ask such a redundant question.

But was it really that case?

Feng Jiu Ge thought of another deeper question: "Why do people live?"

This problem was just too broad and deep, the answer varied according to the person, a thousand people would come up with a thousand answers, in fact, even the same person would have different answers at different time periods.

Feng Jiu Ge could not answer this question.

He could only take a step back and ask himself truthfully: "For what purpose do I live?"

Feng Jiu Ge could not help but think back to his life experience.

He loved music when he was young, he did not hesitate to cultivate sound path.

From the start of his cultivation journey, he wanted to create a total of nine songs, to express himself, to express all living beings, and to express heaven and earth.

After that, he found a fortuitous encounter in a mountain valley, he by chance discovered the inheritance left behind by a sound path great expert, Spatial Sound Immortal Master.

He started to cultivate in the valley alone, feeling no loneliness at all. He was immersed in the delight of music, he cultivated and lived every day in a fulfilling manner. In this valley, he easily passed the crucial tribulation and became a rank six Gu Immortal without causing a commotion.

After becoming a Gu Immortal, Feng Jiu Ge did not have any emotion of pride or desire to show off.

Everything was natural, plain and simple.

He continued to cultivate in the valley and develop his immortal aperture, going from rank six to rank seven.

One day, two Gu Immortals arrived in the valley, they sang with Feng Jiu Ge.

Back then, it was nighttime with the moon hanging high and light wind blowing gently, causing ripples in a glittering lake in the valley.

As the three Gu Immortals sang in harmony, time flew by rapidly, and they had sung till dawn.

The three stopped singing and started laughing. They did not greet each other, but left full of joy.

Afterwards, the two were framed and hunted by the righteous path, after Feng Jiu Ge learned of this, he did not hesitate, he stepped forward to help them.

Thereafter, the unstoppable legend was created, he fought against all ten great ancient sects alone, he became a renowned champion in the world!

The ten great ancient sects lost their reputation, they accused Feng Jiu Ge of being a demonic cultivator and joined forces to resist him.

Feng Jiu Ge was not afraid, fighting as he continuously traveled a huge distance, suddenly changing his tactic and going for the enemy headquarters, causing the ten sects to lose miserably. The scene was total chaos and there was nothing anyone could do.

During this process, Feng Jiu Ge met with Spirit Affinity House's Fairy Bai Qing, they developed feelings for each other, Feng Jiu Ge went into Spirit Affinity House and became a righteous path member.

Afterwards, Spirit Affinity House's reputation soared, by relying on Feng Jiu Ge's strength, their territory expanded, firmly suppressing the other nine ancient sects.

Following that, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed, Feng Jiu Ge led his group to investigate the situation.

Thus, a series of future events occurred, he was by chance saved by Fang Yuan and repaid the debt in Southern Border, blocking Wu Yong for him. After repaying the debt, Feng Jiu Ge chased after Fang Yuan again.

Until this point, Fang Yuan let Feng Jiu Ge go multiple times and even reminded and guided him to the stone lotus island, gaining a Red Lotus true inheritance.

"If my entire life's journey was arranged by fate Gu, was I willingly living this life?"

Feng Jiu Ge shook his head, he was more willing to see it from another perspective: "It was all my choice! Back then, I chose to stand up for the two immortals, I gave up my life of peaceful seclusion because of the anger in my heart, I wanted to seek justice."

"I married Fairy Bai Qing and had a child with her, that was because I loved her. I taught my daughter Feng Jin Huang and raised her into an adult, that was also my love to my child. It was not decreed by Fate."

"If Fate wants me to lose Bai Qing and Jin Huang, will I do the same as Red Lotus?"

"If I have a good chance at this moment, in which as long as I make a move, I can destroy Fate, will I do it?"

Destroying Fate went against his own benefits. After all, Feng Jin Huang was the Great Dream Immortal Venerable decreed by fate Gu!

"But does Feng Jin Huang herself really want to become Great Dream Immortal Venerable?"

Feng Jiu Ge suddenly realized that just like how nobody had asked him if he wanted his status as a Dao Guardian, nobody had asked Feng Jin Huang if she really wanted to become Great Dream Immortal Venerable.

Including Feng Jiu Ge himself!

It was as if everything was natural and a matter of fact, there was nothing to question.

Feng Jiu Ge asked himself an even deeper question.

"If Huang Er likes the fate of becoming Great Dream Immortal Venerable, while fate Gu is right in front of me and I can easily destroy it. Then, will I do it?"

This question made Feng Jiu Ge hesitate, he was unsure, he was perplexed, he was lost.

Reality did not give him time or space to think about this closely.

The battle to repair fate Gu was still in heated commotion now, Feng Jiu Ge had to join the battle.

On Hairy Foot Mountain, he saved Feng Jin Huang by singing destiny song.

With rank eight future self, he was one of the strongest Gu Immortals in the world. Destiny song's power made even Di Zang Sheng falter.

On the battlefield, Feng Jiu Ge met with Fang Yuan once again.

Fang Yuan transmitted secretly: "Oh Feng Jiu Ge, you finally created destiny song. What do you think of this killer move?"

Feng Jiu Ge was silent.

He had to admit that this was truly his song, it was a song that he would create with his personality. His voice was contained in this song.

Yes, he did not want to acknowledge the existence of fate, but he felt deep emotions towards the cruelty and profundity of fate. He observed the lives of countless people, they had their highs and lows, he saw the hope, struggle, joy, happiness, sadness, and despair of these people..."

"If one says that fate is fixed while luck is a variable, then I desire that variable to exist within the people and all lifeforms, these changes should occur from one's own choice!"

Feng Jiu Ge understood the truest intention in his heart.

"I did not create fate song, I created destiny song! This is the most honest thought I have in my inner heart."

At this moment, he realized the scheme that Fang Yuan and Red Lotus Demon Venerable had plotted.

They knew about his nature, so they did not try to convince him. They only passed destiny song to Feng Jiu Ge, and used Feng Jiu Ge's voice to convince himself.

Indeed.

This destiny song that Feng Jiu Ge sang allowed him to support the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals and raise their strength. When he sang for the enemies, they would weaken. But the truth was, he was singing for himself, he was singing to understand his true feelings!

And thus, he understood.

He loved Fairy Bai Qing, he also loved his daughter Feng Jiu Ge. But Feng Jiu Ge was not alive for their sake.

His wife and daughter were just choices he made in his life journey, they were part of his life, but not the entirety.

"For what purpose am I alive?"

This question brought him back to the starting point, he wanted to sing nine songs, to express life, to express heaven and earth!

Currently, he had already created nine songs. But he has not sang everything about life and the world yet, he had to continue singing.

But as he sang, fate restrained him, it was like an invisible pair of hands strangling him, how could he sing freely like this?

Seeing that Feng Jiu Ge did not reply to him, Fang Yuan transmitted while in intense combat: "Oh Feng Jiu Ge, your voice is your aspiration, how can the person who created destiny song be aligned with Heavenly Court?"

Feng Jiu Ge was calm as he replied secretly: "You know me well! But even so, I will not join you. Unless you can create a situation where we can easily destroy Fate, otherwise, I will not help you before that. Heavenly Court and Central Continent have treated me well, so everything still depends on you."

Fang Yuan chuckled: "Then watch properly."

Next, he purposely got hit by Duke Long, he fell towards Embroidered Tower, activating Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's hidden arrangement.

Unexpected to Feng Jiu Ge, Fang Yuan used Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's strength to overwhelm heaven, directly destroying fate Gu.

After that, upon hearing Duke Long's words, Feng Jiu Ge realized that the battle had not ended yet.

When Red Lotus' will appeared once more, Feng Jiu Ge gradually realized the plot that Red Lotus Demon Venerable had set.

Thus, when Fang Yuan asked for destiny Gu's recipe, Feng Jiu Ge finally took action.

He helped Fang Yuan, he was also making his own choice!

In the past, when he helped the two immortals while challenging the ten great ancient sects, he had once said: "Neither demonic nor righteous, there is only Feng Jiu Ge in this world. To leave or to stay, I decide my own life and death."

Now, should he stay or leave?

This question could not puzzle him anymore.

He, Feng Jiu Ge, had turned from the demonic path to the righteous path, now, it was time to go back!

Because Feng Jiu Ge was still Feng Jiu Ge in the end.

Chapter 1966: Great Era!

"Feng Jiu Ge!" Duke Long screamed, charging towards him.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Claw Strike!

Immortal killer move — Spiraling Dragon Fang!

Claw marks emerged, nearly ten feet long, cutting through the air with invincible might. Dragon fangs flew everywhere, like piercing sharp blades, circling and flying while emitting murderous aura.

Feng Jiu Ge retreated slowly as he continued to sing his destiny song.

Around him, there were several clones, they looked like him but had mystical powers.

Immortal killer move — Song Warrior!

Song warriors fought for Feng Jiu Ge, not only blocking the dragon claws and fangs but even fighting against Duke Long.

After several rounds, Duke Long destroyed a song warrior.

But next, a brand new song warrior appeared on the battlefield, engaging with Duke Long in combat.

Duke Long instantly understood that killing these clones was pointless, the true way to fight was to go after the source, to directly deal with Feng Jiu Ge.

Immortal killer move — Dragon Gate.

Duke Long crossed a large distance and approached Feng Jiu Ge.

Feng Jiu Ge calmly activated yang pass tune as he pulled apart their distance once again.

Duke Long was unable to fight Feng Jiu Ge in close combat, he could only use qi path killer moves to attack at a distance.

Feng Jiu Ge showed no fear, his destiny song continued to weaken Duke Long while he used his hands to unleash the triple extreme sound killer move, with drum fist, bell palm, and finger whistle.

Feng Jiu Ge fought against Duke Long while exchanging many blows, they unexpectedly were evenly matched!

Rank eight future self brought a qualitative transformation to Feng Jiu Ge's battle strength.

While the three regions' Gu Immortals hesitated on whether to help Feng Jiu Ge, they were shocked to realize: Feng Jiu Ge did not need anyone's help!

The battle strength he displayed shocked everyone.

Duke Long was unable to take down Feng Jiu Ge, he was shocked and furious. At this point, he realized that even though Feng Jiu Ge was fighting earlier, he had been keeping his true strength hidden, he did not use his full power at all.

Right now, Duke Long wanted to destroy Red Lotus' scheme. But Fang Yuan was a tough enemy, Duke Long knew about his strength, so he chose to fight Feng Jiu Ge instead.

As long as Feng Jiu Ge was disrupted and destiny song failed to activate, then Fang Yuan and the others would not have the Immortal Gu recipe, they would not succeed.

But Feng Jiu Ge's strength far exceeded Duke Long's expectations, he could only attack more aggressively while trying to take down Feng Jiu Ge as soon as possible.

Duke Long was stalled by Feng Jiu Ge, while Wu Shuai controlled Dragon Palace to defend Fang Yuan's main body, Calamity Luck Altar was blocking Demon Judgment Board.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals unleashed a storm of attacks but the other three regions' Gu Immortals and Di Zang Sheng stopped them.

The battle situation was tilting in the favor of the three regions' Gu Immortals, but Fang Yuan was facing a problem now.

The sea of human wills was vast and turbulent.

Using the human wills as Gu material to refine destiny Gu was wishful thinking.

But it was a possible method.

Under the effect of destiny song, the human wills and flames merged, refined into a mystical Gu material that was formless and colorless.

Fang Yuan, who was controlling this Gu refinement session, had to endure the terrifying waves of human wills. He had to calm the human wills like subduing tides, sending them to the respective tributaries.

Fang Yuan's expression quickly turned dark, his veins were bulging on his forehead, thoughts collided endlessly in his mind, he could not keep up with this expenditure, his storage of thoughts was rapidly used up, about to be emptied!

At the periphery of the battlefield, Spectral Soul and his servants kept a close watch on the situation.

Fairy Zi Wei saw Fang Yuan's expression as she analyzed: "Oh no, Fang Yuan is not in good shape. I know about his wisdom path foundation, he is most skilled at blocking deductions and concealing his true location. But this refinement expends his thoughts and focuses on his cognitive ability. The sea of human will is truly terrifying, even I myself cannot last long in it."

But Spectral Soul smiled lightly, saying calmly: "Don't worry, a certain venerable has already prepared for this. Fang Yuan should know what to do."

Spectral Soul could not help but recall the past.

When he was still alive, exploring Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

There, he found wisdom Gu, he also saw Giant Sun's special will left behind by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Back then, he wanted to immediately take wisdom Gu for himself.

"Spectral Soul, I would like you to let wisdom Gu remain here." Giant Sun's special will had to show up and stop him.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable smiled coldly: "You can't stop me."

Giant Sun's special will nodded: "Of course, you are the current Demon Venerable, invincible in the world, I have no way of stopping you. But I am sure you have made a deal with Red Lotus Demon Venerable already?"

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's expression changed, before coming here, he had obtained one Red Lotus true inheritance, he made a deal with Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

"You mean to say?" Spectral Soul Demon Venerable hesitated.

"That's right, my main body has made arrangements in this wisdom Gu. When the crucial person arrives, he will destroy Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, this wisdom Gu will go along with him." Giant Sun's special will said openly.

"So that's it." Spectral Soul Demon Venerable looked at wisdom Gu deeply but did not take it.

At this moment.

"I've already given it my best effort... it seems I need to use wisdom Gu after all." Fang Yuan sighed.

By now, he had already guessed many of the venerable arrangements.

Wisdom Gu was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement, but unlike those of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, it had activated long ago. Back then, Fang Yuan was unaware of this.

Fang Yuan had just opened his immortal aperture's entrance when wisdom Gu flew out by itself, floating above Fang Yuan as it emitted a divine radiance.

Fang Yuan instantly felt relaxed as his expression went back to normal, he felt a sense of ease.

"So that's it." He inspected it closely, realizing: "Wisdom Gu is one of the Gu materials, no wonder it is so effective. With the addition of wisdom Gu, my thoughts are expended more slowly, but my immortal essence expenditure is huge. This rate of consumption is not something I can sustain."

Even though the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time was very fast and could accumulate immortal essence rapidly, Fang Yuan had undergone many intense battles, the expenditure was high as well.

Once he fails to keep up with the expenditure, the Gu refinement would be forced to stop, Fang Yuan would suffer an overwhelmingly terrifying backlash!

But Fang Yuan was not flustered, he was cool as ice.

He knew clearly, at this point in time, the venerables were not going to watch by the side.

As long as he still had a trace of value, he was irreplaceable, the venerables could not allow him to die at this moment.

"Next, it should be your turn to take action, Giant Sun..."

Far away in black heaven, a dark gold palace floated quietly in the sky.

In the palace, immortal zombie Giant Sun slowly opened his eyes.

He looked towards the south, the scenes in Heavenly Court were reflected in his eyes.

"We have finally reached this moment." Immortal zombie Giant Sun smiled before sighing to himself lightly: "Red Lotus, it was your scheme that worked after all."

Certain memories in his life started to surface.

On the stone lotus island, Gu Immortal Giant Sun who had yet to become venerable received Red Lotus' gift.

At the same time, they also made a transaction.

"This is the incomplete Immortal Gu recipe of destiny Gu?" Giant Sun received this incomplete recipe and was immediately drawn to it. He was the creator of luck path, it had never failed him, but from this incomplete recipe, he saw a whole new world!

"Red Lotus, you are the one who damaged fate Gu, giving me the chance to create luck path. Now, you are gifting this incomplete recipe of destiny Gu to me, I owe you an immense favor!" Gu Immortal Giant Sun said solemnly.

"I will make the arrangements according to our agreement. I will leave wisdom Gu behind and create responsive luck Immortal Gu to help that unparalleled genius who will create destiny song. Furthermore, I will retain my final attack, as long as the situation advances to reach that stage, I will take action and help your million year plan succeed!"

Red Lotus' will smiled: "I will thank you in advance. If my plan fails, please follow our agreement and try your best to refine destiny Gu yourself."

"Of course!" Gu Immortal Giant Sun said resolutely.

...

Within Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, immortal zombie Giant Sun slowly raised his right hand.

Boom—!

An enormous beam of light flew through the sky and shot towards Heavenly Court's direction at an extreme speed.

This beam of light was so gigantic, like a large river that spanned across heaven and earth.

Wherever it went, it pushed aside all the air, the beam's movement was accompanied by a deafening and majestic sound.

Such a grand and powerful killer move shocked everyone and sent them into a daze.

Even Duke Long, Feng Jiu Ge, and Fang Yuan felt incredibly small and insignificant upon seeing this move.

The beam of light started from black heaven above Northern Plains, piercing through the regional wall and directly bombarding Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court shook intensely, the world seemed to tremble as countless Immortal Gu Houses cracked and broke.

Within Imperfection Regret Pavilion, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's silhouette gritted her teeth.

She watched as Giant Sun's attack approached, but Limitless' silhouette was drawing her attention, forcing her to have no time to deal with it.

Giant Sun's attack landed with unstoppable might, instilling itself into the sea of human wills and flames.

The three sources gathered and instantly formed a golden ball of light that was the size of a mountain.

Within the ball of light, flames flicked, human wills shined with rainbow light, incredibly dazzling. Fang Yuan remained unmoved at the center, he was controlling the situation.

Traces of pale white light started to spread out from his tightly grasped hands.

These traces of light were so familiar, Fang Yuan had a deep impression of them.

He was internally shaken: "Heaven path dao marks!"

Tens or hundreds of heaven path dao marks slipped out from the cracks between his fingers.

Fang Yuan opened his hands wide at this moment, with a loud sound, countless heaven path dao marks flew into the sky, entangling with each other.

Traces of dao marks went towards Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan grunted, intense pain assaulted him, causing his body and mind to shake!

"These are newly added heaven path dao marks on my body? Wait no, not just me..." Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light, he acutely sensed that many of the heaven path dao marks vanished all of a sudden, following the sources of the human wills.

"As expected." At this moment, Fang Yuan was finally certain about Red Lotus Demon Venerable's plan.

He wanted to refine destiny Gu but he was not truly trying to refine a Gu.

Fang Yuan grasped this chance, doing his best to collect these heaven path dao marks.

With every single heaven path dao mark carved in his body, his sovereign immortal aperture's foundation would rise by a level.

This was an unprecedented and huge fortuitous encounter!

Each complete heaven path dao mark would cause a small qualitative change in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture world.

After his trip to Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan became even clearer of the immense value of this opportunity.

But the fusing of heaven path dao marks was very painful, even someone with a firm mind like Fang Yuan started to feel dizzy after gaining ten complete heaven path dao marks.

But he was the main person refining this Gu, he could not use other methods, otherwise, he would disrupt the Gu refinement and fail the process, that would be a huge problem.

Fang Yuan relied on his determination as he gritted his teeth and held on.

He was not the only Gu Immortal enduring pain, he was just one of countless people.

At the same time, in the vast five regions, countless mortals screamed in pain, the heaven path dao marks found their way to the sources of the human wills and carved themselves into these people's bodies.

Each of these mortals could not endure even one ten-thousandth of a complete heaven path dao mark, many of them fainted at the first moment.

Those who could remain awake were fortunate, they were able to absorb more heaven path dao marks.

Pain!

Intense pain, pain that went beyond words.

Fang Yuan soon tore the skin of his lips as his eyes opened wide, even the corners of his eyes were torn, blood flowed out.

His entire body was shaking and covered in sweat, he still tried his best to continue fusing with each additional heaven path dao mark.

Soon, the Gu Immortals scattered across the five regions also started to endure this process.

Heavenly Court's fighting came to a stop, all of the Gu Immortals' expressions changed, they gritted their teeth as their faces turned red. With the addition of heaven path dao marks that automatically went to them, they were caught off guard and could barely endure this.

"No—!" Duke Long screamed in agony, at this moment, he finally realized what Red Lotus' plan was.

Duke Long was unable to take down Feng Jiu Ge after so long, he could only turn around and hope for the best as he tried to attack Fang Yuan, but the intense pain also assaulted him.

Feng Jiu Ge persisted in using destiny song, seeing that Duke Long was leaving, he quickly attacked more intensely to stall for time instead.

With a loud sound, like splattering water, the mountain-like human wills vanished on the spot.

Success!

"People of this world, I have entrusted fate to you. All of you hold a portion of fate, from today onwards, there will no longer be fate in this world!" Red Lotus' will spoke through the human wills, his voice was transmitted into the minds of everyone in the five regions.

The five regions' humans were still in agony and indescribable pain.

Because of the intense and unbearable pain, there were many cases of suicide on the spot.

"Red Lotus—!" Duke Long shouted in anger, he finally got away from Feng Jiu Ge as he arrived in front of Fang Yuan.

But it was too late.

The last bit of Red Lotus' will managed to gather into human form as it blocked the ferocious Duke Long for Fang Yuan.

"Master." The young looking Red Lotus smiled: "I succeeded at long last. Fate Gu has been split into countless portions by me and distributed to everyone in this world. It still exists, it has not been destroyed, but because fate has been fused with luck, it can no longer be used by heaven's will."

Duke Long was furious, his eyes were red, his hair standing on end.

"Traitorous disciple!" He screamed, he charged even quicker now.

At the next moment, he completely destroyed Red Lotus' will as he arrived in front of Fang Yuan.

Duke Long's aura broke through its limit again, reaching an unprecedented level, his strength was so overwhelming that even Di Zang Sheng and Feng Jiu Ge felt a threat to their lives!

Fang Yuan did not move, he did not even put up a defense.

Duke Long charged with unparalleled might, but when he was still a step away from Fang Yuan, his expression changed.

His aura froze at once, his advancement stopped.

His lifespan — was exhausted!

It was slightly earlier than in the previous life.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, he had found the truth when he saw a bit of the scattered light earlier.

The truth was, back then in Eastern Sea, when his Qi Sea Ancestor identity used steal life on Duke Long, it was effective.

But the effect was low and not easily observable, Duke Long also had incredible concealment abilities.

Afterwards, in order to avoid fighting Qi Sea Ancestor, Duke Long even took out Primordial Origin's true inheritance to successfully deceive everyone. This was because Duke Long did not know that Fang Yuan's steal life killer move had a limited number of usages.

This also caused Duke Long to become even stronger than in the previous life at the same time period.

The hero of a generation, the pillar of Heavenly Court, the master of Red Lotus, and the creator of the dragonman race — Duke Long!

Finally, his life was over.

Before dying, he still charged at the forefront.

For Heavenly Court, for the sake of humanity, he had truly done everything that he could until his death.

During the intense war, he forgot the limit of his own lifespan. Thus, at the moment of his death, other than rage and killing intent, there was also confusion on his face.

"Lord Duke Long..."

"Damn it, you must be feeling very unwilling to die like this!"

"Senior Duke Long!!!"

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals cried out loud, their morale rose sharply, this was the will of the mourning troops!

Intense battle occurred again, the Gu Immortals of the three regions were actually suppressed by Heavenly Court which had fewer numbers.

Fang Yuan no longer participated in the fight.

He still endured intense pain as his gaze pierced past Heavenly Court, overlooking the entire five regions.

Earth shook as it produced waves of deep, rumbling noises.

At this moment, the regional walls that separated the five regions had completely disappeared. The earth veins were connected as the five separate regions merged into one!

Without the obstruction of the regional walls, people could freely move through the five regions with no obstructions. At the same time, the differences in heaven and earth qi also disappeared gradually.

The bloody cape on Fang Yuan's back slowly disintegrated, he raised his head slightly and took in a deep breath.

Ah, the air was filled with freedom.

From now on, there was finally a possibility of pursuing eternal life.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's lips curled up as he revealed a faint smile.

"The great era... has finally arrived!"